Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, TertiaryColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, AlphaLevel, Encoding
Style: Default,Verdana,18,16777215,16777215,16384,16384,-1,0,1,3,2,2,10,10,12,30,0
Style: UP,Verdana,18,16777215,16777215,16384,16384,-1,0,1,3,1,6,10,10,12,30,0
[Events]
Format: Marked, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:00:00.63,0:00:02.50,UP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Ted:Okay where were we?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:00:02.52,0:00:06.64,UP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,It was June of 2006,and life had just taken\Nan unexpected turn
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:00:06.66,0:00:09.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Dad,Dad, can't you just skip ahead\Nto the part where you meet Mom?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:00:09.65,0:00:12.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I feel like you've been talking\Nfor like a year
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:00:12.39,0:00:14.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Honey, all this stuff\NI'm telling you is important.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:00:14.71,0:00:16.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,It's all part of the story.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:00:16.21,0:00:17.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Could I go to\Nthe bathroom??
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:00:17.41,0:00:18.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,No.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:00:19.21,0:00:23.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,The summer of 2006\Nwas both wonderful and awful.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:00:23.83,0:00:25.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,For me, it started out great
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:00:25.48,0:00:27.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,In fact, day one was amazing.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:00:27.65,0:00:30.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I'd finally gotten together with Robin.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:00:30.35,0:00:34.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,But while I'd been off having one of the best nights of my life,
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:00:34.32,0:00:38.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,your uncle marshall had been having one of the worst nights of his.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:00:41.34,0:00:42.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,marshall: So that's it?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:00:42.60,0:00:44.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,We're breaking up?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:00:44.31,0:00:45.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Marshall,I'm sorry.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:00:45.48,0:00:46.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I just...
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:00:46.47,0:00:53.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I just need to go to san francisco and do this art program and-and figure out who I am outside of us.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:00:53.16,0:00:56.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,And the only way that I can do that is if...
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:00:56.58,0:00:59.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,if we don't talk for a while.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:00:59.47,0:01:01.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,For a while.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:01.32,0:01:03.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Try never,okay?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:03.44,0:01:06.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You walk out that door,and we're done.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:06.31,0:01:09.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You're never going to hear my voice again.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:09.12,0:01:10.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I should call her.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:10.38,0:01:11.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,No,no.\NTed it is--
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:11.79,0:01:15.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,if you call her when she asked you not to you're just going to look weak and you're going to regret it.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:15.57,0:01:19.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Now,listen,whenever you feel like calling her,you come find me first.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:19.97,0:01:22.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,And I will punch you in the face.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:22.89,0:01:24.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You're a good friend,ted.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:27.85,0:01:28.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,So,did you hear the big news?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:29.01,0:01:31.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You mean how lily and marshall broke up,
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:31.12,0:01:36.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,and lily's gone and nothing else even remotely important happened last night,yeah,I think he knows.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:36.36,0:01:37.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Oh,my god.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:37.98,0:01:39.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I-I'm so sorry.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:39.32,0:01:41.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Wh-- what happened?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:41.29,0:01:43.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Well,she left.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:43.25,0:01:46.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,And I don't even know if she's coming back.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:46.17,0:01:48.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I didn't get your message until I woke up.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:48.19,0:01:50.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Bro,I am so sorry.\NThanks.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:50.50,0:01:52.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I know it must be tough,
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:52.31,0:01:57.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,but are you ready to hear something that will not only make you feel better,but will actively excite you?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:57.65,0:01:58.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Sure.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:01:59.01,0:02:05.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,For the first time,ever,the three of us are single at the same time.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:02:05.34,0:02:10.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I've dreamed about this day,boys,and it's going to be legendary.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:02:10.04,0:02:13.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Together,we will own this city.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:02:13.05,0:02:18.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Anytime a girl wants to get back at her ex-boyfriends,we'll be there.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:02:18.97,0:02:27.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Anytime a girl wants to solve her father issues through promiscuity and binge drinking,we will be there.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:02:27.75,0:02:31.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Anytime a bachelorette party drives through the city in a limo,
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:02:31.33,0:02:34.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,sticking their heads out the sunroof shouting,"What's up,new york?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:02:34.80,0:02:38.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect," We will be what is up new york.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:02:38.78,0:02:42.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Gentlemen,we are about to embark on...
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:02:46.16,0:02:48.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,aw,man,you guys did it,didn't you?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:02:48.55,0:02:55.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,sync:fisherchen\Nwww.YDY.com
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:02:55.94,0:03:01.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,www.YDY.com\NProudly Presents
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:03:03.21,0:03:07.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,One thing I learned that summer is that when love is beginning...
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:03:08.94,0:03:14.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,and love is ending,the first 30 days are remarkably similar.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:03:14.58,0:03:17.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,For one thing,you spend most of your time in bed.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:03:21.91,0:03:24.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,your friends can't stand to listen to you.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:03:25.41,0:03:27.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,He's so ticklish.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:03:27.91,0:03:30.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,It was a really beautiful song.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:03:30.51,0:03:31.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,So...
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:03:32.81,0:03:34.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,stupid,man.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:03:34.63,0:03:37.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,and you never seem to wear pants.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:03:41.64,0:03:43.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,hey,marshall.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:03:43.21,0:03:44.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Hey,ted.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:03:44.74,0:03:45.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You hungry?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:03:45.89,0:03:47.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,What's the point?I could eat some food.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:03:47.63,0:03:50.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,It's just going to leave me.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:03:50.06,0:03:53.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Well,at least in that scenario you get to do the dumping.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:03:54.11,0:03:56.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Come on,it's sunday.It's pancakes day.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:03:57.01,0:03:59.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Lily always made the pancakes.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:03:59.82,0:04:01.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,God,I loved her pancakes.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:01.77,0:04:03.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,So soft.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:03.31,0:04:04.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,So warm.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:04.77,0:04:07.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,So perfectly shaped.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:07.42,0:04:10.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Are we still talking about her pancakes?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:10.57,0:04:12.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Come on,you got to eat something; what can I get you?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:12.96,0:04:13.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Beer.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:13.75,0:04:15.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,No,that's what you had for dinner.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:15.84,0:04:17.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Fine.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:17.29,0:04:19.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Then I'll just have leftovers.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:21.67,0:04:24.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Barney: So,he stays home all the time not getting laid?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:25.01,0:04:28.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,No,see,that's what you do when you have a fiancé.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:28.24,0:04:29.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,He should be down here celebrating.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:29.65,0:04:31.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,He's free.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:31.05,0:04:34.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,He got that redheaded tumor removed.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:34.29,0:04:37.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You should write and illustrate children's books.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:37.46,0:04:38.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You know what marshall needs to do.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:38.90,0:04:41.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,He needs to stop being sad.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:41.86,0:04:46.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,When I get sad,I stop being sad and be awesome instead.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:46.41,0:04:47.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,True story.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:48.44,0:04:50.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,It's only been a month.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:50.16,0:04:51.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,He just needs to go at his own pace.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:51.67,0:04:53.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Anyway,lily's the one who caused this whole mess.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:53.95,0:04:56.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Hey,cut her some slack.She's our friend,too.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:56.36,0:04:58.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,She's just trying to figure out who she is.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:58.34,0:04:59.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Figure out who she is?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:04:59.61,0:05:01.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Yeah,she should call me; I got a whole list.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:01.56,0:05:02.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,She's selfish.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:02.60,0:05:03.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,She's immature.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:03.61,0:05:05.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,She'S...
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:05.39,0:05:06.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,What?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:06.52,0:05:09.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,God,your eyes are so blue.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:09.69,0:05:11.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Aw,teddy bear.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:15.15,0:05:17.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,oh that's A...
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:24.86,0:05:26.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,yeah,it was hard to feel too bad.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:26.81,0:05:30.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I was dating the woman of my dreams,and things were going great.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:30.48,0:05:31.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Well,for the most part.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:31.73,0:05:33.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,So,I found her shampoo.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:33.96,0:05:35.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I guess she left it here.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:35.75,0:05:37.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,It smells like her.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:39.46,0:05:44.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Like lavender and seashells and hope.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:45.55,0:05:51.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Somehow,erotic and comforting all at the same time.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:51.55,0:05:53.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,That's my shampoo.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:53.85,0:05:55.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Oh,sorry.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:05:56.23,0:05:58.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Mmm,I thought he'd never go to sleep.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:01.22,0:06:02.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Already?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:04.09,0:06:05.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,He's calling her.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:05.85,0:06:08.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I don't hear any-- he's calling her.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:08.72,0:06:09.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,No.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:10.70,0:06:13.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Okay,you're right,I won't call her.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:13.88,0:06:16.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I will not call her.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:16.35,0:06:18.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Well,I called her.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:18.59,0:06:21.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,And get this,she changed her number.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:21.84,0:06:23.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,What,like I'm going to stalk her,or something?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:23.85,0:06:25.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Like she's so special.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:25.75,0:06:27.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Like she's the only lily aldrin out there.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:27.89,0:06:30.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,'Cause there are four others in the san francisco area alone,
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:30.72,0:06:35.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,and they all seem a lot better than her based on the brief conversations I had with them.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:35.65,0:06:37.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Does he know I'm in here?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:37.10,0:06:38.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Yeah,hey,robin.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:38.58,0:06:40.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Anyways,one of the lily aldrins said...
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:40.17,0:06:41.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,this has to stop.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:41.68,0:06:43.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Ted,we just started dating.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:43.36,0:06:47.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,We agreed we don't want to move too fast,and yet somehow,we have a baby.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:47.34,0:06:48.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,He can't feed himself.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:48.87,0:06:51.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,He cries a lot,he keeps us up all night.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:51.04,0:06:52.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Have you tried breast-feeding?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:52.72,0:06:54.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Nailed it!
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:54.94,0:06:56.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Look,they were together nine years.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:56.74,0:06:58.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,It's only been a month and a half.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:06:58.54,0:07:00.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,He just needs to go at his own pace.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:07:00.35,0:07:02.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,He slept on our floor last night,ted.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:07:02.75,0:07:04.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,He watched a scary movie.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:07:04.50,0:07:06.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,It is time for some tough love.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:07:06.79,0:07:08.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,We need to get him out of that apartment.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:07:08.66,0:07:09.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,He needs fresh air.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:07:09.96,0:07:11.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,He needs sunshine.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:07:11.23,0:07:13.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Mmm,sunshine.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:07:14.02,0:07:18.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Gentlemen,please welcome to the stage,sunshine.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:07:22.14,0:07:24.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,All right,I really don't think this is going to help.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:07:25.03,0:07:27.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Do you know why you're not over lily yet?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:07:27.22,0:07:29.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,It's 'cause you can still picture her naked.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:07:29.35,0:07:33.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You can't get over a woman until you can no longer picture her boobs; it's a scientific fact.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:07:33.90,0:07:40.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,The average male brain can only store a finite number of boob images or "b-pegs".
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:07:40.50,0:07:44.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,And your hard drive's filled to capacity with lily'S.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:07:44.68,0:07:46.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,There are a lot of them.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:07:46.26,0:07:50.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Well,they won't go away until you overwrite them with images of other women's boobs.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:07:50.30,0:07:56.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Now,this journey may take as many as a million boobs,so we begin here tonight,my friend.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:07:56.71,0:07:58.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Two at a time.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:07:58.49,0:08:00.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Those count as four.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:08:05.48,0:08:06.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,This is fun right?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:08:06.72,0:08:08.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,We're outside,it's a beautiful day.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:08:08.87,0:08:11.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,The indians are winning.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:08:11.39,0:08:13.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I got to admit,it is really nice to be outside.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:08:13.83,0:08:19.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Yankee fans,please turn your attention to the diamond vision for a special seventh-inning-stretch surprise.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:08:19.19,0:08:20.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Oh,no.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:08:28.49,0:08:30.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,it's all a big lie!
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:08:30.67,0:08:33.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,She's just going to break your heart.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:08:35.29,0:08:38.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,you can drag me out of here,but she has no soul!
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:08:38.22,0:08:40.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,We've tried everything-- baseball,strippers.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:08:40.96,0:08:43.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,The guy still won't eat a damn pancake.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:08:43.03,0:08:44.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I think he's beyond repair.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:08:44.64,0:08:46.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,See,this is the problem with guys.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:08:46.48,0:08:48.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You don't know how to deal with heartbreak.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:08:48.21,0:08:50.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Oh,and what's your prescription,dr.Estrogen?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:08:50.91,0:08:55.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Eat haagen-dazs and watch love actually,till your periods sync uP.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:09:00.81,0:09:03.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,yeah,that's the stuff.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:09:03.24,0:09:04.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Oh,my god.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:09:04.58,0:09:06.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,How long have you been doing this?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:09:06.25,0:09:08.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Well,my dad taught me to me shoot when I was a kid.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:09:08.42,0:09:13.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Whenever I'm feeling lonely or depressed,I come here,and it reminds me that...
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:09:13.12,0:09:14.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,guns are fun.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:09:18.49,0:09:21.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,um,you know,ted is kind of against guns.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:09:21.91,0:09:25.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,And that's why ted's never going to find out about this.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:09:25.07,0:09:28.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Whoa,that sounded kind of scary with me holding a gun,didn't it?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:09:28.56,0:09:31.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,No,I-I just mean,please don't tell ted.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:09:31.36,0:09:33.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You want to try?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:09:33.33,0:09:35.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Only hell yeah.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:09:35.69,0:09:38.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Oh,yeah,yeah,this is what I needed.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:09:38.69,0:09:42.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I felt so powerless this whole time,but this...
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:09:42.87,0:09:44.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,this is power.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:09:44.39,0:09:45.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,This is...
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:09:48.02,0:09:50.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I should of mentioned the recoil.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:09:50.40,0:09:54.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I got to hand it to you,when he got home,marshall was smiling-- did you sleep with him?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:09:54.69,0:09:57.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,'Cause I was actually,like,three days away from suggesting that.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:09:57.61,0:10:00.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Sometimes,all you need is to get in touch with your feminine side.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:10:03.77,0:10:05.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,yeah,yeah!
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:10:05.70,0:10:06.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Well,congratulations.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:10:06.98,0:10:09.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You're the first person to cheer him up all summer.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:10:09.17,0:10:10.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You win.\NOh,what do I win?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:10:10.93,0:10:13.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I'll tell you what you win: I'm taking you away this weekend.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:10:13.16,0:10:14.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You are?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:10:14.24,0:10:15.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,That's so nice.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:10:15.06,0:10:18.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Yeah,my aunt and uncle have a beach house out in montauk,oh,it's really romantic.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:10:18.72,0:10:20.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,My uncle's had like three affairs there.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:10:20.98,0:10:25.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Wow,must be a nice house,I've seen pictures of your uncle.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:10:25.80,0:10:27.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,This is going to be so great.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:10:27.18,0:10:28.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,We'll finally get some time alone.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:10:29.54,0:10:31.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Are you sure marshall's going to be okay with this?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:10:31.46,0:10:33.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Yeah,absolutely.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:10:33.07,0:10:34.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Dude,I'm doing much better.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:10:34.90,0:10:36.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,In fact,take my car.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:10:36.57,0:10:37.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Really?\NYeah.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:10:37.55,0:10:38.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Hey,thanks...
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:10:38.51,0:10:44.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,and,hey,if you need anything day or night,just call me-- you know what,please don't call me.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:10:44.58,0:10:45.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,What?What's wrong?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:10:46.35,0:10:48.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,It's,uh,lily's credit card bill.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:10:48.71,0:10:50.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,She must have forgotten to switch her address.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:10:50.67,0:10:52.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,So?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:10:52.19,0:10:54.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,So,I wonder what kind of charges she's making out there in san francisco.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:10:54.96,0:10:57.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,No.No,no good can come from looking at this.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:10:57.28,0:10:58.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You've made too much progress already.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:10:58.54,0:11:01.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I know but I just,maybe the-- no!
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:11:01.54,0:11:03.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You're going to thank me for this.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:11:06.24,0:11:08.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You're a good friend,ted.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:11:09.60,0:11:12.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,August 5th,one charge-- tickets.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:11:12.20,0:11:13.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,To what?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:11:13.09,0:11:16.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,George clinton and the p-funk all-stars.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:11:16.30,0:11:19.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,August 10th,one charge: Tennis emporium.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:11:19.44,0:11:27.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,August 18th,two charges: Mario's bistro and,get this,pet palace.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:11:28.05,0:11:30.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You guys see what this means,right?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:11:32.25,0:11:34.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Wow,mario's bistro.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:11:34.82,0:11:37.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,What a perfect place to whore around.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:11:37.91,0:11:40.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Only the best for my little lily pad.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:11:41.10,0:11:43.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Oh,funk legend george clinton,
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:11:43.09,0:11:49.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I am so glad you spotted me at your concert and dragged me onstage to dance with you courtney cox-style.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:11:49.53,0:11:52.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,And I'm so glad you agreed to play tennis with me.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:11:53.36,0:11:56.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You know,marshall tried to get me to play tennis for nine years,
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:11:56.69,0:12:00.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,but I didn't do it,because I never truly loved him.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:01.39,0:12:03.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I got you a gift.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:05.18,0:12:07.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,A ferret.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:07.43,0:12:11.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Oh,I'll buy it some food next door at the pet palace.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:11.13,0:12:16.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Oh,I've always wanted one,but marshall had this secret phobia of ferrets.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:16.06,0:12:19.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I bet that's something he made you promise not to tell nobody.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:19.28,0:12:21.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,It was.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:22.45,0:12:25.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I love you,funk legend george clinton.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:25.46,0:12:27.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I love you,too,lily.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:27.42,0:12:29.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,That's right,marshall,she's all mine.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:30.14,0:12:32.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Now I'm gonna let her play with my hair.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:35.56,0:12:37.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,that's the craziest thing I've ever heard.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:37.37,0:12:39.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Yeah,why are you afraid of ferrets?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:39.04,0:12:39.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,They're adorable.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:39.92,0:12:43.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Because,robin,they're like fuzzy,tube-shaped rats.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:43.91,0:12:45.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Plus,those charges are from,like,a month ago.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:45.83,0:12:46.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Exactly.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:46.50,0:12:48.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,For new charges,you have to go to her online account.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:48.72,0:12:52.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You can see credit card activity from,like,two hours ago.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:53.95,0:12:56.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,But,you know,don'T.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:58.52,0:12:59.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Why do you talk?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:12:59.63,0:13:01.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Why do you talk?!
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:01.81,0:13:04.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,He needs her password.It's not like he has her password.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:04.18,0:13:06.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Ooh,this is good,he has her password.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:06.41,0:13:11.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,There's a charge from earlier today: The kellett hotel on 5th.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:11.76,0:13:12.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I don't believe this.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:12.82,0:13:15.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Lily's back in new york.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:17.45,0:13:19.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I can't believe this.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:19.20,0:13:21.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Lily's in new york?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:21.18,0:13:24.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I-I guess I've been thinking when she got back,she'd call me.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:24.79,0:13:28.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,That's really the only reason I've been able to hold it together so far this summer.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:28.05,0:13:30.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,This has been "holding it together"?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:31.00,0:13:32.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Okay,you know what?I'm calling her.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:32.44,0:13:33.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,No.\NTed,give me the phone.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:33.66,0:13:34.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You're not calling her,this changes nothing.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:34.99,0:13:36.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You,come here.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:37.85,0:13:41.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Look,while we're away this weekend,can you keep an eye on him,make sure he doesn't call that hotel?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:41.70,0:13:43.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You want me to babysit him?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:43.45,0:13:44.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,20 bucks.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:44.79,0:13:45.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,An hour.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:45.68,0:13:46.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,And money for pizza.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:46.90,0:13:50.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Uh,yeah,how about you do it for free or every time we hang out,you have to watch this?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:50.65,0:13:51.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Come here.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:51.57,0:13:55.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,My little blue-eyed baby,baby lips.\NOoh,ooh,sugar,sugar...
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:55.51,0:13:58.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,okay,I'll do it!Stop being a couple.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:58.79,0:13:59.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Marshall.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:13:59.54,0:14:00.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Marshall,marshall!
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:00.71,0:14:02.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Ted,I know I shouldn't do this,but I have to!
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:02.66,0:14:03.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You call her we were together for nine years!
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:03.93,0:14:05.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,And everything we've been working so hard for is completely flushed down the toi...
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:05.89,0:14:08.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,hello,lily aldrin's room,please.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:08.91,0:14:10.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Thank you.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:10.45,0:14:11.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Hang up now.\NTed,I can't hang up now.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:11.91,0:14:14.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,The missiles are in the air,and I know that you don't approve.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:14.08,0:14:15.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Hello.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:21.11,0:14:23.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Uh,a guy answered.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:23.18,0:14:25.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,There's-there's a guy in her room.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:27.45,0:14:28.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I'm going down there.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:28.41,0:14:29.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Barney: Dude,you can't do that.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:29.21,0:14:31.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Have to go down there,and I have to tell her I love her;
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:31.43,0:14:34.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I have to beg her to take me back,even if I have to get down on my knees.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:34.15,0:14:35.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Marshall,you can't do that.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:35.46,0:14:36.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Oh,really,why not?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:36.59,0:14:37.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Ted: 56 days.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:37.98,0:14:40.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,That's how long it took me to get right about here.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:40.62,0:14:43.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Because you're pathetic!
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:44.88,0:14:47.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I'm sorry,but right now,you are not marshall.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:47.78,0:14:52.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You are the miserable,whining,shampoo-sniffing ghost of marshall,
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:52.50,0:14:56.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,and frankly,a guy like you doesn't have a shot in hell with a girl like lily.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:56.15,0:14:59.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You know who might have a shot somewhere down the line?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:14:59.12,0:15:00.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Marshall.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:15:00.08,0:15:01.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,The real marshall.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:15:01.79,0:15:06.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,But if you go down there right now like this,you're going to blow it for him,and he's never going to forgive you.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:15:07.30,0:15:10.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Of course,whatever I say,you're just going to do the opposite,so have a great weekend.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:15:10.65,0:15:12.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Good luck screwing up your life.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:15:12.27,0:15:13.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Come on,robin.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:15:17.94,0:15:20.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,is it still okay if we borrow the car?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:15:21.71,0:15:22.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Bold.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:15:22.56,0:15:24.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Bold to go for the car.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:15:27.83,0:15:29.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,What?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:15:29.05,0:15:31.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I didn't say a thing.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:15:31.38,0:15:33.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You think I was too hard on him.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:15:33.17,0:15:34.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I didn't say a thing.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:15:34.72,0:15:37.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I can't believe you're accusing me of being too hard on him.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:15:37.06,0:15:38.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You're the one who said "tough love.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:15:38.40,0:15:40.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect," Yeah,tough love,not "hand the guy a noose.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:15:41.00,0:15:43.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect," Oh,but it's okay to hand him a nine millimeter?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:15:43.78,0:15:47.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Yeah,he told me.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:15:48.84,0:15:50.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,So you're a gun nut?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:15:50.38,0:15:52.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,No,I'm a gun enthusiast.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:15:52.37,0:15:55.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Do you know how many people are killed each year the second amendment protects my right to bear arms...
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:15:55.37,0:15:57.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,all right,all right,all right.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:15:57.52,0:15:59.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I was too hard on him.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:00.26,0:16:02.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,A little.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:04.30,0:16:06.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I'm going to call barney,see how they're doing.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:07.33,0:16:08.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,go for barney.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:08.45,0:16:09.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Oh,hey,where are you guys?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:09.64,0:16:13.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,We're at a fundraiser,helping young women raise money for community college.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:13.43,0:16:14.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Strip club,nice.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:14.76,0:16:16.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Is marshall okay?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:16.23,0:16:17.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,yeah,he's here and he's great.Uh,hang on.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:17.73,0:16:19.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Marshall?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:19.81,0:16:20.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Tell ted that--
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:22.35,0:16:24.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Already?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:24.63,0:16:25.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,What?What uh-oh?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:25.90,0:16:27.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,He's gone.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:27.46,0:16:28.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You lost him?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:28.46,0:16:30.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I can't believe this.He's going to go down to that hotel.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:30.55,0:16:31.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Crap,you're right.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:31.27,0:16:32.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Okay,okay,here's the plan,here's the plan.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:32.92,0:16:34.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You go down to the hotel and find him.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:34.92,0:16:36.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I'll stay here and get a lap dance.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:36.12,0:16:38.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,On three.One,two...\Nbarney!
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:43.59,0:16:46.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Was there a hot tub at your uncle's place?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:46.67,0:16:49.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,A really nice one.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:51.87,0:16:54.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Hi,uh,could you tell me what room lily aldrin's in?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:16:56.26,0:16:57.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Marshall.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:00.63,0:17:02.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,What happened?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:02.12,0:17:07.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Well,I went up to lily's floor,and I had this little speech in my head--
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:07.62,0:17:12.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,everything I've been wanting to say to her all summer about love,loyalty,respect.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:12.70,0:17:14.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I knocked on the door.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:20.36,0:17:22.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,So you knocked out lily's new boyfriend?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:22.71,0:17:23.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Yeah.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:23.90,0:17:25.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,It wasn't lily's boyfriend.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:25.54,0:17:27.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,What?\NWho-- who was it?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:27.17,0:17:32.87,UP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Ted: His name was joey adalian,although he went by a number of aliases in his years as an identity thief.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:32.90,0:17:35.16,UP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Apparently,earlier in the summer...
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:35.21,0:17:38.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,lily: Oh,this is so embarrassing.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:38.47,0:17:41.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I-I could have sworn I had some change.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:41.78,0:17:44.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I know,I know.I'm sorry.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:44.32,0:17:46.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Oh,here we go.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:46.54,0:17:48.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,No,that's-that's a button.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:48.61,0:17:50.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,It was a button.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:52.78,0:17:54.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Do you,uh,take credit cards?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:54.90,0:17:56.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Yes,I do.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:17:56.68,0:18:00.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,So lily's not back in town,and she doesn't have a boyfriend?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:18:00.28,0:18:01.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Th-that's good news,right?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:18:01.46,0:18:02.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Yeah.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:18:03.52,0:18:05.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I don't know.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:18:05.61,0:18:09.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Those credit card charges were the only remaining connection I had to her.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:18:10.61,0:18:14.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I don't know where she is or what she's doing.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:18:14.53,0:18:18.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,She was my whole life,man,and now she's-she's gone.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:18:22.52,0:18:26.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You know,first day of college,I showed up,I was so freaked out,and-
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:18:26.91,0:18:34.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,and I got up to my room,and there was my roommate,lying on the bed with his feet up on the wall.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:18:34.12,0:18:39.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Had headphones on,big smile on his face like he just didn't give a crap.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:18:39.24,0:18:40.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Happy.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:18:40.39,0:18:41.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Confident.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:18:41.51,0:18:43.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Not afraid of anything.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:18:43.89,0:18:45.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,That guy was you.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:18:45.98,0:18:48.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You before you met lily.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:18:50.22,0:18:51.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Ted?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:18:51.42,0:18:53.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Yeah?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:18:53.26,0:18:55.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I was high that day.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:18:55.29,0:18:55.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I was.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:18:55.84,0:18:59.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,I was so high,I thought you were the dean.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:19:00.16,0:19:08.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Wh-what I'm saying is there's a version of you without lily,and it's not this.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:19:08.68,0:19:14.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,You can't let lily steal your identity the way that guy stole hers.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:19:15.44,0:19:16.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Okay.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:19:17.63,0:19:20.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Okay,resolved.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:19:20.14,0:19:24.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Starting tomorrow,I'm going to start being okay.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:19:24.22,0:19:25.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Cheers.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:19:32.76,0:19:36.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,But he wasn't,'cause that's not how life works.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:19:36.81,0:19:41.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,The next day,he found one of her socks or something,and we were back to square one.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:19:43.66,0:19:45.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,And then,one morning...
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:19:45.50,0:19:48.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,ted,I think you should see this.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:19:48.83,0:19:50.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Oh,no,what now?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:19:52.04,0:19:54.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Marshall,what are you doing?
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:19:55.10,0:19:56.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,It's sunday.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:19:56.91,0:19:59.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,It's pancakes day.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:20:03.48,0:20:08.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,It took him 67 days and one really disgusting batch of pancakes...
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:20:12.81,0:20:14.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,so good.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:20:14.63,0:20:16.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,So good.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:20:16.55,0:20:19.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,But marshall had come back from the dead.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:20:19.22,0:20:22.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,Because while baseball,strippers,and guns can help,
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:20:22.27,0:20:26.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,the only thing that can really heal a broken heart is time.
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:20:26.81,0:20:37.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,sync:fisherchen\Nwww.YDY.com
Dialogue: Marked=0,0:20:41.94,0:20:48.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,www.YDY.com\NProudly Presents
