What's the matter?
- I'm scared.
- Don't be. Everything's gonna be fine.
Come on, come on.
I'm almost done.
OK.
At first I just thought they'd go away,
but they never did.
They just kept growing and growing.
- I see you've had symptoms.
- Mainly indigestion, which I've always had.
Even as a child, I had a nervous stomach.
But there's also been vomiting and blood
in your stool? Why didn't you call me?
I knew we should.
Somehow I just kept putting it off.
We were supposed to go to Florida
next week to visit our son.
We haven't seen him in a year.
We were gonna call you as soon as
we got back but the pain got too bad.
I wish you had called me as soon...
Well, we'll just start doing some tests
and hope for the best.
What would be the worst?
That these are two tumours
which may have metastasised and spread.
What are the chances that's the case?
Let's just do the tests and hope for the best.
Claire?
Morning.
It's not very good.
I think Mom's machine's a little more low-tech.
Sometimes I miss the days
when coffee was just coffee.
I have a huge darkroom day today.
Hopefully, I'll be back in time for dinner.
Don't stay here any more. It's too much.
- No, it isn't.
- It is.
I was bad before
but now I'm starting to sleep.
I haven't had a panic attack in two days.
I've even cut down on all the Ativan
so you are officially evicted as of today.
David, are you sure? You seem...
- Jeez, this coffee really is gross.
- I don't know. I think maybe I should stay.
I don't need my baby sister
baby-sitting me any more, OK?
Hear those two cats
having sex in the alley last night?
They were worse than Mom and George.
- Why do they do it? It sounds so painful.
- I mean, they live in an alley.
They deserve some kind of diversion,
don't you think?
- Did you hear what I said?
- Yes. You can't see me any more.
It's over. Goodbye.
Goodbye, Rico. Get outta here.
I am so stupid. I hid that pack of cigarettes
from myself so good I can't find them.
Did you look on top of the refrigerator?
I just want to say that I'm sorry,
but I just feel like this isn't right in some way
to my wife and to my kids...
Oh, yeah? And why is that?
This is not about fucking.
You made that plain and clear.
This is about just being friends.
I think I need more guy friends.
You tell me today when my lupus is acting up.
I gave you that money and I never heard
a word about you going to a doctor.
- Did you go to one...
- I got the damn lupus!
You never even liked me.
This was about
you needing to feel like a big man
and now that you got what you need,
you're done?
OK, just leave the gift that you promised Nicole
- and get out of here.
- Shit.
You didn't bring the "Jack The Pig" book
you've been going on about?
- I left it at work. I could bring it by tomorrow.
- Forget it.
She needs to learn -
people promise you things...
but then leave when they get tired of you.
She's George's new wife,
the one who came after you.
Jesus, lady, what the hell are you doing?
George'll kill you if you mess with his things.
You're snooping. You're too snoopy.
I was too snoopy and he got rid of me quick.
- You are some dumb cluck.
- Wanna know why George doesn't like
to be asked anything about his past?
Yes, I do. Tell me. Please, tell me.
What doesn't he want me to know?
Why can't I know anything?
All of these caskets are available
with customised inserts.
You can have your wife's name,
her favourite Bible verse, a family photo.
Is there one that appeals to you?
I don't know, son.
- You seemed to like the blue one.
- There's a lot of options.
I think that maybe you need
to take a little time to look.
I'll give you two a moment to decide.
You were meant to be here 40 minutes ago.
Maya's not used to daycare.
- I had to stay with her.
- No-one was here to meet the Morrisons.
- Well, where were you?
- That's not the point.
You were gonna talk about arrangements
with Mom. What did she want?
I tried to bring it up with her.
It always seemed like a bad time.
Fine. Then...
what do you want?
Pick the casket, then we'll talk about
who's gonna speak at this thing.
Dad, I need to know what you want here.
I want her back.
- I want things back the way they used to be.
- Yeah, well, it's too late now.
If you guys had faced the truth,
Mom would be alive
and we wouldn't have to fucking decide
about what casket she's gonna be buried in.
Apparently, the father never said a word to
anyone as the tumours kept getting bigger.
Man, I don't understand people.
I get it. Having to admit fucked-up shit
about yourself fucking sucks.
Come on!
- David's been cleaning again.
- So what? It relaxes him.
It's annoying. I could've used him
upstairs with the Morrisons.
I'm doing intakes. David's staying down here.
I know that David doesn't want
to be around people right now,
but if you've come back to the business,
then be back.
The two of you are acting like
you can do whatever the hell you want.
Why are we buying fake Windex
when only the real kind works?
I'll get some real Windex later.
Since there's nothing going on here,
would you mind swinging by the hospital
to pick up Mrs Morrison?
- I'm cleaning.
- That's fine. We'll figure something out.
Didn't I just have a rag? I must have left it
out there. I don't know where my mind is.
David can't take the van out.
The van is where it happened.
- That's fine. Then you go.
- Actually, Maya and I have to go to the...
- Maya's in daycare.
- That's right.
And there's this get-together once a month
where we get together
with the other parents.
Fine. I'll go.
Great. So long as you're out,
can you get the real Windex?
Anita?
- Hey.
- Oh, hey.
Anita went over to Russell's so I just
decided to hang out and wait for you.
What are you hiding?
Nothing. It's one of my photos.
It's one of the ones I took of you.
OK, so it's bad.
It's not. It's really good.
Then why can't I see it?
It's too good. It's like I can't believe
this actually came out of me.
It's so good, I don't want anyone to see it.
I'm not even gonna show it
at my crit tomorrow because...
I don't know... It's just for me.
- Is that crazy?
- Not at all.
- It's so beautiful.
- I know.
I love this shadow that
goes across your face. It's so cool.
You've got to show this at your crit.
What are you so scared of?
Look at my expression.
Nice to know that finally my hours of watching
"America's Next Top Model" have paid off.
- I definitely owe you one for this.
- I'll think about how I can collect on that.
- Are you available next Tuesday?
- Nate, I told you this is the last time.
You said that last week
and the week before.
No, this is the last last time.
All right, fine.
We'll never talk again...
until you call me tomorrow.
Oh, God. I don't know why I'm doing this.
It's all Joe's fault. If only he enjoyed
nice, normal, perfectly average sex.
Wasn't I a little above average back there,
at least for a few seconds?
As opposed to what I told you
about me and Joe.
- The "Hurt me, Mommy" stuff?
- Stop.
Give me a break, Bren.
- Excuse me?
- This isn't about Joe, it's about you.
- I of all people should know.
- What is that supposed to mean?
You and Joe move in together.
You get scared by the intimacy.
You have sex outside the relationship.
You can't fool me. I used to be Joe.
Well, this is all very illuminating.
What about you? Why are you doing this?
Why not? I'm at a place in my life
where I want to have some fun.
Of course.
This couldn't be just another way for you
to avoid having a permanent relationship.
- What are you looking for?
- The condom.
I dropped it on the floor
when I took it off and I can't find...
Here it is.
Sperm is...
I don't know.
- It seems so tiny to be able to do so much.
- I know.
It's odd.
I'm going to be gone all day tomorrow.
OK.
I'm going to hunt for fossils in Cold Canyon
like I do every year.
That's nice. I know how much
your annual fossil hunt means to you.
You could come with me,
if you wouldn't find it too boring.
I don't know.
I have to return some books to the library.
You don't have to invite me.
I'm happy for you to do whatever you want
whenever you want
with whomever you want.
OK.
But I want to go fossil hunting
so I will go fossil hunting, darn it.
OK, now I'm starting to freak out!
- We'll find it.
- It's my favourite earring.
I know. You keep saying that.
When Javier gets here,
we'll figure something out.
Nothing yet, but I've got
five of Detroit's finest looking for it.
If it's in this auditorium, they'll find it.
It was given to me by the only person
who ever really loved me. Now it's lost.
Oh, God, when will someone
ever love me again?
The real me?
Everyone else has someone.
Here is the entire universe and here is me.
You're exhausted. You need to go back
to your room and get some sleep.
Please don't minimise my depression.
I would never do that to you.
Only one thing will make me feel better.
Just give me a few moments
and we'll blow out of here.
- Well, we're fucked.
- What do you mean?
Halfway through the tour,
she always gets depressed.
We go to whatever stupid gay club we can
find so she can get worshipped by the fags.
- We're going to a gay club?
- Yeah, dude.
Try to act a little cooler about it.
- Midwestern queers really creep me out.
- I know what you mean.
- Keith Charles.
- Are you still working?
Yeah. Late night.
I'm sorry, I just couldn't sleep and I...
It sounds like you're in a bar.
I am. I'm with Celeste.
She's fighting a severe depression.
- That's a gay bar.
- Dude, Celeste is looking over here.
- She's annoyed you ain't looking at her.
- Listen, I gotta go.
- I'll call you in the morning.
- Sorry to bother you.
If anybody gets mad,
tell them your wife's on her woman's time.
They'll feel bad for you that I'm such a bitch
when I'm on the rag. Night.
Your old lady pissed off? You could've
just told her you was at some fag bar.
There was no chance
of you taking home some pussy tonight.
Javier, I'm gay.
I have a boyfriend. I sleep with men, OK?
I have a lot of sex and it's really, really gay.
That's cool, man.
Well, that site back there was completely
picked over. I'll bet I know who did it, too.
Last year I caught this guy from USC
following me...
- George, I think I'm dehydrating.
- Nonsense.
- I'm about to dehydrate.
- Why did you drink all your water so fast?
I was thirsty.
Here, just have some of mine.
I asked you if you had water.
You said you didn't.
Because I thought, if you knew,
you wouldn't make your water last as long.
Let's talk about lunch.
I always go to the Inn of the Seventh Ray.
I'm going to visit my sister.
I didn't know we were gonna be in Topanga.
She lives a few miles from here
and I haven't seen her in ages.
Family is very important to me
even if it isn't to you.
Mom is hunting for fossils?
Why would a person hunt for fossils?
Because their husband does.
This is great. I was gonna ask her
to baby-sit for me tonight.
I'm busy.
- You're out a lot lately. Is this serious?
- No, of course not.
Maile's a girl I worked with at doggie daycare.
I've seen her a few times,
but she's just...just fun.
It's really weird you worked at a dog place
for, like, six seconds.
Well, it wasn't exactly my decision to leave,
was it?
People who write Op-Ed pieces
should be shot.
Hey, what time's the movie tonight?
Actually, I'm seeing Russell tonight
and I plan on staying over at his apartment.
It's purely a physical thing, but...
it's something very intense
I need to explore.
If you're having any emotions about it,
now is a good time to express them.
No, it isn't.
Look, do whatever you want.
So it'll just be me and Edie tonight.
I'm fine.
I've just been working on Mrs Morrison
for 110 years.
The tumour lady.
Her body's totally shot from the chemo
and the radiation. She's all crumbly.
Edie and I are going to the movies. Join us.
Girls night out? I'm there, totally.
I'm a lonely little Petunia in an onion patch
an onion patch, an onion patch
and all I do is cry all day
- What the hell was that?
- My mother used to sing that to us.
Well, that explains a lot.
Why, when you move,
can you never find the things you want?
You just find things you regret bringing
and not throwing away.
- I never hold onto anything.
- Smart.
You should be proud of that.
I'm thinking of building shelves
in the other bedroom.
That's not one of those things
you need to know how to do
in order to be able to do it.
Let's finish settling in later
and watch bad TV.
OK, but we're gonna have to make
a decision at some point.
The office won't always be an office.
It's gonna be a nursery as soon as...
- You might already be pregnant.
- Oh, I'm not. I got it yesterday.
That's why you looked so sad
when you came home late after class.
Why didn't you tell me?
I don't know.
Well, look, it was only
our first time up at bat.
I'm sure this month it'll happen.
- Maybe it's for the best.
- Yeah, exactly.
We get another month of just the two of us.
We have to learn to appreciate those.
Yeah.
Well, it's definitely an improvement.
Yet there's still something unsatisfying
about these.
Does anyone know what it is?
They're technically good.
It's just that they're...
- finite.
- Elise, that is a beautiful way to put it.
They show us something, but they
don't leave us with anything to ponder.
All except...this one.
Claire, what do you think
this photograph is saying?
It's about being half-hidden,
what it means to come out of the shadows.
The woman in the photograph looks at us
like she wants us to come closer.
But we don't. She teases us,
almost like she's daring us.
But what is the dare? Ls it to touch her?
She looks like she knows we're scared.
But what's so scary
about this beautiful woman?
What's so scary about
getting close to someone?
Because we don't quite know the answer
to any of these questions,
the photo haunts us.
Nice work, Claire.
Does anyone else have any comments?
- Yeah. I'm really pissed off.
- Why is that?
Claire takes an erotic picture
of her girlfriend
and she gets an A
just because you're a lesbian. This sucks.
- She's not my girlfriend.
- Give me a break.
- Anita, tell her she's just my friend.
- She's not Claire's girlfriend.
That I know of.
Why isn't she answering?
I don't think there's anyone here.
I suppose you're right.
- Oh, my God.
- Sarah!
Honey?
Oh, for God's sake, Fisher!
I tell the children
to make the ugliest monster
and then we put their pictures on them.
They are sort of ugly.
- This one is really hideous.
- That's mine!
It's wonderful that you've become a teacher.
I'm just the crazy art lady
who comes in a few afternoons a week.
I don't have any actual certification
so the pay is pretty terrible.
Yes, but the last time I saw you...
I'm glad you've put your life together.
Wow, I had no idea.
George has just told me the entire history
of papier-mâchê. It was fascinating.
- May I use your bathroom?
- Let me show you where it is.
So I left five fucking messages for you
after I came back into town.
- Why haven't you called me?
- I don't know.
- You look funny.
- I was dehydrated earlier.
Now that I have you back, I won't let you go.
You have to stay for dinner.
I have a million questions for you.
You must have a million for me.
I've been having this funny feeling lately
so this morning I decided to follow him.
Fucking bastard!
I told you he'd do this to you one day.
Maybe there's a logical explanation.
Maybe he...
- Oh, my God.
- What is it? What's going on?
Rico's charity has a double D.
I will cut his balls off!
I need you take the boys tonight.
I need the house to be empty
when I talk to him.
I'll be here for hours.
This shit show's been on forever
and none of the regulars give a fuck.
- I could come by tomorrow and get them.
- Fine.
Are you gonna be OK tonight?
Don't worry about me.
What if there is a handsome prince?
- She's really pretty.
- And he's a really good kisser.
She's gorgeous, but in a really subtle way.
- What do you think?
- I don't know what makes a girl pretty.
I don't look at girls that way.
From the producer
who brought you The Vanishing...
When you were little, you went on and on
about how beautiful Jennifer Aniston was.
I was parroting what the culture
was telling me to think. I was 11.
- Do you love me?
- Yes.
Then I have everything I need.
If you make a noise, I'll shoot...I'll shoot...
If you even breathe,
I'll shoot you in the spine.
I have to get out of here.
- What's going on?
- I forgot.
Something I have to do at work
with the tumour lady.
You give Claire a ride home, OK?
Do you have any idea what's it's like
to see your life fall apart?
I'm just nervous.
It's Maya's first night with the new sitter.
She seems like a nice girl.
I used to baby-sit when I was a kid.
I hope you hid all your private papers.
You used to snoop around
people's private things?
All the time.
You wouldn't believe the stuff I found.
- Why do ugly people have dirty photos?
- I don't know.
One time, this widow brought in
the grossest photo of her husband
to help with the embalming.
- He was... You want me to describe him?
- Please don't.
- So how is it being back at work?
- It's the same old same old.
I'm trying not to let it get me down.
Right now,
I'm concentrating on having fun.
Really? What kind of things
do you like to do?
I woke up and the bastard was gone.
Stole $5,000 from me
and some Tiffany lamps.
- But I'd always hated those, anyway.
- You must have been so depressed.
This one? Are you kidding?
We went to Taos that night
and stayed a week.
Had a blast.
Julia Roberts and her husband live there.
We chased them around town
like they were wild boars!
- How were you able to do that?
- The only way you can show everybody
is to have the time of your life.
George, let's hear all about you.
You seem interesting.
Yeah. Ruth tells me you had a son
sending you boxes of shit.
- Bettina!
- What?
Like my daughter hasn't done worse to me?
Come on, you want to compare war stories?
Actually, no, I don't.
Do you have a TV?
There's a documentary on PBS
I wouldn't mind watching a few minutes of.
Oh, sure.
There's one in the other room
under that mess in the corner.
Having a hard night?
No, I just...saw some bad coming attractions.
That's a new one. So what can I get for you?
- Vodka gimlet.
- Really?
Yeah, my father used to drink them
when he wanted something strong.
Vodka gimlet coming up.
- Let's kick the shit out of him.
- No, let's kill him.
We could just hide in his car.
You want this?
The kitchen made an extra order
by mistake.
- You don't eat that many fried foods.
- No, not so many.
And spend a little too much on clothes,
I notice too.
Maybe a bit.
And you shave well.
None of the other guys
shave as well as you.
Fuck! I'm gonna fucking kill Javier.
Why didn't you tell me you were gay, bitch?
Calm down, they're the ones who told me.
Javier's got one big blabbermouth.
I think it's because he's got a crush on you.
Come on, he's married.
Javier's straight, isn't he?
Neil, I met on match.com.
The teacher I met on Salon.
Are these internet sites safe?
Do they screen these men?
Course not, thank God.
If there was screening,
none of us would make it through!
I remember I really liked
"Looking for Mr Goodbar" when it came out.
So is he never coming in to dinner?
George gets very caught up sometimes.
He's a very focused person.
It's a show about the Elgin Marbles.
How caught up can he be?
Tell me about the one you're seeing now.
His name is Bernie,
he's a freelance editor and he has a cat.
He's nice.
- He's a loser.
- Stop that. He's someone to do things with.
If all you can say is that
he's someone to do things with,
that's worse than being alone.
Well, I like him, so shut up.
I suppose we should be getting home.
George drives slowly at night
and he doesn't like me to talk
so he can concentrate.
You could stay here. The bed's pretty bad
and the guest room has a strange smell...
- We'll take it.
- You can have some more wine, then.
Then, bam, the lady was dead
because she let the tumour get so big.
- You listening?
- Course I'm listening.
"Bam, the lady was dead
because she let the tumour get so big."
Can you imagine? Something horrible
just growing inside of you?
Something terrible
just eating away at your insides?
Yes, actually, I can.
Oh, my God, this is so dirty!
What with your roommates and Maya,
I just figured...
I'm sure they clean it once in a while.
No, I meant this.
This is so dirty.
- I'll take one more for the road.
- Sorry, buddy, we're closing.
Shit.
I can't do this.
What happened?
You were, like, in heat before.
I'm sorry, I can't. I can't.
God, why do I always pick the crazies?
She's in a better mood.
Yeah, no gay clubs tonight.
Someone called for you on the stage phone
when you was in the can.
"Higwood Jablome"?
- I don't know a Higwood Jablome.
- That doesn't sound right. Look at it again.
"Higwood Jablome." Don't know him.
No, that's not a G, that's a Y.
And that's an E, not an I.
Oh, Heywood.
I don't know a Heywood Jablome either.
That's not how he said... Let me see.
- J-A-B-I-O-M-E. Ja-blow-me.
- I don't know this person.
- Say his name right. Maybe you do.
- OK, OK. Heywood Jablome.
Heywood Jablome.
- What's so funny?
- Say it again.
- Heywood Jablome!
- Sure, I'll blow you, K.
She seems sweet.
You two would make a lovely couple.
Well, she's just somebody to have fun with.
We don't have that much of a connection.
Cos you won't let there be one.
Nate, make a connection with her.
Nah, she's not ready to settle down.
Now, you, you were ready to settle down.
I'll say.
But I think you two could get together
and have a beautiful life.
You can have the life with her
you didn't give me.
- I gave you everything I had, Lis.
- Right.
Here's my advice to you.
Stop with the cheap motels,
stop sleeping with the crazy ex.
Try to have a real relationship with this one.
What's stopping you?
- The pain.
- What's that supposed to mean?
I can't ever again go through the pain
of starting a life with someone
- only to have it taken away from me.
- Please.
- That hurt.
- Life is pain. Get used to it.
- All right, so I guess that's it.
- Here we are.
Claire, what's going on here?
I don't know.
I mean, I feel like maybe you're into me,
but you're just confused, right?
Because I could be into you
if I knew you were into me, you know?
So I'll need you to say it.
I can't say it.
OK, look, this is what I know.
It's, like, you really inspire me.
I want to be with you all the time.
I feel like you're this really special person
who makes me feel like I am more special.
- OK, that sounded really stupid.
- No, it didn't.
This... I'm sorry.
- Hi.
- Hey, soldier. Just checking in.
Bren, can we have an honest conversation?
Oh, fuck.
I'm sorry, one of us has to wake up here.
It isn't good for you. It's not good for me.
It's keeping us
from really having anything good.
You know what? We deserve to be happy.
From everything you say,
Joe seems like a good guy.
A little weird, but so are you.
Give him a chance.
Go be with him, really be with him.
Give yourself a chance to be happy.
- What if it's too late?
- It doesn't have to be.
Tell him the truth. What we've been doing.
See where that goes.
That didn't work so well
when I told you the truth.
Maybe he's more mature than I was then.
Hold on a sec.
- Why aren't you watching the funeral?
- These things run themselves.
Where's David?
Now he doesn't even clean?
He wasn't feeling well this morning.
I told him to stay at home.
I'm working. I should go.
- Good luck.
- OK. Bye.
George seems nice, Ruth.
He reminds me of someone.
- Nathaniel.
- You must be joking. They're so different.
George is so academic
and Nathaniel was so...Nathaniel.
That jovial nature masking something else.
- Oh, that.
- Intense privateness,
that need to withdraw.
Maybe it's true what they say.
We all pick the same person
over and over again.
There's something nice about that.
Hey, let's move it.
Get a move on or we're gonna be late.
OK, great.
We feed breakfast burritos to the homeless.
Breakfast burritos on top of everything else?
Oh, my goodness.
The teaching, the dating,
chasing Julia Roberts like a wild boar.
How do you do it?
Ruth...
maybe you want to be
getting out a little more.
It's so much harder to do things
when you're married.
I hear you.
It's not like I've been able to have
a long-term relationship
and not subsume myself. I wonder why.
Mom.
Maybe that's our legacy.
But maybe it doesn't have to be.
- Hey.
- What's going on?
- Nothing.
It's just this sad story about this man
whose wife left him
because he couldn't control his eating.
Nothing the therapist or anybody did
could get him to stop eating
so she left him
and he had a heart attack and died.
Is this your way of telling me
that I need to cut down on my snacks?
I've done something bad.
I think I've been...
really, really scared
about my feelings for you
and it's caused me to act out
in old and familiar patterns.
Say it.
I slept with someone...
a few times.
This is my problem
that I am obviously
continuing to struggle with.
It's not you.
What are you thinking?
I need to know what you're thinking.
I'm thinking...
I am so fucked.
I never liked anyone as much as you
and I'm never going to like anyone
as much again, so...
that's it, it's over
and this sucks.
It doesn't have to be over.
It could be like...a new beginning.
Do I know this person?
No.
So what do you think of it...
being, like, a beginning?
Not much.
- What do you think it all means?
- OK.
Heywood Jablome.
Heywood Jablome. This is a tough one.
The obvious answer
is that he wanted to blow me.
Sure.
Freud would say that on some level
he wanted to blow me
whether he knows it or not.
I don't recall Freud's position on the
"Heywood Jablome" phoney message.
How do I know if he's conscious of wanting
to blow me or not?
That is the question.
It is and it is an important one.
I don't know, I guess I could
make some sort of pass at him.
What do you think I should do?
Are you still there?
- I don't want to do this any more.
- What?
Us. This. Having sex with other people.
We said if one of us was uncomfortable,
we could stop doing it.
I want us to stop doing it.
I don't remember that rule.
What's going on?
Oh, Keith, why did this happen to me?
What did I do
to deserve to have this happen to me?
- Nothing.
- Oh, God.
Let it out. I'm here.
You're gonna be OK.
I'm here.
- Where are the kids?
- Rico, I know everything.
About this woman.
About how often you call her,
about what you bought her!
I've done nothing wrong.
- I know you're sleeping with this person.
- I'm not sleeping with her!
I told you, I'm just helping Sophia.
Oh, my God.
I don't want this to be happening.
- But nothing is happening, nothing...
- Bullshit!
Bullshit! Bullshit! I saw her!
I sat outside that house!
I saw her face when she opened
whatever the fuck it is you left for her!
She loves you!
She doesn't.
Oh, my God.
You gotta get the fuck out of here.
- No, no!
- Yes, get the fuck out of this house.
Please, Vanessa, just try to understand this.
I do understand this. I understand it
a whole lot better than you do.
Edie, what are you doing here?
Claire, I just... I couldn't be away from you.
I have to be with you. I really need you.
- You left your wallet in my car.
- Oh, my God, thank you.
I thought I lost it this morning.
You know, maybe on some unconscious level,
you left it because...
OK, fine, I give up.
Let's just sleep together.
Now?
In a sec. I need to brush my teeth.
Last night,
it seemed like this isn't what you want.
It isn't.
- Come on, get undressed. Let's go.
- I don't understand what's changed.
Hold on.
Nothing has changed.
Part of me thinks this is what I want
and part of me thinks it isn't, but...
what if the part of me who thinks it isn't
is just scared?
And, after all, I do owe you one.
All right, you're on.
- Go away.
- Just let me talk to you for a few minutes.
- Please just let me in.
- Why?
Please.
Oh, I fell down!
You know what?
Maybe you and me and Maile
will do something fun this Saturday.
What do you think of that? Oh, I fell down!
Huh? She has two dogs.
You love doggies, right? Hello!
Oh, man, I can't wait till you start talking.
What the hell are you doing?
Calling Maile. I'm doing what you said.
Trying to start a relationship.
With that girl? Are you crazy?
That'll never turn into anything serious.
- But you told me...
- I was desperate.
I am so scared
that you're gonna go back to Brenda
that I'll do or say anything to stop it.
If you have a relationship with Brenda,
I'll really be dead.
Brenda's just sleeping with me
because she really loves Joe.
- That's what she does.
- No, it's different this time.
You love her and she loves you
and you should be with her
before it's too late.
This is giving me a bad feeling.
If I were you, I'd check that out.
It might be a tumour.
English