- I'm sorry.
- No, it's my fault.
Nothing is anybody's fault.
Well, good night.
You're beautiful.
My God, David, is that you?
I'm sorry, can you
hold on just a second?
Hello?
- Yeah?
- It's Jennifer.
- Hi.
- My father's been killedl
My God, I'm so sorry.
How did it happen?
He was struck by lightning.
Do you think you can handle it?
Yeah, of course we'll take care of it.
- David, are you OK?
- No, that's just...
- You sound...
- Hold on, it's just...
It's my mouth guard,
so I don't grind my teeth when I sleep.
- What the fuck?
- Jennifer's father died.
I can't believe it.
I hope she's married.
That way I won't have to feel so guilty
for wasting two years of her life.
Every woman needs
to fall in love with a gay man.
It's a female rite of passage.
What about Claire and whatshisface?
Don't tell her I told you about that.
I'm serious.
Just like every gay man
needs a period where he tries to be straight.
I don't think that's a requirement now.
We were the last generation that did that.
What about Claire and whatshisface?
- So I'm back on Celeste duty today.
- Another talk show?
Some rehearsal for some charity tomorrow.
What should I wear?
Helmut Lang jeans,
a black T-shirt, the faded
Banana Republic one with the stretch,
and black lace-up boots.
David, this is a profession, OK?
There's an image to project.
And that image isn't
fucking Keith of Finland.
Are you not out on the job?
- No one's ever asked.
- You big whore.
What? I'm not only defined by being gay.
I'm defined by being a lot of things.
Being black, American...
Busted? You broke up with me
because I was not out!
Yeah, to your family.
I don't expect you to come out
to every person you meet.
Nor do I expect you to come out
to every client,
whether it's Celeste or Cameron Diaz
or lan fucking McKellen.
- But the people you work with...
- Calm down.
I'm not the enemy. I'm your lover.
Thanks, Barb, she's never been before.
Seriously, you've never
taken Maya to Legoland?
No.
She was too young for it
until, basically, now.
I used to love to play with
those blocks when I was a kid.
Didn't you? Does Maya love them?
Too young, small parts, choking?
Oh, dear, she's still that orally fixated.
Well, no wonder, she was still
breast-feeding when...
Yeah.
She keeps getting bigger every day.
Yeah, kids kinda do that.
You got me.
Thanks.
- Uncle Nate?
- Yeah?
Could you be sure
and give this to David?
Yeah, sure. OK.
- Tell him that it's from Michaela.
- Right.
OK, so we'll drop her off
on Sunday around six or so.
Listen, you guys, thanks so much for this.
If there's anything you ever need...
Well, yeah, we do need...
I guess, what, Hoyt?
100 bucks, maybe 120.
For, you know, Maya's share of the hotel,
the parking, and the restaurants...
- Stroller rental.
- Of course, yeah.
Look, could you just take her?
- Does Maya like to swim?
- Yeah, she loves it.
She loves it.
- Here you go.
- Say goodbye to Daddy, honey.
Bye, baby girl. I love you.
Have a good time.
Nate, are you doing OK?
Yeah, you know...
it comes and goes.
I can appreciate the attempt, but...
I think it looks like something
you'd see on a calendar,
like in some bargain bin somewhere,
- three months after the new year.
- Can you be a little more harsh?
No, it's obviously a stylish calendar,
in an upscale store...
OK, so this piece is no good. Let's move on.
I think the question is not
so much is this piece good?
I would rather we ask
is this piece successful?
Well, this is America,
successful equals good.
Successful in achieving its intention.
Anita, what was your intent with this piece?
I don't know.
I liked the way the light
was hitting her head.
Do we have to know
exactly what every piece means?
No, but surely it means something to you,
or you wouldn't have brought it in.
I can't believe this!
I thought Arthur was merely eccentric,
not seriously disturbed.
Kinda brings new meaning
to the term "dump truck," huh?
Stop marking it, Sammy!
Sloppy. You guys blow!
Hey, over there.
How many of those guys
you think she fucked?
Them faggots are too busy
fucking each other
- to ever work her in.
- Right?
Yo, K, what's up? You coming
on the road with us next month?
I'm still waiting to hear.
Johnny, you suck!
Jennifer, I'm so terribly sorry.
David, this is my fiancê Greg Sutton.
Hi, Greg. I'm glad to meet you.
- Yeah, me too.
- Shall we?
He'd been depressed for years,
ever since my mom divorced him.
- Well, you remember.
- Yes.
Will your mother be coming to the funeral?
No, she's...
in a nursing home.
- You're kidding. She's so young.
- Honey, I don't mean to rush you,
but I've gotta be back on the site
by noon at the latest.
So what's going on tour like?
All right, the thing about Celeste...
every concert's
packed with teenage girls
fucking horny out of their minds.
You know what I'm saying?
You better check IDs
or you'll find your ass in jail.
Nah, you just got to make sure
you don't videotape nothing.
What, you married?
No, not married, but we live together.
Don't do it.
I'm on number three,
and I can't seem to fucking learn.
I don't want to play myself,
I wanna play someone ugly or fat,
to show I can be a serious actress.
Hey, you mind if I ask you
a personal question?
If I do, I won't answer it.
How many times a week
do you get your pole wet?
What? I'm curious.
It averages out, I guess,
to about five or six times a week.
Damn.
You don't need to go on tour.
What about you?
Once.
Twice if I'm lucky or if I buy her something.
- That's not good.
- That is so motherfuckin' not good.
See if you can at least get
some free clothes out of it.
These two great black balls
of male erotic fury
go to explode on one another.
That's when everything started.
From those cave paintings,
the creation of the idea of "image,"
of the representation of ourselves.
And that's when we stopped
living inside nature,
and started living inside our heads.
Yeah, which is why we can
just sit back and watch
while greedy corporate
Bush-suckers destroy nature,
- since we're no longer a part of it.
- If you take humans out of nature,
then all they're left with is human nature.
OK, that sounds good
but what the fuck does that mean?
That's no doubt his new assistant.
I heard you fucked him.
No! I did not fuck him.
So why were you so mean
during my crit, you bitch?
Or is that just the new Claire Fisher?
There's a new Claire Fisher?
What was wrong with the old one?
She just waited around
for the world to happen to her.
- Hey, Jimmy.
- What the fuck?
Oh, God, I'm sorry.
I thought that was going
to be a charming moment,
- but now you want to kill me.
- No way.
What good would my life be without you?
Shut up.
So, Claire Fisher.
Yes, Jimmy.
I'm not exactly sure
I know what your last name is.
I would love to hang out with you.
Say when.
OK, you are verging dangerously
close on being smarmy.
You still haven't answered my question.
I could come over tomorrow afternoon,
but I have to be home by seven at the latest.
No! That's hardly any time with you at all!
And Nicole misses you.
Well, I miss Nicole too
but I have kids of my own, Sophia.
Federico, did Arthur leave
some sort of forwarding address?
No, I don't think so.
Vanessa, I'm gonna have
to call you back, OK, sweetie?
Vanessa? Oh, no, he didn't.
He's engaged in a campaign
of harassment against us!
Ruth, I wish you'd let this go.
No. I have a good mind
to get the authorities involved.
That's never a good idea.
What have you got here?
Male, 60s, struck by lightning.
What happens to a person
when they get struck by lightning?
Cardiac arrest is what kills 'em,
but their insides get fried
wherever the current goes.
In this case, his right arm and left leg,
hence the separate embalming.
So he becomes sort of
a human fulgurite, as it were.
Federico, I need to contact Arthur!
Surely there's some way of tracing him?
Calm down!
Fine.
I'll just resign myself
to receiving excrement in the mail forever.
You little shit!
I'm losing patience
with all your "sensitive man" bullshit.
You're not sensitive.
You're a fucking eunuch. A castrato.
- Castrato, I like that.
- You little shit, you don't make jokes!
You take this seriously.
I'd flip you over and spank
your candy ass till it bled
if I didn't think you'd like it so much.
I won't, I promise I won't like it.
Nice try.
I wonder who that is.
Hey, shut the door.
What, you don't want somebody
to see you all tied up like this?
Too bad, because I want
the whole world to see
what a twisted sister you are.
Freak.
Hi.
I thought you might be up for
grabbing a movie or a bite or something?
Maya's with her Aunt Barb.
They went to Legoland.
I'm going kinda stir-crazy.
I just need to be with somebody, I think.
I just...ordered out for pizza.
That's who I thought you were,
the pizza guy.
I like pizza.
Bad timing.
- I guess I should have called.
- No, Nate...
stay.
You can meet him.
- OK.
- Just give me a few minutes.
I don't know if he's the right guy for her.
At least he has sex with her.
I had sex with her.
Right, you're the stud because
you've had sex with more women.
You're like, almost heterosexual.
What's up with you?
I don't know. It's weird at work.
I feel like Sarah Jane
from lmitation Of Life.
That makes me Troy Donahue.
OK, this fits.
But there's this side of me
that feels all puffed up
because everybody thinks I'm straight.
It's like I feel like I'm 15 years old again.
How fucked up is that?
In a culture that puffs up men
for being straight? Not very.
But, Keith, you have to come out.
David, that's my decision.
You are the last person I ever expected
to turn into a self-loathing homo.
Wait, I'll get that.
Duane, what up?
11am? I know.
Two venti soy lattes.
Yeah, later.
Bitch. Just because I'm the new guy,
I'm their fucking waitress?
- I can't answer my own phone?
- No, don't be silly.
I'll just make sure
they call me on my cell.
David, if they take me on tour
I can make 100 bucks an hour, OK?
And that's for us!
Hi, this is David and Keith. We can't come
to the phone because we're too gay.
So after watching this thing 100 times
I decide to do the Scarecrow for her.
So I'm dancing around, doing the thing
and throwing myself around like a rag doll and
she's laughing.
And then she starts doing it.
She's throwing herself around
and I can just see her
cracking her head open
on the edge of a coffee table.
You go from feeling like Super Dad
to the village fucking idiot.
Parenthood is
such a huge fucking responsibility.
Aren't you ever, you know, terrified?
Yeah, but I just remind myself
that some things in my life
I just don't have any power over,
and I never will.
You know, because fear is no good.
Fear can take over your life.
I still feel like Lisa's around...
pushing me to move on.
Wants me to...
But you can't. You can't rush it.
I should go.
- Nice to meet you, Joe.
- Yeah, you too. Take care.
- Are you all right to drive?
- Yeah.
I can't believe I was the only one drinking.
I feel like a lowlife.
Well, be good to yourself.
Yeah, OK, I will.
That guy is seriously wounded.
I want to put one of those
lampshades around his head,
like they put on dogs
so they don't chew their stitches.
I know. I felt like
I couldn't turn him away. Sorry.
No, I love having your ex-boyfriend invited in
when I'm trussed up in the other room
like a Christmas ham.
- Yeah?
- Yeah. That's hot.
- Really?
- That's very hot.
Hey, buddy.
Well, hello.
Whatcha doin'?
So long.
What is it?
Hey, buddy boy.
What's up, huh? How ya doin', huh?
What are you doing, huh?
Incoming.
- Is Celeste in there?
- Who wants to know?
Nancy Freymire.
I'm chairwoman of this event.
Please, stand back from the door.
- Hi, Celeste, I'm...
- We have a problem.
- That's why I'm here...
- I do my own hair and make-up.
It's in my contract.
Yes, but we were unaware that
there would be a $3,000 fee...
These people work hard.
We're actually trying to raise money
for people with anticoagulative
blood disorders.
Right, that's why I'm here for free.
I'm totally committed to this.
Lucien and Phyllis are not as rich as I am
- and cannot afford to work for free.
- Perhaps a more reasonable...
This problem needs to be resolved
before I go on stage, all right?
Otherwise, I don't.
Fine, but might I just say...
I think you're a gigantic bitch,
and I will no longer allow my daughters
to listen to your music.
I'm sorry. You're either trying
to weasel out of what you agreed to,
or were too stupid to even read it,
and I'm the bitch?
Trollop.
Jesus, some people are tense.
Keith?
- That's right.
- You peed in my john.
I did, and I apologise.
I used to be a cop.
I'm kinda new to this.
I'm a little weird about my bathroom.
What the hell is so funny?
Sorry, I can't hear you...
you got your head so far up Celeste's ass.
It is not!
Good boy.
I've been expecting you.
I have many messages for you.
Yeah. Yeah? What's my name?
They don't tell me your name,
just that you've lost a lot,
and that your heart has been broken.
Yeah, who's they?
An older man who watches over you.
Your father? Your grandfather?
He was very unhappy in life.
The other one is a woman, I think.
I can't be sure.
Sit!
You have a lot to work out in this life.
Too much for one life.
- You will have many lives.
- Right.
Listen, I think I oughta go, no offence.
- I just think this is a ball of crap, so...
- She's not gone.
She's trying to get to you.
She just doesn't know how.
She's...
Who is?
I see...a woman. I see water.
She thinks you stopped loving her.
But I only started loving her...
I wanted to love her...
the way she deserved to be loved.
- You still can.
- She's dead.
She isn't dead.
She's trying to get back to you.
She loves you.
- What can I do?
- You're embarrassing me.
Try to understand what I'm going through...
I am trying, but it's never enough!
My older brother dies when I'm ten,
my mother develops Alzheimer's
really early,
the love of my life turns out to be gay,
and my dad gets struck by lightning.
Why did all this happen to me?
I don't know.
But I do know that you...
Don't you fucking take my hand.
Are you serious?
You fucking broke my heart
and stomped on it.
And I was such a fucking idiot,
I went out of my way
to make it easier for you?
Because you wanted to suck cock!
I was so fucking in love with you,
you fucking sadist!
You make me sick!
I hate that you're gay.
I fucking hate it.
You don't hate that I'm gay.
You hate that I lied to you.
You should hate that.
I lied to myself too.
Are you sure you like it?
How could I not like the first piece
of furniture we purchased as a couple?
It'll be nice to have a place
to display my rock collection.
I spoke to a lawyer today
about pressing charges against Arthur.
Oh, shit.
Look, Ruth,
Arthur never sent us any excrement.
Then who did?
My son. That toy truck
was something I bought him.
The only thing I ever bought him actually,
before he was even born.
- Brian?
- Kyle.
I thought your son's name was Brian.
I have another son.
Why have you never told me this?
Because he's never been part of my life.
If he's sending us shit in the mail
he's a part of your life.
No, he isn't. I was very young.
His mother and I never even married.
Her family didn't think I was suitable.
- So you just left?
- He wasn't born yet.
I was very young.
Nobody wanted me to be part of his life.
Are there other wives
you've neglected to tell me about?
No! Of course not.
Art is just a sentimental construct
to alleviate our fear of death.
No, there's no way
to even determine what makes art art,
much less to teach it.
It's an illusion that anyone
can be taught anything.
I mean, yes, we can all be
conditioned up the wazoo,
but to really learn something,
something important,
that always comes from within.
The cunt has spoken.
Now the world sits in silence.
So, why do you teach art then?
Why?
Because I need the goddamn paycheck.
No, you don't, baby.
Bern left me very well taken care of.
All you have to do
is keep making paintings
and I'll keep buying them.
Did you know Olivier taught my son?
- No.
- I'm hot for teachers.
Drink more, Mom.
Darling, try the Shiraz, it's delicious.
No, I'm good.
I read in the paper
about a student who allowed
some corporation to tattoo
its logo on his forehead,
and in exchange
they paid for his education.
What the hell is that?
I imagine it's an education for someone
who wouldn't be able to pay for it himself.
It's way more than that.
My students are all in such a mad rush
to become commodities.
But that's always been true of artists.
Where is your bathroom?
Straight through there, to the left.
It's him!
He's the one. I can feel it. He's the one!
You're drunk.
Now, isn't it nice to have someone
who's not only great in bed,
but who's also your intellectual equal?
Don't fuck it up this time,
like you always do.
What if she's really not dead?
- Nate, they identified her teeth.
- Yeah, I know.
But what if, by some amazing coincidence,
somebody had
the exact same work done as Lisa?
I suppose that could be possible,
- but I think the chances are remote.
- But it could be possible, right?
- Are you high?
- No, I'm not, not any more.
Maybe you should just,
like, stay in tonight and try to chill out. OK?
I've got to go.
I've got a date with the Matthew Barney
of LAC Arts.
Even though I'm so not
the Björk of LAC Arts.
All the chicks are hatched and fluffy now.
Listen to them... cheep cheep cheep.
Make the chick sound.
Hi, baby, I made some Asopao.
Are you hungry?
Damn. I had a sandwich at work.
Where are the kids?
Gusto's in bed, Julio's spending
the night at Charlie's house.
I love you, Vanessa.
I know that.
Tell me what you'd like.
I like you.
No, tell me what you like me to do.
Just do whatever you want,
and I'll let you know
how it works out for me.
Why won't you tell me?
Look,
I don't have, like, a checklist
I need to go through.
- Like to have your nipples played with?
- Not if we have to talk about it!
How else am I supposed
to know what to do?
Are you telling me you don't?
OK, maybe we should
just go to the movie.
Maybe I should just go home.
All right.
You're never gonna learn anything, sweetie,
not in that programme.
How could you learn about counselling
in 18 months?
Well, after a lifetime of learning
how not to do things,
maybe I'm a little ahead of the game.
I just still can't believe you're
planning on becoming a shrink.
The irony.
It's superb.
The real irony is that shrinks
are who we hire
to straighten out our lives,
but invariably, they're the ones
who are the most fucked up.
I mean, twisted. Demonic.
Then it makes absolute sense
that Brenda would become one.
Honey, come on now.
A good shrink needs a sense of humour.
- Are you a good shrink?
- I think I'm a very good shrink.
- Does that mean you're fucked up?
- Abso-fucking-lutely.
You have no idea.
Darling, do you ever hear from Nate?
Yeah, actually, we saw him last night.
He's still grieving.
He showed us pictures of his daughter.
My God, she's so beautiful.
Those eyes, so open and trusting.
It's mind-boggling to think
that we were all like that once.
I get it!
Now this makes sense.
You want a baby!
Where did that come from?
You are getting a little long
in the tooth, you know.
This would be the time.
Brenda's feeling eggy.
OK, well, it's time for us to go.
- Nice meeting you.
- Nice meeting you, Jim.
I hope you're up for the challenge
of my daughter.
I am. I am.
- It's Joe, not Jim.
- Bye, see you in a few years.
Terrible evening.
What?
What time is it?
Time for you
to stop keeping things from me!
It sounds absurd when you talk like that.
OK.
I was just a grad student,
and I...
accidentally knocked up a young woman
from a very wealthy family.
I offered to marry her.
Her family was dead set against it,
so... I signed something,
and we both went on with our lives.
What was I supposed to do?
You've never even seen this child?
Yeah, I've seen him.
He tracked me down a couple of years ago.
He was living in some
motel over in Burbank.
And?
I didn't particularly care for him.
As a matter of fact,
I found him very unpleasant.
And I assumed he never
wanted to see me again.
Why?
Because he said,
"I don't ever want to see you again."
Where are you going?
I'm going to the bathroom.
George, how can you...?
I just don't see how...
- I feel like I don't know you at all.
- Ruth, please.
Don't blow this all out of proportion.
It's not good for either one of us.
- Hello?
- Nate?
- Barb?
- It's Lisa.
- Where are you?
- I don't know. They won't tell me.
Who won't tell you?
Nate, the number three is not important.
Wait, what?
You buried me. How could you bury me?
- I thought that's what you wanted.
- But I'm not dead.
It's not healthy, being so
disconnected from your own son.
That's why I called him,
and told him to expect us shortly past noon.
His number was in your address book...
- You looked without asking me?
- ..some shred of paternal feeling in you.
This is important to me.
I do not ask you for many things.
All right.
- You look terrible.
- I feel terrible.
I'm worried about you.
You're not taking care of yourself.
I'm doing the best I can, Mom.
You pointing out the ways
I'm failing doesn't help.
I'll be waiting for you in the car.
Nate, can I ask you something?
Now may not be the best time, George.
Has your mother always been so...
anxious about everything?
Pretty much.
She's gotten a lot better
since you two got married.
How'd you deal with her?
I moved away when I was 17.
For none of us liveth to himself,
and no man dieth to himself.
For if we live, we live unto the Lord.
And if we die, we die unto the Lord.
Whether we live, therefore, or die,
we are the Lord's.
Blessed be the dead who die in the Lord.
Even so sayeth the spirit,
for they rest from their labours.
- The Lord be with you.
- What?
That's not a very nice way
to answer the phone.
This is starting to get weird, OK?
You are not my wife.
I know that.
I do not want you calling me all the time.
Of course, I'm sorry.
I didn't think that I...
I don't ever wanna be a problem for you.
George, I have a question for you,
and I want you to answer me honestly.
Ruth, I get the feeling you think
I haven't been honest with you,
but I always have.
I just don't want to burden you
with things that don't matter.
That's what I would want from you.
What did you want to ask me?
I have no idea.
- We just wanted to thank you.
- Of course.
Seriously, man, thanks.
Jen told me how she unleashed on you.
I think she really needed to do that.
She's been doing it to me, mostly.
Which was making it harder
for him to be there for me.
Yes, that's a scenario I'm familiar with.
The funeral was awesome.
The old guy would have really liked it.
- OK, I'll go get the car.
- OK, thanks, hon.
I'm sorry.
I said some terrible things about you.
- Most of which were true.
- No, David.
I know it was hard for you,
probably harder than it was for me.
You're doing it again. Making it easy for me.
- Some things never change.
- Yeah, well, some things need to.
So why didn't you just
tell him what you wanted?
Cos there was absolutely no way.
I mean, it would just be too...
Seriously, you would do that?
- Of course.
- Yeah.
They'll never figure it out for themselves,
no matter how much
porn star screaming I do.
I just wish they knew how to do it
on their own.
- It's so embarrassing.
- Well, that's why girls are better.
They know.
No, thanks. I love you
but I'm not into eating pussy, OK?
I tried it once. It was...not for me.
I'll just have to keep
telling stupid guys point blank,
- "Lick my clit while you finger me."
- My God!
But, OK,
last year, I went out with this guy, Phil.
He was so hot, and he was, like,
so totally into sex,
I mean, we were always...fucking,
I mean, like, always.
But every time he would,
you know, go down on me,
it was like there was
this unspoken time limit.
I knew that just when it was
starting to get good for me,
he was gonna look up at me
with these lobster eyes,
like, "Can I come up now?"
So what makes you come?
I don't know. The usual stuff.
Why are we talking about this?
Maybe you've never had an orgasm.
Of course I've had an orgasm.
Because if you had,
you wouldn't be embarrassed
about asking for more tongue time.
Could I have really never had an orgasm?
Well, I've definitely felt a surge of desire.
And then, you know,
a sort of relief of that desire.
My God, Claire.
Have you never even rubbed one out?
- You don't masturbate?
- I don't find it that interesting!
You know, Claire,
we could show you
how to give yourself an orgasm
right now if you want.
Hello, not lesbians.
I don't think it's possible
that I've never had an orgasm.
Well, if you haven't,
you're seriously missing out.
I'd like to say George
has told me a lot about you,
but he really hasn't told me anything.
That's because he doesn't
know anything about me.
I know you blame me for everything
you don't like about your life.
Why is he here?
- This was your idea.
- Well...
Of course it was her idea.
You made it clear
you never wanted to see me again.
I didn't! Thanks.
Kyle, look, we can't change the past.
But maybe we can start fresh,
if you're willing...
You can't walk in here and start saying
this is this, and that is that, like you're God!
Because you know what? You're not God.
You're not even close.
I want all deliveries of excrement
to our house to cease!
Yeah, well, I want world peace,
but I don't see that happening either.
Why are you so angry at me?
It's your mother you should be angry at
and your grandparents.
What is it, you find my shit offensive?
No. I find it childish and hostile.
And I'm completely baffled at the timing.
- I mean, why now?
- Because my therapist says
I need to express my true feelings to you.
This is a goddamn waste of time.
George, please. Are you all right, Kyle?
- Do you need anything?
- Like what?
I don't know. Clothing, underwear, socks?
No.
Would you like a cappuccino
from my $7,500 espresso machine,
which I bought
so I never have to leave this room,
because I'm so fucking twisted
thanks to you know who?
Thank you, yes, I'd love a cappuccino.
I was kidding.
I don't know how to work it yet.
Well, we could all go to Starbucks.
I feel so Sharon Stone.
Do people still do these things
when they've had kids?
Yeah, some people do,
and some people don't.
I once walked in on my parents.
My father was rubbing a rolling pin
over my mother's breasts.
Is that something you'd
like for me to do for you?
No, thank you.
But I mean, that fucked me up more
than if they'd just been
fucking in front of us.
Which they also did, by the way.
I'm sorry.
- That was fun.
- No, it wasn't.
Kyle deliberately spilled
his frappuccino over me.
No, it was just that he was so nervous
being out in the world.
My heart goes out to him.
He lives in a motel!
Only because he's too damn lazy
to change his own sheets.
Ruth, his mother's family
comes from major money, old, old money.
He doesn't need us.
Children need more from
their parents than money!
It's unfortunate that I was cut out of his life,
but the fact remains,
I was cut out of his life.
And that's not gonna change.
He seemed so lonely.
Maybe we should invite him to dinner.
Yeah, sure. Why not?
Hey. How was the funeral?
It was...
"Awesome.
The old guy would have liked it."
What's this?
That? That's The Rock.
I would definitely tap that ass.
I'm still not out at work.
Yeah, so?
You were kinda pushing me to come out.
I don't care about that any more.
It's boring.
And I'd rather not fight.
OK.
Did you have fun? Huh, did you have fun?
She had a blast.
I can really see Lisa in her, Nate.
Yeah.
Listen, Barb, I need to tell you something. I...
I went to a psychic.
Was that helpful?
She said Lisa's still alive.
Jesus Christ.
I don't believe this.
What's wrong with you, Nate?
Do you need help?
Because if you do, you should get it
and not from a fucking psychic.
I want to have kids too.
Or just one or... or several.
And I want to have them...
it...
with you.
I mean, I never really
saw myself as, or...
I never really thought it was possible,
but somehow, ever since we've met...
everything seems...
English