- I'll see if they need anyone at the store.
- You know something, I need money.
- My rent is overdue and you're not helping.
- You could sell something.
How about you loan me some cashola
from your trust fund instead?
You could sell me your Justice League
of America Versus The Alien series.
A guy on eBay sold one last week for 500.
- For the whole series? That's bullshit!
- Swear to God.
The auction was rigged.
Besides, I need more than that.
Wanna know what you could sell that'd
pay your rent for the next three months?
- What?
- Blue Twister, 1941, issue number one.
- No fucking way. Can't do it.
- It's worth three grand easy.
I know what it's worth, Norbert.
I'll give you 2,500 for it.
- You just told me it was worth three.
- So? How bad do you want to pay your rent?
No way, I'm never selling it.
In fact, I'm going to be buried with it.
It's in my will.
Yeah, right.
Larry? Larry?
Larry, you there?
- Morning, fellas.
- Good morning.
Morning, Nate.
Rough night?
A little rough. I miss sleeping in my own bed.
I miss the boys, I miss Vanessa.
Not me, slept like a baby.
Dropped Maya off over Bettina's with Mom.
- How's she doing?
- Maya's fine.
If you want to know how my mother is,
she said call her and ask her yourself.
So when's she coming back?
I haven't the slightest idea.
Apparently, she still needs some space.
- You do want her to come back home, right?
- Of course.
Well, with all due respect,
why don't you get off your ass, go over there,
eat crow and bring her back home?
Because that's just what she wants me to do
and I'm not playing that game.
Yeah. Yeah, that's the way I'd play it.
You guys are more pathetic than I am.
I woke up in the night and you weren't there.
You were out here watching television again.
Yeah, I watched Jaws 3.
I drank too much green tea.
I kept having to get up to pee.
I am so glad we're not doing
that whole open relationship thing any more.
Me, too.
You are? Really?
You're not just saying that
because I said I'm glad?
No.
David, I have to come clean with you
about something.
What?
I had sex with someone after we decided not
to sleep with anyone outside the relationship.
- We said we weren't gonna do that any more.
- I know, but I fucked up.
- So who did you sleep with? Javier?
- No. Celeste.
OK, bullshit.
I'm serious.
Celeste is a woman, isn't she?
She is.
But I've slept with women before.
You know that.
You're serious? You slept with Celeste?
It was just once. It was an accident.
You were walking by
and just happened to fall into her vagina?
It just happened. I'm sorry it happened,
but it did and I felt I should tell you.
You haven't secretly decided to switch teams?
No. No way.
OK.
But OK.
Edie?
What are you doing here?
Hello. I'm Edie's friend Anita.
I just needed to talk to her.
Is she, like, home?
- Yeah.
- Well, can I come in?
- She doesn't want to talk to you.
- Why the fuck not?
She's just kind of over you for the moment,
that's all.
Oh, I see. Why?
Because you were a lesbian for about
two minutes, then suddenly you weren't.
On top of that, she said you got all grossed
out by her pussy. That was totally not cool.
OK, for the record,
I was not grossed out by her pussy.
OK, pussy, per se, does not gross me out.
I just didn't know what exactly to do with it.
It wasn't personal.
It just didn't do it for me, you know?
I'll pass that along.
No, we weren't related.
We used to work at Hi-De-Ho together.
- Is that a grocery store?
- It's a comic book store in Santa Monica.
Did he have a family, someone locally
or out of state, we could contact?
We're pretty much it.
I guess that's why he designated me
to be the executor of his estate.
We were all in the West Co
Blue Twister Society together.
Blue Twister?
The guy who can turn into a human tornado?
Yeah, or shoot smaller tornadoes
from his fingertips with the strength of an F5,
the strongest tornado there is.
His name was Alan Talbot, a scientist doing
research in a machine called the Vortexicon.
It was a prototype
for a nuclear-powered particle accelerator.
- Something went horribly wrong.
- He turned into the Blue Twister.
I read it when I was a kid.
I had no idea he had a society.
It's kind of an unofficial fan club.
Anyway...
..he wanted to be buried with...
..this.
It's issue number one from 1941.
It's extremely rare.
Extremely valuable.
Last thing he said before the shelf fell on him
was he wanted to be buried with it.
We were on the phone when it happened.
He made this noise like...
And then I hung up and called 911.
We're very sorry for your loss.
Oh, honey, that's terrific.
Marcie's lawyer poked so many holes in
the case, the Feds dropped the charges.
Wonderful.
I don't like lawyers,
but you give him a blow job if you have to.
OK, sweetie, I'll talk to you soon. OK, bye.
- That's a relief.
- It certainly is.
You wanna help Grandma fold laundry?
- No.
- No? That's OK.
You just sit there
and be your adorable little self.
- We should get out and do something today.
- OK, what?
I came up with the zoo.
It's your turn to come up with something.
- We could go to the park.
- We've been to the park almost every day.
Maya loves the park.
We've been through thisl
- Getting on your nerves, aren't we?
- Yeah.
- Like us to leave?
- I didn't say that.
- Are you sure?
- If I wanted you to leave, you'd know it.
Think big, Fisher. Think different. Something...
The sky's the limit.
I'm tired of coming up with all the ideas
in this marriage.
- This isn't a marriage.
- It's starting to feel like one.
I don't suppose
you want to make up with your hubby?
I'm not ready.
What if I told Nate to take Maya back
to daycare for the next couple of days?
- That's a start.
- What would you like to do?
No, you're missing the point.
What would you like to do?
George is always talking about his travels.
I thought we'd have adventures together.
- So far he hasn't taken me anywhere.
- So?
- Let's go on a road trip.
- Now you're talkin'.
- Where do you wanna go?
- Someplace exotic.
God, I love you!
- What, you can't handle that?
- Come on.
You can't, can you?
- Come on, Bren. I just came over here to...
- To what? Fuck my brains out?
You know what? You're right.
I can't handle this right now.
I need to know what you feel for me, Nate.
- Do you feel anything?
- Yeah, of course I do, Brenda.
God, look. I just spent the past year
dealing with losing somebody, OK?
Losing everything I committed myself to.
It wasn't even that good, when I'm perfectly
honest with myself, so I don't want...
- You want me to be available for sex without...
- No, I don't want anything, OK?
- This is too intense! I have a daughter now.
- That is so lame.
- What is lame about having a daughter?
- Using that as an excuse.
- I could be part of both your...
- No, you couldn't.
- I have to go.
- Yeah, fine, go.
- Look, I'm sorry...
- Just go, go, go.
- Hello?
- Hey, Vanessa, it's me.
- Hang on. Juliol
- No, no, no, wait.
- Hi, Papi.
- Hey, Julio.
I wasn't done talking to Mommy.
- She doesn't want to talk to you.
- She doesn't?
- No.
- OK.
How's my little man?
- Good.
- Yeah, yeah.
- When are you coming home?
- Soon. Papi's just been busy at work lately.
- I love you, Papi.
- I love you, too.
Hey, baby.
Nice!
So, where are we going?
- Rosarita Beach.
- Mexico?
That's not too far, is it?
Four hours, tops.
It's your trip, you're driving.
OK, then you're the navigator.
I did all the research.
I got a map from the internet and a list of all
the haciendas and I made us a reservation.
It's the off-season and everything's reduced.
Yeah, what the fuck? Let's go to Mexico!
It's not like I have to cross a bridge every day.
I never have to cross bridges, but...
I think about crossing them constantly.
You're talking metaphorically.
No, I'm talking about literal bridges.
Did anything bad ever happen to you
on a bridge?
No.
Did anything bad happen
to someone you love on a bridge?
They collapse all the time. If you Google
"bridge collapses", you get a thousand hits.
And you're worried that if you cross a bridge,
it'll collapse?
- Yes.
- That's a phobia, Byron.
I know that.
I want you to try something for me.
I want you to imagine
that you're walking down the street
and you come to a bridge...
- But I wouldn't, I would go around it.
- You can't. Going around it's not an option.
- I don't like this.
- It's just a short bridge.
Just imagine...
you're walking across it...
and it doesn't collapse.
Now you're on the other side, safe and sound.
- No, I'm not.
- You're not?
No, halfway across, I jumped off.
Are you taking any medication at the moment?
40 milligrams of Prozac.
OK, I have to check in with my supervisor,
Dr Kee, OK?
So we'll be right back.
I don't think he's suicidal.
I think he's phobic and I think he has OCD.
I think you might be right.
I'll up his Prozac and see if that helps.
I'd like to address his behaviour.
- Want to force him to walk across a bridge?
- No.
Yes, gradually.
You've got a real knack for this, Brenda, but
you can't just force someone who's phobic
- to face their fears.
- Why not?
You have to be more patient. Someone like
Byron might never get over his phobia.
Then what is the point
of continuing his therapy?
Maybe it's the one thing
that keeps him from jumping off a bridge.
I think we can do better than that.
Hey.
- Hey, did you hear?
- Hear what?
Professor Pope. She got in a car accident.
- She's dead?
- No. No, she just suffered internal injuries.
- She's gonna be out for at least a month.
- But she's going to be OK?
Yeah. Well, I mean, that depends on
your definition of "serious internal injuries".
If she punctured her gall bladder, she'll be fine.
Apparently we don't even need it.
But, if it's her liver or lungs
or something more vital, then it's not so good.
What if it was her labia?
Wouldn't that be totally tragic for her?
Why are you looking at me like I'm a retard?
Because I swear, Russell, sometimes you are.
And for your information,
labia are not internal organs.
Hello, everybody, my name is Billy Chenowith.
I'll be your sub for the rest of the semester.
- You know him?
- Yeah, I do.
..until then, you guys are unfortunately mine.
Hey.
- Oh, God, I feel so guilty.
- Why?
For being alive.
I wanted Lisa gone.
I just wanted her out of my life.
But you didn't make it happen.
- It should've been me.
- Oh, God, no.
No. Nate, too many people
love you and need you.
Your family, Maya.
I need you, I need you so much.
That's the problem.
You're so full of holes.
You're this gaping bottomless pit of need.
You neurotic, tedious, self-absorbed bitch!
Hey!
- Move it!
- Fuck off, you stupid bitch!
He turns waste into black gold -
oil and gasoline.
The amount of waste out there is enormous.
12 billion tons of solid waste produced
each year in the United States alone.
It takes the nation's dump trucks
323 million trips
to carry all that trash.
But some say there's more than rubbish
in the landfills.
Brian Appel's company believes there are
riches - a renewable energy resource.
We open this valve
and the oil comes out from here.
They're turning waste into fuel and they've
invented an ingenious new technology...
That's OK.
That's OK, that's OK.
Life is a series of accidents.
One after another.
OK. Well, now we know
the reason it was so cheap.
- It's a dump.
- It's not a dump.
It's rustic.
It just needs a little maid service, that's all.
- At least we can see the ocean.
- Well, there's that.
I made a terrible decision
and brought us to a horrible place.
Oh, come on, it's Rosarita.
We're in a foreign country, Fisher.
Horrible and terrible are underrated qualities
when travelling in a foreign country.
- They often lead to fun and adventure.
- Really and truly?
Know the saying, "You can't make
chicken salad out of chickenshit"?
I don't believe I've ever heard that one.
Well, I'm here to tell you, you can and I have.
I was in Patagonia for a while. Unbelievable
how cheaply you can live down there.
Then I got amoebic dysentery.
My grant money finally ran out
so I figured, time to head back to the States.
That's when I got the call from Dean Perelli
about filling in for Carolyn Pope.
The fact that Carolyn Pope is tenured
blows my mind.
What can I say? Shit definitely rolls uphill.
You don't think she's any good?
Well, she's strictly academic.
Muffin?
How's Brenda?
We haven't spoken in almost a year.
I guess you could say
we're officially estranged.
What's going on with you?
I don't know. I guess I'm depressed.
I don't think it's clinical, but...
.. I just can't seem to have a normal,
healthy relationship with another person.
Right. Get in line.
Nobody has normal, healthy relationships.
My theory, which is yet to be put into practice,
is to pick someone slightly less crazy than you.
Society propagates this vision of people
hooking up and staying together forever.
In reality,
how often does that actually happen?
I think it all comes down
to basic animal chemistry.
If you get the chemistry wrong, it's bleach
and that shit that makes bleach explode.
- Right, I think it's ammonia.
- Ammonia.
Yeah, I hear you.
You know, I think, like, you start out
with whatever your fucking parents
and their sick-fuck gene pools stick you with,
but if you see enough shrinks for long enough,
when you get your cocktail right,
then you can
get over yourself, have a life.
I wonder if there's a cocktail that can
make you compatible with someone else.
I sure as shit hope so.
Dig in, guys.
- These are mushrooms?
- Giant portobellos, the best.
The filet mignon of fungi.
If you wanted a filet mignon,
why not just eat a filet mignon?
Do you know how many units of caloric energy
it takes to make a single calorie of beefsteak?
No, but I've a feeling you're about to tell me.
78 calories of fossil fuel
for every calorie of beef protein.
The meat industry,
along with most of the agribusiness,
is completely and utterly unsustainable.
- So we shouldn't eat meat?
- Meat isn't the problem.
It's how far away from the table
food is produced.
If it's produced locally,
it's not just fresher, it's less wasteful.
I used to work at a food coop in Seattle.
We used to hunt for chanterelles.
I read somewhere
that mushrooms are grown in dung.
- Everything organic is grown in dung.
- What do you think fertiliser is?
These, I believe,
were grown in sheep dung in Ventura.
Evening, gentlemen.
David, care to join us for dinner?
- George grilled some portobello mushrooms.
- They were fertilised in sheep dung.
No, thanks. I'm going home to my husband.
You guys have fun.
I know it's a period piece
and a presidential biopic,
but what most people don't realise
is that William Howard Taft,
aside from being the fattest president ever,
was also, like, this underdog and a rebel.
He was kind of like the Eminem of his day.
Yeah, Sean Penn would be totally awesome,
but would he be willing to put on 150 pounds?
Yeah. All right. Yeah, listen, man, I gotta go.
I'll check you later.
- Hey, Bren. I haven't seen you in a while.
- Yeah.
- What can I do for you?
- I need a little something.
- What you want? Brownies, catch of the day?
- What do you recommend?
The catch of the day is this pale green shit
from Mendocino.
- It's very sticky, very nice, not too skunky.
- Sounds good.
Thanks.
- We don't eat dinner together any more?
- I thought you were working late.
Well, I'm not.
I'm sorry...
I just ate the last piece.
- But you want me to fix you something?
- No, I think I'll go to Fat Burger.
Alone.
You guys want to play three-handed bridge?
No.
Not me. I'm gonna turn in early. I'm beat.
Yeah, I think I really gotta give Maya her bath.
What the hell was that?
- Whoever the fuck you are, we can see you.
- Yeah, and we've got a gun.
And a phone! So if you don't step out
from behind those drapes...
- We're gonna fill 'em full of holes!
- Don't shoot. No shooting.
- It's you.
- You don't have a gun.
No, but unless you got a good fucking reason
for breaking in...
- I'm calling the cops.
- What the hell is going on?
- Where's Maya?
- In the playpen...
Run for it.
I think you broke my arm.
What the fuck are you doing in my house?
Get up.
You broke in
to steal your dead buddy's comic?
- It was his idea.
- Shut up. It's worth four grand.
Maybe four-and-a-half.
And he wasn't my buddy. I didn't even like him.
- That's it. I'm calling the cops.
- Don't bother, Rico.
I don't care if you liked him or not. His last wish
was to be buried with this. That's what we'll do.
So put it back.
Get the hell out of my house
before I change my mind and call the cops.
I think you broke my fucking arm, dude.
- Nicely done.
- Thank you.
Oh, man, I gotta get out of here.
That's cool with me.
Hey, don't forget your bag of tea.
- This water isn't very hot.
- It's a lukewarm tub.
- Have some of this?
- I don't like tequila.
You know that cold, rubbery lobster dinner
we just ate?
It was probably seething with bacteria.
Couple of swigs of this, we won't be fighting
over who gets to ride the porcelain bus.
We've been in here over ten minutes
and it's not getting any warmer.
- I've half a mind to complain to the manager.
- Go for it, Fisher.
- Do you speak English?
- Yes. How may I help you?
The heater in the Jacuzzi
doesn't seem to be working very well.
I'm sorry, we turn it off after sunset
during the off-season.
My friend and I are paying guests of your motel
and we would like the heater on in the Jacuzzi.
Whether or not it's the off-season
is none of our concern.
You can turn the damned thing on
or give us a full refund.
We can't give you a refund for the room.
You've checked in.
Then we'll check out
and I'll call the credit card company
and have them refuse payment.
I'll turn the heater on in the Jacuzzi,
but only for one half-hour.
Thank you very much.
I don't know what you did in there,
but this baby is cooking like a lobster pot!
Gimme some more of that.
What do you think?
Just remembering the first time I realised
what Dad really did in this house.
I had this dog, Yippie. I found him underneath
my bed and he was already dead
so I wrapped him up in a blanket
and I brought him downstairs to the prep room.
I thought maybe Dad could fix him,
you know, bring him back somehow.
Then I realised
there were all these bodies down there
and they were all dead.
Dad was fixing them, but not bringing anybody
back. He was making them more presentable.
I always thought they were so sad and alone
in the dark down there.
They just needed someone
to come and sit with them.
Yeah, I thought that, too.
Sometimes I still do.
That's you.
That's me.
Where's Dad?
He's not here.
Is this for class?
No, I'm not sure what it's for yet.
Maybe it's just for me.
I love that little coffin refrigerator.
Thank you.
I mean, I still always think about acting out,
but, now when I get in the car and take a drive,
instead of picking up a hooker,
I just go to the Krispy Kreme.
So now I'm addicted to Krispy Kreme
and I'm 40 pounds heavier and...
even my wife doesn't want to,
excuse my French, fuck me.
I'm sorry, someone here tonight
reeks of marijuana.
It's not AA.
No, but it's still against the rules.
I think you should leave
and come back when you're straight or sober.
You're right.
I'm sorry, but...
.. I really need to be here.
I'm...
I need to be here.
I'm really scared about what'll happen to me
if I leave so please don't make me leave.
Thank you.
Hey, buddy boy.
Yippie's dead.
Can you fix him?
I'm sorry, kiddo, but I can't.
I'll tell you what we can do, though.
We can give him a real nice sendoff.
We need something of yours to put in with him.
- He has my blanket.
- Something more personal.
I know. Why don't you climb in with him?
That way he'll never be lonely.
Nate, I'm sorry,
but I have to take something with me.
Being alone for eternity
sucks like you wouldn't believe.
I need something really personal,
like a piece of me.
- I've decided it should be Maya.
- No.
Nate, you know what Dad used to say?
We all have to go sometime.
- Who are you supposed to be?
- Death Man.
I wanted to be the Grim Reaper,
but the folks at Marvel had a copyright on it.
Sorry, kiddo,
you're all coming with me.
I could stay if you want me to.
Yes.
Nobody stays.
Including you.
Sit.
I'm allergic to dogs.
Now, there's the man I married.
Who wants the end piece?
Honey?
Buddy boy?
He liked a lot of things.
His comic book collection, of course.
The Lord of the Rings trilogy.
Every movie that Halle Berry was in,
except Monster's Ball.
For some reason,
he didn't like Monster's Ball.
It's like these guys hit 15
and got stuck in some kind of time warp.
It's kind of scary, isn't it?
It's just depressing how alienated they all look.
Well, from us maybe, but...
Iook at them, they're a community.
This is who they are.
Her name would maybe have been Linda...
- Are you crying?
- No, no.
OK, you know something?
You're acting like a serious freak.
Maybe I am a serious freak.
I don't know what the hell's going on with me.
I love this.
I feel like Butch and Sundance.
Isn't this beautiful?
Going on a beach with a horse...
You want to know what I think?
I think you should just move on.
- You do?
- How long were you two together?
- Since high school.
- That's a long time.
I know a lot of mammals mate for life,
but most primates don't.
We're human beings, not primates.
We share 98.8%
of the same DNA as a chimpanzee.
We're more closely related to them
than they are to gorillas.
Maybe your time with her is over.
You're young enough.
Just go find another one.
Oh, my God, you guys folded my undies.
That is so fucking sweet.
- Is she still living here?
- Evidently.
- Weren't Edie and Anita supposed to be here?
- They were supposed to be, but they're not.
I think it's because of me.
- I thought we were gonna take pictures.
- Dude, nobody brought a camera.
Here, feed the pigeons.
This sucks. Wanna go see a movie?
Not really.
Wanna get something to eat?
- I'm not hungry.
- Yeah, me neither.
We could drive over to LACMA,
check out the Arbus exhibit.
Why don't you go ahead,
then report back to us?
OK, maybe I will.
Later.
So I heard something.
- What did you hear?
- It was from Edie and Anita.
They said something about
you never having an orgasm.
Edie did a piece on it last night
at Nuts and Jolts.
She did?
"A straight girl wanted to eat my pussy,
but then she changed her mind."
- She said that?
- Verbatim. It was kinda cool, though.
- God, I am so fuckin' embarrassed right now.
- Nah, don't be.
- Yeah, that's easy for you to say.
- No, listen, really, don't be.
- Is it true, though?
- Yes, I changed my mind.
No, I meant about the orgasm.
Because if it is, it's totally cool.
Believe me, most of the women I've been with
have had a hard time.
But I heard about this new technique and
I've been looking forward to trying it out.
Would you like me to try it out with you?
OK.
- I was watching that.
- Too bad.
- You trying to pick a fight with me?
- Maybe I am.
- I thought we were OK about Celeste.
- We were, now we're not.
You can't just be OK with something,
then not be OK for no reason.
Maybe I've had time to think it through
and it's not digesting well.
Take a Tums, why don't you?
I fucked Sarge.
- Who?
- The veiny guy from La Habra.
Who didn't secretly want me
to have women's breasts!
Wait. When did you fuck the veiny guy?
After we agreed not to fuck anybody else.
Why would you ask me not to fuck anybody
if you were gonna fuck somebody yourself?
Because I didn't want you to fuck anyone else.
I wasn't planning on fucking anybody either.
- Well, how was that fair?
- I could do it without it meaning anything.
Believe me,
I can do it without it meaning anything, too.
- What's that mean?
- I wouldn't do it if it meant anything
because I love you.
You are not getting off that easy.
Look, I fucked Celeste, you fucked veiny guy
from La Habra. Tit for tat, we're even.
You don't get to say the word tit to me. Ever.
I'm taking a shower.
Yeah, well, don't blow anybody
while you're in there.
- Pretty good, huh?
- Oh, my God.
You know what it's called?
It has a name?
Grinding the corn.
Grinding the corn?
What's the corn?
You know, with, like, a mortar and pestle.
Only you push the pestle against
the rim of the mortar, not in the bowl.
Yeah.
Hi, Maya.
Come in.
Is he going to be OK?
- It's not my fault, is it?
- Of course not, Fisher.
Probably something wrong with it.
I think I'd like to go home now.
English