Hello!
Damn it.
If it hasn't worked for the last
45 minutes, it's not gonna work now.
That goddamn night guard
must be drunk and deaf.
I'll try my phone.
We've already tried.
There's no reception up here.
Just wait for the rescue teams.
Shit.
- Shit.
- Don't do that.
- You'll make it worse!
- We have to.
Let's all try to open this door once more.
Give it everything we got.
OK, go.
We're gonna drop ten floors and die!
We could use a little more
Bruce Willis attitude, mister.
Let me out. Here.
Just let me out!
- Will you just let me out?
- So obnoxious!
You'll be fine.
- Get up there, we'll give you a boost.
- OK.
I'll take the stairs. I'll get some help.
My God!
We're all gonna die!
- Somebody grab my hand.
- No, she should go first! Go.
Come on.
- Oh, my God!
- Ken, get in here!
No! Let me go.
Don't pull me back in!
Oh my God! What happened?
Go find out what happened!
Let's both go.
I think we should stay together.
I'm too scared.
George, the glass, put on your slippers.
What did you do?
I'm awake.
You were whimpering
and paddling with your feet.
What were you dreaming about?
I don't remember.
Yeah, it's at the Bellandi Gallery, downtown.
Where Jimmy was.
You got my postcard, right?
OK, call me if you need directions.
All right, I'll see you tomorrow.
Bring cool people.
Hi, Edie. It's Claire.
Listen, tomorrow is my show.
I know you probably won't be there
but I wish you would be there.
OK, never mind.
- I broke up with Russell.
- Why?
Why do you think? He's a big drama queen.
Everything's so heavy and negative.
- He's such a fucking victim.
- Yeah, really.
He got in my face about your show.
God, he's unbelievable.
I was like, whoever's idea it was,
and I don't fucking care, Claire ran with it.
I was like, adapt, dude.
Thank you for defending my honour.
I brought you a present. Happy fame.
My God, is that cocaine?
- This is so disco!
- Let's do a few lines.
Shit, I want to, but I have to go to my gallery
and meet some, like, huge movie star.
Seriously? What movie star?
I don't know. Some, like,
celebrity woman wants to buy my stuff.
- You're getting way too cool for me.
- Fuck you.
No, it's a fishtail.
- It's a fishtail!
- Yes.
I'm calling the lawyer again.
You're too clever. He already told you.
I know he already said that Barb has no right
to custody, but there's an article on the web.
You're the father. Barb's the aunt.
Maya's staying right here where she is.
You're not taking this seriously.
I am, but it doesn't do us any good
to live in this constant state of panic.
That's easy for you. Maya's not yours.
Yes, can you reach Mr Sutcliffe
for me, please? Nate Fisher.
- It's an emergency.
- This is about your emotions, not Maya.
Would you stop using the therapy voice?
It drives me nuts.
How would you know? You've never tried it.
I don't need it.
It's not my fault there's always a disaster.
What's with this book? It's macabre.
Just get rid of it or put it away.
Michaela gave it to me to give to David.
I keep forgetting about it.
- I really wish you'd consider it.
- Everything is under control!
Of course it is.
Number three.
Excuse me?
That's him, number three.
David.
David, it's almost eleven.
Are you gonna get up?
Yeah.
What?
I'm still replaying that
fucking look he gave me.
- Do you want to talk about it?
- No, I don't want to talk about it.
I've told you about it 900 times.
I've told my therapist about it 900 times. I want
to fucking move on and leave it behind me.
So do it. You can.
No, I can't. I'm fucking stuck.
If you could do anything,
what would you do?
I'd tell him what I think of him
and what he did to me.
That evil, evil fuck.
Well, you can do that.
I know, I said it all to the therapy pillow.
No, you can visit him in jail.
What?
He'll either see you or he won't. But try.
- Are you serious?
- Yes, I am.
It would be extremely self-destructive
to put myself in that situation!
I can't believe you'd even suggest it.
Two hours, great! Let me know when
you're on the ground and I'll come meet you.
Me too.
Bye.
My daughter's on her way
to Hawaii for a conference
and she has a layover this afternoon.
Would you like to meet her for lunch?
Maggie? Really?
Oh, yes!
This is so exciting!
What kind of conference?
I don't know what she does.
- Pharmaceutical rep.
- You're proud of her. I can tell.
She's the apple of your eye.
I know you're doing this for me, too, George.
- Thank you.
- You'll like her.
I can't wait!
I'm not the person
who's supposed to be here.
We've been divorced for ages.
He must have a new wife or a girlfriend.
You were his emergency contact.
He worked at the same place for 25 years.
I'm sure he just forgot to change the form.
Maybe he still loved you.
He's a very nice guy
but, you know, I've moved on.
I'm sorry, but there are decisions
to be made about the funeral.
Well, I don't want to make them!
Now there must be someone else
who can deal with this.
Cos I can't believe it!
How can you get killed by an elevator?
Three other people were stuck inside.
He tried to get them out
and the elevator tore him in half.
I hit a new low.
I made the bereaved vomit.
Don't say we have to send him elsewhere.
I just embalmed him.
No, we worked it out.
It's weird we don't sew him together.
Yeah.
Once he's in the casket,
can't even tell the difference.
Here, it's a present from Michaela.
What a sweet kid.
Little morbid, but sweet.
So unlike her mother,
that crazy bitch from hell.
What's that?
It's Roger Pasquese.
Does that ring a bell?
Yeah. Yeah, it does.
How are you, Keith?
I'm fine. A little surprised.
How are you?
I'm well, thank you.
Enjoying the day. Carpe diem.
Yeah, that's great. What's up?
I'm taking a break
from angry ugly white men.
Let's take it easy now, huh?
OK, seriously.
I have a business proposition for you
and I'd like for us to meet. What do you say
you come to my house and we talk?
Probably not. Nothing against you,
it just doesn't seem like a good idea.
But thanks, anyway.
You know, certain papers
have yet to be signed.
Our lawsuit might rear its ugly head again.
Roger, we had an agreement.
I don't think a blow job is legal or binding.
How about tomorrow afternoon?
I'll think about it.
Well, you see, Nicole,
Claire has a plurality of
influences at work here.
They're portraits, an ancient, classical form.
And they're photos, which are modern.
And then they're torn to bits.
A nod to the Dadaists and the Cubists as well.
Then the pieces are reassembled
for a deconstructed mix
of detachment and tenderness
which seems to me
to be very new millennium.
Anything you'd like to add, Claire?
What you said is part of it.
- Of course, it's more involved than that.
- I totally get it.
It reminds me of
paper dolls and bad relationships
and lies people tell about stupid things.
- Right?
- Right.
- ls this all you have?
- As a matter of fact,
she's working hard on a whole new series.
It looks very promising.
Cool, when can I see it?
Soon. Very soon.
I have to figure out some stuff.
We used to come
to this place when I was a girl.
Sarah and I would eat
Thousand lsland dressing all by itself.
- What a treat!
- I like this place.
The menu never changes.
And this building has stood through
all the mudslides, fires, earthquakes.
Yes, it's comforting.
- Maggie!
- Daddy!
- Hi.
Sweetie, it's great to see you.
- You, too.
- This is wonderful.
What a treat.
With managed care the way that it is,
most of these samples that I haul around
end up going to patients
who can't pay for prescriptions,
so everybody at the doctor's office
is glad to see Maggie.
So what's new in antibiotics?
Here. A course of this will knock out
just about anything.
But you have to take the whole seven days.
Any side effects?
Minimal. Maybe a little nausea,
so take it with food.
- Thanks, hon.
- Are you sick?
No. I just want to be prepared.
Of course, these things
won't touch anything viral.
Did you know that you can order
potassium iodide off the internet now?
That's great.
That is so much more convenient.
What's potassium iodide?
Anti-radiation.
If you take it in time,
it blocks the thyroid's uptake
of airborne radioactive iodine
from a nuclear accident.
Let's not worry today, Dad.
We're OK today.
Of course we are.
OK, I'd like to talk about this morning.
What about it?
Well, besides the fact that your attitude
to therapy is totally medieval,
you have really big emotions, Nate,
and they're not that easy to live with.
Sometimes you dump them all
on me and it's not fair.
Maybe if I got some support from you,
that's not how it'd feel to you.
You have got to be kidding, right?
All I do is support you. It's like a full-time job.
What are you looking at?
I can't compete with a dead woman.
Brian and I just adored him.
He took us hiking, camping...
Camping? I love camping!
We'll have to go, too.
- He taught us campfire songs.
- Campfire songs? You?
- Yeah, a couple.
- Remember?
It was kid heaven.
Oh, George.
If you ladies will excuse me...
Well, thank God he shaved for you.
He used to have a big scraggly beard.
A beard? I can't picture it.
- Yes, I can.
- Exactly.
He looked like he just walked out of the Bible.
- So how's he been?
- Fine.
No problems?
You can tell me.
What do you mean?
Ruth, I want you to have all my numbers.
If you need me, call. Anywhere, any time.
Well, thank you.
He trusts me.
Can I ask you a personal question?
- If it isn't too personal.
- Are those whiskers your own?
No one else has claimed them.
Do you think I should?
I can't tell you what to do.
What do you mean?
You love to tell me what to do.
This is different.
One more question.
Are you wanted by the police?
That's just the trouble. Nobody wants me.
Maybe if I see him and tell him how I feel,
I can finally get my balls back.
- You have balls.
- Yeah.
Look, if you decide to go, I'll go with you.
No, I have to handle this alone.
- I'm going.
- I just said...
I know what you said. The same thing you said
when I was on the road. ''I'm fine.''
But you weren't. You weren't honest with me.
I wasn't honest with myself.
- I did the best I could.
- I know.
But, I still don't know when to believe you.
I'm not taking any chances.
Come on, guys. Look at this mess.
You're supposed to be helping me out here.
And you're sitting too close to that TV.
Get away from it.
Garbage man, come on.
Come help Mommy out.
Very good. Thank you.
Would you turn off the light and go to sleep?
Can't.
Yes, you can,
if you quit suckin' weed and lie down.
I have to make sure
I invited everybody on my list.
Plus, I'm not tired. I'm all buzzy.
Did you get into that blow without me?
No, look, it's my first exhibition.
There's all this stress.
Claire. One night. Some pictures. A party.
I think you can deal.
- Hey, Bren!
- Maya's still asleep.
- Check this out, this is what Lisa wore.
- Yeah.
No, when she died.
She bought this shirt a week before she died.
- Nate.
- No, I know it.
- Don't do this.
- She showed it to me.
She asked me if I liked the colour.
This is the shirt.
This is the beach where she disappeared.
How did Michaela send this picture of Lisa
when Lisa never made it to Santa Cruz?
I don't know.
There's probably a simple explanation.
- Then I want to hear it.
- God, this is never going to end.
Don't you realise what's going on? There was
somebody there who took this photo.
- Why don't you call the girl and just ask her?
- No, I'm going up there.
The way they feel about me, do you think
they're gonna just give her the phone?
How do you think they're going to feel
when you turn up sounding crazy?
- Thanks for the support.
- Come on, this is ridiculous.
You're driving up there
all because of some random snapshot.
- I don't need your permission.
- No, you don't.
I don't. So I'm gonna take Maya
to my mother's house.
Why?
Well, because she's never
spent the night here without me.
If you don't think I can take care of Maya,
there's not really a lot of point
to the three of us living together.
OK, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I just, you know...
I have to do this.
Every day it seems harder to breathe.
ls that my imagination?
No. The air is poison, George.
It's a scientific fact.
They took blood samples from
a remote village of lndians in Bolivia.
Alto Los Zarzos.
Even they were contaminated.
There are chemicals in the rain.
I keep thinking any minute
something terrible will happen.
It's already happening.
Yes, I know, but...
Our days are numbered.
It's only a matter of time.
But I truly believe if we prepare...
Don't be naive, George,
you weren't brought up that way.
- There's no hope.
- Stop saying that!
Even if it's true, I can't give up.
No! No, I won't.
- Are you all right?
- Yes.
No.
Could you sit with me?
The way he died, God, it's awful.
I can't stop thinking about it.
If there was anyone
who deserved to go in their sleep, it was Ken.
It's the way that Ken lived that's important.
We weren't close any more.
- He was your husband once.
- 15 years ago.
Honestly, when I got the call,
I had to think, ''Ken? Ken who?''
Then I remembered.
Every minute we spent together,
I remember everything.
I'm going to bury him with the rest of my family.
- That's the way it should be, don't you think?
- Yes, yes I do.
Even if I marry again,
when I'm dead I want Ken there, too.
Family's family.
Divorce doesn't change that.
Not divorce, not death,
not anything. When people...
get in your heart...
They stay for good.
Maggie, this is Ruth.
I'm very sorry to bother you in Waikiki,
but please call me back.
I'm worried about your father.
Mr Fisher.
Can I see a valid passport, a visa,
alien registration card
or valid driver's licence?
You may take in one handkerchief,
an unopened pack of tissue,
$30 in coins and dollar bills only.
You may not take in cameras,
phones unless approved
prior to entering the visiting room.
I don't have anything.
Are you wearing implants
or prosthetic devices?
No.
Please go down the hall to the next officer.
He'll direct you to the metal detector.
Sir, please proceed down the hall.
What if a lot of people come?
They're all going to be looking at me.
lsn't that what you want?
I don't know. I haven't done much coke. I don't
wanna be more nervous than I already am.
No, it'll help. This shit's not cut with meth.
It's pretty smooth.
It makes you feel really important
for about 20 minutes.
Gimme.
- I'll hang on to it.
- I thought it was a present.
It is, but since it's your special night
I could be, like, the keeper of it.
- Yeah?
- OK. It's nice.
- What?
- I just want to look.
Whatever. I'll meet you back here
in a half hour for a little...
The boys are at a birthday party.
But if you call, you could probably stop over.
It's you I came to see.
Well, I gotta go soon.
Vanessa,
I apologise. This is...
This is all my fault.
All my fault.
What I gave Sophia,
the time and the attention...
The money.
The intimacy.
I had no right.
It all belonged to you and the kids.
Even if you hadn't slept with her,
it was adultery.
Being close to somebody else when
you're the most important person in my life,
yes, that was adultery.
I betrayed
my marriage.
I was so wrong.
I'm so sorry from the bottom of my heart.
You finally said it. Thank you.
I'll come back home and
we'll go back to being ourselves again.
We can't go back.
Everything has changed.
I never expected this.
And I feel really sad, but it feels right.
No.
You know that we got together so young.
Being on my own is good for me now
and I think that maybe it's good for you, too.
No.
No, it is definitely not good.
- Don't you love me any more?
- Of course I love you.
It's just not like before.
Oh, Jesus.
I'm not trying to hurt you, Rico, I swear to God.
I want a divorce.
You don't mean it.
- Who are you?
- David Fisher.
Remember me?
Yeah, I think so.
How ya doing?
How do you think I am?
I don't know.
You look pretty good compared
to everybody else I see.
I hope you're happy here
behind bars where you belong.
Nobody belongs here, man.
You ever been through detox? It's like dying.
Every fucking minute you die.
Good.
Did you bring me something?
No, I hate you.
Oh, God. Here we go.
You soaked me with gasoline.
You beat me and stuck a gun in my mouth.
Well, yeah, you drove me all over hell with
a dead chick farting in the back of your van.
What was I supposed to do?
You scared me shitless.
Now I walk around feeling like everybody's
gonna humiliate and murder me.
Well, they are. So I did you a favour.
Now you'll be a little more careful, won't you?
Stop your fucking games for once...
It's your game. You come here
and you don't bring anything.
You just want to shit on me and break me
down, like everybody else. Well I won't let you.
- Apologise to me.
- For defending myself? Fuck you.
You have a family, right?
You have people looking out for you?
- Yeah, but...
- All I have is you, David, and you hate me.
You made a special trip up here
to tell me that you hate me.
I think I'm the one that
deserves a goddamn apology.
You really are sick.
I'm not the one who sits in jail
when he doesn't have to.
- Well, at least you know how I feel.
- And you know how I feel.
You can come visit me again
if you want to.
No, I won't be back.
Well, maybe when I get paroled
you can come and take me out to lunch.
Probably not. I'm pretty busy.
I don't think you can be an artist
without experiencing major suffering.
And you have to be aware
of the suffering around you.
Yeah, I've been influenced by
Dada and Cubism
but I also feel like I've added detachment...
..and tenderness, for the new millennium.
This is fucking fantastic.
Everybody loves my shit.
- There's somebody in here.
- Have you talked to Jimmy?
No, every time I see him,
somebody grabs me to talk.
- You should at least get him high.
- Here, you do it.
- How do you think it's going?
- What?
- My show, whore.
- Fine, whore.
What are people saying?
I don't know. I'm just hanging out.
Come on, I wanna know what they're saying.
And don't do it all. Save some for me.
Maya.
What are you doing?
Everyone is very impressed with Claire's
pictures. You must be very proud.
I certainly am.
I'm proud of all my children.
Nate and I back together again.
It must seem very sudden.
I married my husband
almost right after we met.
Sudden is something I understand now.
It's not always best.
But, sometimes it is.
Brenda, I'm glad Nate is with someone,
and I hope the three of you are very happy.
Thank you.
He says you're studying psychology.
Yes, I am going to be a cognitive therapist.
What does it mean when a person
starts talking to himself out of nowhere?
- None of your pieces have names. How come?
- I couldn't think of any.
Come on, don't bullshit me.
I'm actually interested.
I feel like when you give something a name
people take your word for it.
Which is OK for some things, but not these.
I didn't want to tell anybody what to see.
It's like music that's called Opus 15
or Three-Part lnvention ln A Minor.
What's that about?
I want you to really look at it
and deal with it on your own.
You know, it's like life.
It's kinda scary.
With no guide, I don't know where I'll end up.
You know what?
I have no fucking idea
what these pictures mean.
I know. lsn't it great?
- Roger, you don't need a bodyguard.
- Yes, I do.
Look, I have enemies. There are fuckers
out there that would do anything to get me.
Anything. I just want to feel safe.
And I will pay you a shitload of money.
Well, I couldn't work for you exclusively.
It would have to be a freelance situation.
I'm sure we can figure something out.
We'll draw up a contract.
First, I need something in writing that says
you're going to drop our lawsuit. Forever.
Oh, all right.
ls that one of the people you're afraid of?
No, that's Steve.
He stays in the guesthouse sometimes.
Well?
I'll give it serious consideration.
- I wasn't sure you'd be here.
- Of course I'm here.
You were my student, my assistant.
You think that means nothing to me?
It's my responsibility and pleasure
to support you.
Besides, you're competition now.
Though I thought it would be
Russell first in this position.
Well, you were wrong. Because it's me.
And so it all begins.
With the first success, corruption.
It's corrupt to feel like
I finally did something right?
Actually, yes, it is. You'll see.
But so what? Who wants to be a saint, right?
- Not me.
- No, no one does.
And the work suffers.
I toast you with this shitty wine.
Hello there.
Wow, you look recovered.
I feel fabulous. Everyone should drop an organ.
After the first shock, it's positively liberating.
So, is this the fruit of Nate's loins?
Maya, this is Margaret.
Look, don't take this personally,
but I don't think she likes you.
She hardly knows you're here.
Margaret can't help trying
to make us feel bad about ourselves.
You know, Brenda, it's unethical to use
an innocent child to express your resentment.
Claire, do you do commissions?
Yes.
Well, I want you to photograph Olivier and me
and do that thing you do,
only mix all our pieces together.
That will be a portrait.
Kudos, darling, you're brilliant.
Later.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Somebody may want to buy something.
I'll be right back.
What the fuck? Are you blowing me off?
- No!
- You haven't said shit to me since I got here.
I mean, what the fuck?
I think it's pretty fucking rude.
OK, maybe you didn't realise this
but I'm a little fucking busy right now.
I'm in the middle of my fucking show.
Maybe you don't remember, but I'm the one
who fucking got you this fucking show.
Jimmy.
Well, fuck you, then. Fuck you all.
- Hi, Michaela.
- Hi, Uncle Nate.
I gave the book to David.
Thank you.
He liked it a lot.
- There was a picture in it.
- I know.
Where'd the picture come from?
Do you know who took it?
Why did you put it in the book?
You should talk to my dad.
He's in the office.
God, you freak,
when are you gonna let it go?
When you admit in public
that I am part of your work.
You're not!
I created these pieces.
They are mine, people love them.
I love you.
You love? You fucked a man and lied about it.
- You fucked a woman!
- Not when I was with you!
No, you just went and had an abortion
without me!
Don't you dare go there.
Don't you fucking dare!
ls there a problem, guys?
You are so deeply irrelevant.
- Are you fucking him now?
- All right, Russell.
You fuck Jimmy, get a gallery.
What can Billy Chenowith do...
- You asshole, I fucking hate you.
- Stop now. It's time to leave.
- Get your hands off.
- Just leave.
This needs to stop. Out.
Are you all right?
Take me home.
Are you crazy?
If I was you, I'd move on down the road
before Barb finds out you're here.
Hoyt, I'll ask you one more time.
Then I'm calling the police.
Did you take that picture?
She's a Kimmel.
We tend to point cameras at each other.
Somebody obviously took it.
Maybe it was me.
No, I remember this. This was
a couple of years ago. We had a picnic.
You're a fucking liar.
You were with there with Lisa
on the beach the day she died.
- No...
- Yes, you were. And this proves it.
- You son of a bitch, what did you do to her?
- Nothing! God, nothing!
This was a place that we used to go.
I'd drive south and I'd meet her there.
Alone?
Maybe, a few times. Yeah.
Why?
We had a thing. It was on and off.
But it was intense. You know Lisa.
She was intense.
When was this? When we were married?
Before.
I don't believe you.
She told me what it was like to be your wife.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Why did you put her through all that?
You think she just spent
her whole life waiting for you?
People loved Lisa. And she loved us back.
She might have killed herself because of you.
Did you ever think about that?
No, she...
Listen, let's take a walk, OK?
This is a big misunderstanding.
No! Lisa would never kill herself!
I know that.
She might leave me
but she would never leave Maya.
So you tell me what happened
on that beach right now. Right the fuck now!
I wanted some time by ourselves.
Lisa said she wasn't into it.
You know, clean slate, never again. OK, fine.
I couldn't let her tell Barb.
I did not get angry with her.
I played the guitar. I sang her a so..
I sang her a song.
And we...
went our separate ways.
Have you been here all night?
I had to put things in order
and I guess I fell asleep.
Didn't mean to worry you.
No harm done.
Come on, let's go back to the house.
I can't do that.
Yes, you can, dear. It's where we live.
No, Ruth.
This is where I live now.
Let's get married and have a baby.
Will you?
Yes.
Oh, good. My bougainvillea needs this.
You were brave to face him.
- Not really. There was a guard.
- Doesn't matter.
I'm proud of you.
I thought it would set me free
but it didn't change anything,
except now I know he really is insane.
You're missing the point.
There is no point. That's the point. lsn't it?
Don't give me this phoney existential bullshit.
I expect better from you.
The point's right in front of your face.
Well, I'm sorry, but I don't see it.
You're not even grateful, are you?
Grateful?
For the worst fucking experience of my life?
You hang onto your pain like it means
something, like it's worth something.
Well, let me tell you, it's not worth shit.
Let it go.
lnfinite possibilities and all he can do is whine.
- What am I supposed to do?
- What do you think?
You can do anything, you lucky bastard.
You're alive.
What's a little pain compared to that?
It can't be so simple.
What if it is?
English