You stupid, stupid son of a bitch!
You've got three beautiful girls
and they are never gonna be
able to take a drink!
They are never gonna
be able to have cocktail hour.
You wanna know why?
- Suzanne, take it easy.
- You wanna know why?
Because you are a fucking alcoholic.
- Suzanne.
- What?!
Should we get some help?
What? What's up?
I just do not want to go to fucking ldaho.
Oh, don't drive yourself crazy over it.
I just don't want to go.
You told them you were coming,
you were gonna go, so just go.
You know, I'd be fine if it was just
the dedication of Lisa's ashes...
- But?
- I don't wanna be with the Kimmels.
And I really don't wanna put Maya
in that situation.
Death, death, death.
I'm done looking backward,
I just wanna look forward,
with you, with us.
- You do?
- Yeah, I do.
What are you doing, little monkey?
Honey, half these boxes
are full of Lisa's clothes.
Yeah, I saved them for Maya
so she can see them when grows up.
Well, when you think about it,
this ceremony does the same thing.
You wanna go so that when Maya grows up
you can say to her, "You were there."
- I have colitis.
- Oh, no.
Yup. I do.
There it is, colitis.
Fuckin' Jesus, Mom!
You're a seven-letter whore.
And it's on the triple word.
It's all about the seven letters for her.
It always has been.
She skips three turns
then mashes the shit out of you.
- I'm your biggest problem.
- You are.
- You. You.
- You!
- I quit.
- The hell you do.
I'm going to miss this.
- I don't wanna go home.
- Play the game.
Is...
- umurawi a word?
- What?
It's all I've got. Umurawi.
Fisher.
Coming!
- Sorry, were you sleeping?
- No, but we were in bed.
The people are coming,
the people are coming, the people, the people!
- What time is it?
- It's Miller time.
- Hey, whore.
Dude, come on,
help me bring this over here.
- Where do you want it?
- Over there.
Guess Jimmy's the refrigerator magnet
of the week again?
I get dizzy trying to keep up.
I get it, cos you and Russell are like
Mr and Mrs Happy Suburban Love Couple?
Maybe we are.
Maybe we're gonna buy
a ranch house in a cul-de-sac.
- Did you bring weed?
- Yeah.
Hey, sweetie?
Did we bring my CDs in?
I got 'em, Baboo.
- Get out of my shit.
- You said you brought pot.
- I could get it for you, Stonehenge.
- Get it then.
I want a lot of flowers. I mean it, a lot.
I don't want it to look like,
you know, like...
like I didn't care because I do.
More than they'll ever know.
More than anyone.
Of course.
Rob liked lisianthus.
Didn't he, honey?
They're sort of halfway
between tulips and roses
except they have no thorns
and they're usually purple or white.
- They sound beautiful.
- Yeah, they are.
We'll take purple.
Shit!
OK, so, you...
What? You'll put him out there?
And then what?
- You could say a few words if you want.
- Oh, God.
"Hi, I'm Suzanne Wething.
"Some of you may have seen me kicking Rob
in the parking lot at Jen's wedding.
"Actually, he was already dead
from alcohol poisoning
"so you can just all stop
looking at me like that."
I don't think so.
What? It's no secret.
Paige knows. Your sisters know, don't they?
Daddy was a drunk.
What is it again? Waterbury what?
"Waterford W Collection
11-inch spire stem vase."
- Terry doesn't fuck around.
- No, when he registers, he registers.
Maybe we should get married.
So we can have people going on
vase-buying errands for us?
No. So, we can say all those
"forevers" and "no matter whats".
You're in my will, I'm in yours,
we basically are married,
even if the law refuses to recognise it.
But I refuse to recognise the Bush
administration so I guess it evens out.
Just some sort of ceremony
in front of family and friends
would make it more real.
I don't think now's the time
to go into event-planning mode.
- Why?
- All the shit you've been through lately.
I just don't think it's the perfect time.
It never is. Sometimes you just have to
pick a moment and do it, right?
Like Nate moving in with Brenda
and taking Maya with him?
- If you ask me, that's crazy.
- You think?
Well, fast.
Life's so short.
I don't know what fast is any more.
Here it is.
$225? They're not getting this from us.
Yes, they are, just bite the bullet.
Right here, a garlic press for 30 bucks.
You want to be the guys
who gave them the garlic press?
They'll use a garlic press
way more than they'll use a $225 vase.
No.
Jesus.
I'm home.
- Hello?
- Hi, I wanna see my kids.
- When?
- Today.
- What time?
- Five. No, wait.
Shit.
Let me drive them to karate tomorrow
and then I'll take them to lunch.
You can't, we carpool with the Koehlers.
It messes everything up.
Vanessa, you can't keep me
from seeing my kids.
I'm not trying to keep you
from seeing your kids.
Why don't you come over tomorrow
and play with them?
- At the house?
- Yes, that would be better.
I'll be there at two.
So, like, from two to four?
Make it three to five
just to make sure we're back.
OK, see you then.
And I was...
hauling this box of meteorites
out to the car and I...
I thought,
"Jesus, God,
"look at yourself moving
these goddamn rocks again.
"How many times are you gonna do this?"
We're supposed to stay together
because you don't wanna move your rocks?
No.
We should stay together
because we love each other.
I love you, anyway.
I do.
I love you too, George.
But this is my thought here,
if you're going to be my husband
and I'm gonna be your wife,
it will have to be, it can only be,
if some conditions are met.
Shoot.
Mainly, that you behave like a husband.
And to me that means sharing yourself.
I don't wanna have to feel bad
every time I ask you a question.
- All right.
- And I want a healthy,
continuous flow of family around here.
Like making a space for Kyle and Becky.
- Becky?
- My friend from the fabric shop.
I set them up.
- Don't be mad.
- I'm not mad.
Not to mention your other children,
Brian and Maggie.
I haven't even met them yet.
All right, you'll meet them.
And I need to feel like
you like me again.
You're my favourite person.
You don't make me feel like
your favourite person.
Look...
I'll try.
I will, I mean it.
I'll...
I'll try.
You poor thing.
Yes, we'll be at the Black Forest Inn.
Yeah.
11:10 in the morning.
No, 1170 is our flight number.
How could we land at 11:70?
Yeah, I was kidding too.
All right, thanks. Bye.
- Secret, you could write...
- The guy is such a knob.
I'll take you guys to the airport.
- You know what?
- Orange.
I've got a better idea,
why don't you come with us?
No, I don't think so.
You don't have to come to the ceremony.
Just come to ldaho.
I really think I'd be in the way.
Well, I really think it would actually make
the whole thing liveable for me,
having it be the three of us.
- You really want me to come?
- I asked you, didn't I?
Come on.
Byron. I can't.
I have an appointment with Byron tomorrow.
I think Byron will be fine
if he misses a session.
- You've only been seeing him for a month.
- Exactly.
It's too soon to leave him by himself
in the middle of reality.
What about my reality?
- Come dance with me.
- This should be illegal.
- What?
- This should be illegal!
- What should be illegal?
- People trying to get other people to dance.
You're right.
- What the fuck, Claire!
- What?
What are you doing?
I just...
You just look so fucking beautiful tonight.
Do I? Wow, that must make it
so hard for everybody.
High much?
Why are you being such a fucking bitch?
The world's not your own private
fucking chemistry set, Claire.
Just stay away from me.
Leave me the fuck alone.
Yeah. Thanks.
No, I already have the number.
Thanks.
Barb called, left a message. There's some
barbecue at Peg and Ed's in an hour.
I should have told them
I was coming tomorrow morning.
They want you to go over now?
Like in an hour.
I'm just gonna call and say I can't make it.
- No, I'll get it.
- I was gonna pass it to you.
Just... You know,
I'll just let them leave a message.
Answer it. I'll be quiet!
- I'm just gonna check the message.
- Whatever.
You should go to the barbecue.
- Yeah, I don't know.
- They just wanna see Maya.
I'll be all right. I got a bunch of work to do.
Hi, do you have a message for room 13?
It's for you.
Hello?
No. But I know how to spell it.
Just the number.
Thank you.
Byron.
Now, Terry, repeat after me.
I, Terry, take you, Paul.
I, Terry, take you, Paul...
To be my lifetime partner, lover and friend.
To be my lifetime partner,
lover and friend...
Cut it out.
- Cut it out.
- I'm sorry.
Don't get me started.
In sickness and in health.
In sickness and in health...
In times of plenty and times of want.
In times of plenty
and times of want.
Until death do us part.
God, you scared the living crap out of me!
What are you doing here?
Anita and I crashed here.
She left early this morning.
But I fell into a K-hole last night
and I'm climbing out right now.
Who had K last night?
I don't know.
- How was it, fun?
- I don't know.
I might have been raped
and I'll only recover the memory
under intense hypnosis ten years from now.
That's cool.
Mom?
- Tender.
- I can't find it.
- Did you look in the garage?
- Excuse me?
This meat is so tender.
- I think we got the marinade right, Ed.
- It's great.
Was it hard for you and Maya
to find the time to get away?
You didn't have anything else going on?
Nothing as important as this.
It's been hard lately.
You think you finally get to
the bottom of the feelings
and then there are more.
Yeah.
OK, Byron, just tell me what's going on.
- I'm on a bridge.
- Where?
Los Feliz. I'm sitting on a ledge.
Byron, you need to get down
off that ledge right now.
There are so many cars
and each one of them
has someone inside driving.
And all those people, they all feel things
every bit as deeply as you and I do.
Byron, I want you to do something for me.
I'd like you to do something for me, too.
I'd like you to honour your commitments
but that's not something
you think you should do.
I'm sorry, I had a family matter come up.
- I needed to attend to it.
- Are you married?
That's not really relevant to the work
we're doing together.
Was it something really important
or did you just blow me off?
I rescheduled with you. I left...
You left a message telling me
when you would be available!
- In an emergency...
- I am having an emergency!
Byron, please get off the bridge.
You're the one who wanted me
to cross the bridge!
Yes, and now I'd like you to get off the bridge
so that we can continue
our work together, OK?
Our work together is important.
I'm not on a bridge.
Where are you?
I am in my living room.
Why can I hear traffic?
It's just my air conditioner.
See? I was just pretending.
Byron, that was very dishonest of you.
If you do anything like that ever again,
I'll have to stop seeing you,
do you understand?
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
Good, I'm gonna hang up now.
OK, goodbye.
Say cheese, Maya.
That was a good one, good job!
Kick it back. Can you kick it back?
Uncle Nate, did you ever give David Stiff?
- What?
- The book I gave you to give to him
when we took Maya to Legoland?
Oh, yeah. I didn't, I'm sorry.
I completely spaced.
But...
but you know,
I can see right where it is in my head
so when I get back, I'll give it to him.
You could read it, too. It's very informative.
Maybe I'll do that.
- You look tired.
- I am.
If you want to go back to the inn,
Maya can play with the kids.
Hoyt said something about
roasting marshmallows.
- Careful, you guys.
- Dad, we're just havin' fun, aren't we?
Why don't you go back and get some
alone-time and we'll bring Maya back?
We're, like, five minutes from Main Street.
She'll be fine. It's family.
All right.
Just give me a call
when you pull up outside.
- Sure.
- Look at the camera, Maya.
Look at me and give me a big smile.
Yeah!
Man, you won again!
You should go on the pro tour, buddy.
- Look at you.
- Yeah.
- Julio finished all of his homework.
- That's good.
- Who's coming over?
- You remember Kenny Simms?
- From high school?
- Hi. Come on in.
- How are you?
- I'm great.
- You look great.
- Thank you.
Am I... I'm not early, am I?
No.
Well, I guess I'll go.
All right, guys.
See you soon.
- Bye, Daddy.
- Bye.
I'm sorry if I came at a bad time.
No, you didn't do anything, no.
- It's all good.
- OK.
Your little boy is so cute.
Thanks.
- Is he...
- Adopted?
Yeah, about a year and a half ago,
from Guatemala.
My partner and I have
had, like, you know,
the most preliminary of
adoption conversations.
- Which agency did you use?
- Whole Family Center.
They're good people and they've got strong
connections in Guatemala
with the bureaucracy, which is great.
But they're kind of religious,
if you know what I mean?
I think so.
They don't work with gay couples so...
You might wanna try Rainbow Kids
or some place like that.
- Thanks for the tip.
- Sure.
You came back!
Where's Maya?
She's playing with her cousins
for a couple hours.
Miss me?
No, I was too busy having
a totally surreal phone session with my client.
Yeah, what happened?
I can't tell you, you know that.
Come on, how much do I unload on you
about the freaky people
I deal with at work?
- This is different.
- Not really.
Yeah, really.
Yeah, this is the whole, you know,
client-privilege doctor thing.
- Yeah.
- It's very professional.
How do I know
this client exists anyway?
How do I know this isn't some hot guy
you've got on the side?
- I was kidding.
- I know.
- I'm not really worried...
I wouldn't have moved in if I was worried.
You know, this is...
like the first time we've been together.
What do you mean?
The other times,
we never really had a relationship.
One of us was always escaping or lying...
- Or stoned.
- Or something.
Yeah.
Now, we're really here.
I drove back here to tell you I love you,
that I miss you
and...
To make sure I didn't escape?
Oh, yeah.
This one's cool.
- If you like nostrils.
- Claire.
No, I can't have this kind of documentation
of my nose just lying around.
Maybe if I just rip out my nose.
There. That's better.
- Nostrilly goodness.
- Stop.
You're an idiot. Stop, stop it.
I'm so much happier when I'm high.
I got your eyes.
That's so scary.
I wish you could see this.
Well, get my camera.
It's right over there.
- How's the light in here?
- Good, we're good.
Yeah.
If you pucker up.
The problem is not nuclear war.
The problem is
what's gonna cause nuclear war.
I don't see us living through
a nuclear war, George.
Of course not.
Not a whole lot of people will.
I mean, in our lifetime.
I don't see it happening.
I married the glass-is-half-full girl.
Which time?
This time. Of course, yes.
What was I thinking?
This decaf is so cinnamony.
Isn't it?
I think when the next A-bomb is launched,
it'll be over God.
- Whose?
- Exactly.
The fundamentalists,
lslamic, Christian and otherwise
will all conspire to end the world the way
their holy books said it would -
with a big war.
But all those theologies have a message
of hope and brotherly love too,
to counterbalance the irresistible force
of self-fulfilling prophecy.
- Whereas corporatism...
- We know, Dad.
You think it'll all be about oil,
just like everything else. Oil.
Close.
Water.
The apocalypse will be over water -
who has it, who wants it
and what they're willing to do to get it.
But global warming, isn't it...
I thought that's supposed
to melt the glaciers or something.
If you like salty water,
I guess that's good news.
But what about rising sea levels or
the disruption of the thermal-haline conveyor?
That's the Gulf Stream.
Have you checked out the Pentagon
report on the Guardian website?
No.
- You have a computer here?
- Sure, downstairs in the office.
- We're done, right?
- I think so.
You have to see this.
So show me.
This stuff was actually published by
the Pentagon and it basically says
anywhere between
two and 20 years from now, kablooey!
- Kyle loves online.
- George, too.
It's absurd! The idea that
there are kids waiting for homes
and people still have the nerve to say
who's good enough and who isn't
based on are you gay or not?
People are stupid. What a shock.
There's nothing in here but fuckin' eggs.
Yeah, I'm sorry,
I thought we needed them and we didn't.
- Twice.
- What's this?
Oh, God, just throw that away.
Trust me, don't even wash it out.
I think we might have
some Rice-a-Roni in here or something.
- Oh, my God.
- What is it?
It's a Chinese baby!
- What's it doing in the cupboard?
- Someone must have left her here for us.
- Who?
- I don't know, someone Chinese.
What?
Couscous.
It's all we've got.
What are you doing? It's past midnight.
It's fucking unbelievable.
When you have all this information
in front of you,
it's a wonder anyone can
get up in the morning.
No one's getting up in the morning
at this rate. Come to bed.
In a minute.
Take a look at this site.
The graphic is a little simplistic.
It was obviously designed for the layman.
But you can literally watch
the world's potable water supply
dripping away moment by moment.
But that's just some people's opinion.
It's not an opinion. It's a scientific hypothesis.
But let's just say they're half-right,
which chances are they are,
but even if they're only half-right,
we're not doing any of the things
we should be doing
in order to prevent it,
much less reverse it.
But it's all so pessimistic.
If it happens, we'll die.
But in the meantime, can't we be happy?
- Happy?
- Yes, happiness!
Don't you remember happiness?
Ruth, I'm crawling
my way to comfortable.
I can't even think about being happy
unless I'm doing something
to help save this planet
or at least prepare myself and my loved ones
for whatever it is that's next.
We're talking about the end of
life as we know it here.
- But you're obsessing about these...
- I don't think I'm obsessing.
Well, you're down here
instead of sleeping,
dreaming good dreams.
Come to bed.
All right.
I'll come to bed.
Come to bed.
Lisa is here with us
right now.
Not in this urn but in all of us.
Each of us here today,
especially little Maya,
shares a part in carrying
Lisa's eternal life
into the future.
May this dedication
of Lisa's humble ashes today
be for all of us a reawakening
to the sparkling and still vivid ways
her spirit continues to live,
grow and flourish
in the lives of those she loved.
Let us pray.
Our Parent,
who art in heaven,
hallowed be Thy name...
Stop it.
I want the crying to stop now.
I want it to stop.
This is hard for Mommy, too.
We are not leaving here until this stops.
Hallie, do you wanna go to
the Cheesecake Factory or don't you?
We are not leaving here until this stops.
Do you understand me? We're not.
- Excuse me.
- What do you want?
- She's lost her father.
- Shut up!
You shut up!
This is none of your business.
See, she's fine. Aren't you, Hallie?
You sure you two don't have time
to get coffee or anything?
No, we gotta get packed up and stuff
but thanks.
- Yeah, you sure?
- Yeah. She won't sleep on the plane.
So I'm gonna make sure
she takes a little nap first.
All right, then.
Bye, Maya. We love you.
Good to see you.
Say goodbye to your cousin.
- Bye.
- Keep in touch, OK?
We will. Bye.
Call us when you get there.
You should ring the bell.
The boys at school?
Yes, but it's scary when someone
just starts coming in.
You should ring the bell.
- Someone?
- Shouldn't you be at work?
- Isn't anybody dead?
- I told them I had an appointment.
I have a problem with you
bringing Kenny Simms over here
and parading him in front of my boys.
- Really?
- Yes. It'll confuse them.
It'll confuse them that an old friend from school
comes to visit me? He's my friend.
Bullshit!
You're looking, Vanessa, OK?
You're out there on the market.
You're dating, it's gonna freak out the boys.
- Look at you.
- Look at me what?
You straightened out your hair.
You don't even look like you.
I blew my hair dry, OK?
I'm a grown woman, separated from...
When did we decide we were separated?
The day you left, Rico!
You don't live here any more.
Give me the keys
or make me go to the expense
of changing the locks.
But you don't live here any more
and you can't tell me shit!
And next time you come over,
why don't you goddamn tell me first?
Should I get this to go for the car?
I'll get a straw. A straw's good, right?
- You like straws?
- Straws help.
I'll get you a straw.
Hey, guys! I didn't expect to see you.
Hey, it's Aunt Barb.
What a surprise!
I thought she was gonna take a nap!
Well...
chocolate muffin, you know?
We're just hanging out having a muffin.
Kids...
Barb, this is my friend Brenda.
- Hi.
- And, Brenda, this is Barb.
- Lisa's sister.
- Of course, I see it.
- Brenda Chenowith?
- Yeah.
I know your name.
Lisa mentioned it to me.
- So you two are...
- We were.
- Before Lisa.
- Yeah, we...
Way back when Lisa came to LA
and told me she was...
Yeah. She told me all about it.
Well, it's so nice to meet you.
I had no idea that you were here.
Well, we came up here together,
we all travelled together,
but we decided that
the ceremony wouldn't be...
Of course not. No.
But how nice that
you have someone to join you
and be with you for everything.
Look, Maya, I got you a cup
for the car with a straw.
Well, I will let you guys
get back to your meal.
- I know you have a big trip coming up.
- Yeah, we do.
- Two planes.
- Yeah, two planes.
Well, travel safely.
Bye, honey pie, baby pie.
Bye.
- It was nice to have met you.
- And you.
Thanks.
- Bye now.
- Bye.
- Small town.
- Yeah.
- The chemicals get to you after a while.
When I went to school here,
there were lines down the hall,
people waiting to get in, develop their shit,
people sleeping in here even.
Now, every time...
Every time I come in here, it's empty.
Yeah, fucking digital.
Is it weird for you
to have me in your class?
Ls it weird for you to be in my class?
Weird in a good way.
You know, sometimes
when you're strutting around up there,
pointing at shit,
I just kind of stop
hearing what you're talking about
and like, stare at your legs
cos they're really long.
My legs are long?
Yeah, you're all tall.
Do you like ceviche?
- I love it.
- You wanna go to Siete Mares after this?
They have the most perfect, perfect ceviche.
I'm kind of getting addicted to spicy stuff.
Like if it doesn't hurt a little,
it's not worth eating.
I'm familiar with that dynamic.
So let's get some.
I'm almost done here.
- That's interesting.
- Isn't it?
Just the name, Rainbow Kids,
it's so fucking condescending.
David, let it go.
Another spicy tuna handroll.
And put jalapeno in this time, sliced.
I'm gonna run to the washroom.
- I'll get the check.
- Yeah, I'm done.
And more ginger, too.
Please.
Excuse me, did you say something?
What did you just say?
- Nothing.
- Bullshit, you said something. What?
I said, "Please."
- To me?
- No, for you. Somebody had to.
Who the fuck do you think you are?
Seriously.
I think I'm a member of the human race
which makes me want
to treat my fellow humans
with a certain amount of respect.
That's who I think I am.
Seriously.
Jesus! Get off me!
What the fuck?
Get the fuck off me!
- You fuckin' bit me!
- What the hell are you on?
You tore my earring out, you cunt.
What the fuck's the matter with you?
Holy shit.
Damn it!
I really do hate to bother you folks.
It's no bother at all, Stan.
It's just been something I couldn't get off
of my mind after the service today.
What is it?
Well, when I was transferring
the ashes into the urn,
I couldn't help but notice
there were a lot of...
bone fragments.
It's the kind of thing you see
in much, much older cremains.
You hardly ever see that now.
Technology's improved so much.
Now, I could be wrong,
but the ashes that we interred...
Just say it.
I don't think they're Lisa's.
Ladies and gentlemen, at this time
we will begin our descent into Los Angeles.
Please return your seats and tray tables
to their upright and locked positions.
We'll also be coming through
the cabin one more time
in case you have anything
remaining to discard.
Here we go.
English