- Shit.
- Oh, I know!
You went a little "Showgirls" on me there.
Not that I'm complaining.
Happy anniversary, baby.
- Same time next year?
- You kidding? I got needs.
I'd better wake up in the morning
with you all over me.
I hope you don't think I'm waiting till morning.
Let's go shower.
Give me a minute.
- This feels too nice.
- Just don't cook yourself.
Honey?
Annie, you OK?
Annie?
Annie? Annie!
Oh, my God! Annie!
I'm gonna miss you. This is the first time
we've been apart for any length of time.
- Not that long.
- Keith, three months is a long time.
David, we were split up for eight months.
We weathered that.
You're gonna get hit on
by really hot guys in every city.
It's been OK for us to have an occasional
random fuck here. What'll be so different?
You'll meet some cooler, smarter, hotter guy
who's a lot easier to get along with than I am.
- I could do that here.
- That makes me feel a lot better.
We'll be able to buy a fucking house
with the money I make
with a pool, a hot tub and a steam shower.
- And room for kids.
- Yeah.
All of which you'll be sharing with the cooler,
smarter, hotter guy you'll meet on tour.
Don't you know I ain't looking?
I'm settled down. I've found what I want.
Besides, this'll be good for us.
- How will this be good?
- It'll show you you don't have to worry.
Come on, David, what does it take?
Don't be so insecure. I love you.
I'm not insecure.
- If you want me not to do anything, just ask.
- Really?
Yeah, as long as you don't do anything either.
- Be safe.
- Course I'm gonna be safe.
- I'm safe with everybody but you.
- Extra safe.
- Even with blow jobs, use a condom.
- Did you use a condom with that plumber?
No, but that was different. We hadn't made up
rules. No sex with anybody more than once.
- We'll see about that.
- Keith...
David.
- There's my car. How do I look?
- So fucking hot, it's ridiculous.
I'm gonna miss you.
- I feel like I'm gonna cry.
- So cry.
- Call me every night.
- OK.
- Starting tonight.
- All right, I will.
All right, bitch, calm down!
Bush just lies and no one cares.
Nate, you got fuckin' oatmeal on my print!
I don't believe this.
- Hey, not in front of Maya, OK?
- Asshole.
- This is really important to me.
- Yes, they're for Claire's crit.
Mom, don't say "crit".
It sounds weird coming from you.
- Are you trying to be a model or something?
- No, I'm not selling anything.
You should try to figure out how to sell out
to the highest bidder as fast as you can
before your life just totally blows up
in your face, because it will.
- It just doesn't stop, does it?
- It gets better, but it never goes away, no.
- Maybe you should try to meet someone new.
- Mom, I don't want to meet... What, date?
- I don't want to be with anybody right now.
- Even if it's just sex, then.
- Sex can be very healing.
- It's OK for us to be celibate if we want to.
- Thank you, Claire.
- Then maybe you should get a job.
I've been trying. It's not easy these days.
- Who's supposed to take care of Maya?
- Us, her family.
I think it's best if I look after my daughter,
thank you.
Don't you think what's best for Maya
is to have a healthy father?
Mom, all I do is think about
what's best for Maya, OK?
A bereavement group?
I was a grief counsellor for three years.
I know what a load of crap this is.
It actually helps to spend time with others
going through the same experience.
- Then why didn't you go when Dad died?
- I did.
- You didn't tell us that.
- I went once a week for several months.
- One of us could have gone with you.
- It would have been wrong to burden you.
Maybe I could have used it, too.
Why is this family so repressed?
I can tell you from experience.
You won't wake up one morning
and find it's all over. You have to grieve.
I know that. I have grieved.
I've done big grieving, OK?
I just feel like I'm...
stuck in this quicksand and
something bigger than me is holding me back.
It just doesn't make sense.
Something as stupid as that.
Falling in the shower.
It was my fault.
No. No, of course not. It was an accident.
No, I dragged her out to the hot tub,
made her drink tequila,
got her all dizzy.
- It was our anniversary.
- Mr Thornton...
I think your wife was very much in love
and did all those things
because she enjoyed doing them with you.
Why did this happen?
Out of nowhere, for no reason?
I was a good husband.
I loved her. I took care of her.
Why is God punishing me?
I don't think God punishes people like that,
Mr Thornton.
No, of course not.
- Hello, Ruth.
- Hello, Becky.
- Pyjamas?
- Hard to get them long enough for George.
- He's such a large man.
- Nothing wrong with that.
No, no, I'm not complaining.
How are things with Hakim?
- He got back together with his wife.
- Oh, no!
Yeah, I guess I was just a pretty toy to him.
$22.40.
- I'm so sorry.
- I'm not.
I left a bag of burning dog shit on his porch
as a little parting gift. Movin' on.
You know, George has a son.
- He got a job?
- I believe he's independently wealthy.
- What's his name?
- Kyle. He's about 40, rather boyish.
Does he have a moustache? I like them.
- No, but I believe he's capable of growing one.
- Why is he still single?
- He's a very complex man.
- I like a man who can keep me guessing.
Maybe I'll have you both over for dinner.
I'll call you.
Shall we start? Anyone?
They remind me
of Katy Grannan's earlier work.
Yes, they certainly do.
I like them.
They're really simple, unpretentious, pretty.
Like Claire herself.
I wonder though...
if they're a little too staged.
Maybe.
Are they staged, Claire?
Well, yeah.
It's hard to take a candid self-portrait.
Not just staged, but...stagy.
And maybe they're a little stiff.
Dead.
That's what I like about them.
This girl who's, like, dead
and beyond everything.
Beyond hunger, beyond sex, beyond boredom.
And, really, it's so beautiful to be in that state.
Like, nothing can reach her.
Nothing can get to her.
- See, I wouldn't say dead, I would say empty.
- Yeah, definitely empty.
- Was that your intention, Claire?
- No.
I was trying to capture the stillness
I sometimes feel.
Really? Not emptiness, apathy?
No. Stillness.
OK, what are you doing in this picture?
Nothing. Being still.
What are you looking at?
What are you thinking?
- Nothing.
- OK.
I thought you were actually thinking
something deep.
OK, let me ask you this,
and feel free to roll your eyes,
but do you really want to perpetuate
the idea of woman as a vacant vessel?
Ls this more lesbian stuff?
Yes. I have to meet my quota
so I get my toaster oven.
I'm not trying to perpetuate anything.
I don't have an agenda.
- I shoot from a more instinctual place.
- An empty place?
- I'm not empty!
- No, of course not.
Maybe with your next work, we can see
something that actually is inside you.
- May I help you?
- Oh, I'm just looking for Rico.
Federico?
Rico Rico.
- Hello.
- Hey, it's me.
God, I'm glad you called.
I hated the way we left things this morning.
- How did we leave things?
- Awkward.
I was just calling to remind you
to pay the cable bill. I left it on my desk.
OK.
- So how's it going?
- It's great. Got our own sushi chef.
I'm eating yellowtail.
It's out of this fucking world.
I'm drinking lukewarm coffee
and driving a body back to the funeral home.
I'm having an awful day.
- Why?
- The way you left seemed so... "Whatever."
Honey, forget it. You're just feeling needy.
"Honey"? When do you ever call me honey?
You don't want them to know you're
talking to a guy? Jesus. Just call me Darlene.
- I gotta go. They're starting a movie.
- What movie?
Some Japanese horror flick they want
Celeste to do the remake of. I love you.
Gotta go.
Rico!
What are you doing here?
Obviously you weren't gonna
come to see me.
Come on, Maria's watching Nicole today.
Let's go to Magic Mountain.
- Are you stoned?
- So? I don't have to work today.
You can't come in here stoned.
You can't come in at all.
- You don't like me any more?
- Of course I like you. It's just...you know.
I want you to take me to dinner.
I got a new dress.
- It's very short.
- No.
Sophia, no. Sophia, no!
You got the wrong idea.
I spent all day alone yesterday.
I was so sad.
I cried, like, three times.
I miss you.
You're important to me, Rico.
You make my life better.
- Whoa, Sophia...
- I'm sorry if I did something wrong, but...
- No, you didn't do anything wrong, it's just...
- I can't help it that I like you.
You're the best thing
that ever happened to me.
I guess I should go.
Maybe I can get off early tonight.
- Sorry.
- No, you're not interrupting anything.
Sophia Morales, this is Nate Fisher.
- Nice to meet you.
- You, too.
Do you need anything?
I was just gonna play some Doom.
- Pick me up at seven.
- OK, OK.
It's not what you think.
Rico, I don't care.
..studios in Los Angeles. This is...
..patrolling for petroll
..more than in any other land.
No wonder about 40...
- I can't believe someone stopped.
- What's wrong?
I ran out of gas. I know, so lame.
- No. It's happened to all of us at least once.
- I'm supposed to help my grandma today.
She broke her hip and can't make it upstairs.
I told her I'd move her bed down into the den.
I know she's just sitting there waiting for me.
I'm sorry, it's just one of those days.
I know what that's like.
Any chance you could give me a lift
to the next gas station?
I wouldn't even ask, I just...
I don't know what else to do.
- Sure, get in.
- Thank you so much.
- I'm Jake.
- David.
David, you just saved my life.
This is so much fun.
I haven't been on a campus in years.
Hi.
Let's wrap him up and take him home!
- Now what?
- You're being wildly inappropriate, as usual.
And, as usual,
I am feeling irritated and resentful.
Well, that's your shit.
- Is Richard Braun teaching here?
- Yeah, my Cognitive Psych class.
You don't believe in all that cognitive crap,
do you?
You have to dig through the past.
Knowing where behaviour comes from
doesn't change the behaviour.
You just know where the behaviour
comes from.
Ricky Braun has the most unusually
shiny penis. I went on this retreat with him.
When he'd get out of the hot tub,
the water would just bead up on his schlong.
- Do you suppose he kept it oiled?
- I don't care, Mom. He's a good teacher.
He's an exhibitionist and an idiot.
Maybe you should teach the class.
Here? No thank you, darling,
I'm not that desperate.
This happens to be an excellent program.
It doesn't matter where you do your training.
You'll be a great therapist.
You really have this uncanny understanding
of interpersonal dynamics,
which you've always had.
You have a problem applying the principles
to your own life. So often the case.
- I was wondering when the insult would come.
- We're exactly the same.
Who's a bigger train wreck than I?
So how's it going with Olivier?
He's a very passionate man. He's a lot of fun
if you don't take him too seriously.
He is completely supportive of my decision
to have vaginal rejuvenation surgery.
Oh, Mom!
Darling, I've had a couple of children.
You, especially, took your toll.
No one wants to fuck a glass of water,
if you know what I'm saying.
Speaking of children,
are you still interested in having one?
- I think so.
- You think so?
And is Joe the man
you want to have them with?
- I think he is, yeah.
- You think he is?
How's the sex?
It's fine.
It's creative. It's interesting.
Dear God, you have to dump him.
Mom, when I brought him to dinner,
you said he was the one.
I didn't realise at the time that the sex between
the two of you was this cerebral exercise.
That's not good. Sex is something you should
feel, not something you should think.
I think to keep from behaving
in a compulsive and destructive manner,
thanks to my early exposure
to compulsive and destructive sexual energy.
You just said that poring over the past
is not important.
- Change the behaviour.
- I have changed the behaviour.
Then what are you complaining about?
This is probably the healthiest relationship
that I have ever been in.
I'm not gonna dump him.
As a matter of fact,
we're talking about moving in together.
Now, that's the Brenda I know.
I hate your new hair.
I could feel the gentle rocking of the train
as we started to move.
And he was so handsome,
sitting there against the window smiling at me.
When I woke up, I could hardly believe
I was this old lady in bed all by myself.
And what's odd is
I had completely forgotten about that trip.
It was so long ago.
I have so many memories
of my time with Walter,
I can't even remember them all.
Memories are nice, aren't they, Ellen?
- Their ATM is down.
- Really?
I got no cash so I tried to use my credit card
to get a gas can and a couple gallons of gas.
I'm way over my limit so he wouldn't take it.
I begged him, please,
and he laughs in my face.
- How humiliating is that?
- Sorry.
Man, I must have been a serious asshole
in a previous life.
I don't think it works that way.
Things just happen.
At least I stole a pack of gum.
- You stole that?
- I figured he deserved it.
Want a piece?
Now you're my accomplice.
- Oh, shit.
- What's wrong?
Poor Grandma's still waiting for me. I'd call her,
but she's deaf. She never hears the phone.
Let me buy the gas can and gas, OK?
- No way.
- Really, it's no big deal. I'm going to.
Only if you take me to an ATM
so I can pay you back.
OK.
An apple, some sharp cheddar,
and a hunk of crusty bread.
And somehow, it all tastes little bit better
when you cut it
with your grandfather's pocket knife.
I've been thinking
we should invite Kyle over for dinner.
- Why?
- So he can meet my friend Becky,
who's quite adorable in her own way
and quite single.
- Ruth, what are you doing?
- I'm trying to arrange a dinner.
I can make my vegetable lasagne.
And Becky said she...
- You're meddling.
- It's not meddling to introduce two people.
When one of them is my son
who leaves boxes of shit on our doorstep?
Oh, yes, that's meddling.
But don't you want to help him?
I only agreed to meet with him
because I wanted you to see first-hand
what a mess he is.
If I'd had any idea...
Christ.
Look...
just leave it alone, Ruth, OK?
You deal with your messed-up children
and I'll deal with mine.
I don't care for that tone.
I'm very disappointed in you, Ruth.
Very.
When you lose somebody you love,
you truly have lost a part of yourself.
You shared a lifetime with this person
so it's only natural to have moments
when you're feeling completely lost.
What if you haven't?
Well, if you don't feel lost...
I didn't get to share a lifetime with her.
I'm sorry, I've been listening
to your stories and they're...
They're upsetting because I don't have that.
I don't have a lifetime of memories.
We were just getting started.
Just working things through.
And...
now I have a...
I have a two-year-old daughter
who doesn't have a mother and so she...
she has to get everything from me
because I'm all there is, but I don't...
I don't know what to do with that.
Most of the time, I just...
I just feel numb.
And then sometimes I feel just...just terrified.
Then sometimes, I just feel so angry,
but then I don't want to be this bitter guy
so I try to deal with it because I don't want
my daughter to have to live with that poison.
I try and be thankful.
I try so hard to be thankful.
And I am thankful. Thankful I have
a beautiful child that Lisa gave me.
Yet some days, some days I just feel like I'm
going crazy, like I'm literally losing my mind...
- That's the fire alarm.
- It's probably just a false alarm.
But just to be safe, we're gonna walk down
the hallway and out into the parking lot.
- Is everyone ready?
- I've never heard that before.
Thanks for the gas, man.
Well, this is one incredibly shitty day for me,
but you are, like,
the coolest guy I ever met, David.
Now we just gotta hit that ATM.
They're usually all over.
- Do you want some water?
- No, thanks.
Are you gay?
- Yes.
- I thought so. You look gay.
No, I mean you could be.
I was hoping you were gay.
I mean, I figure you have a boyfriend.
You're too cute not to.
But what if I could be your guy on the side,
who understands you
and loves you unconditionally
and pretty much lives just to please you?
You want me to take my pants off?
Hello? Do you want some water or not?
Oh, no, thanks, I'm fine.
- Dude, where did you go?
- I'm a little preoccupied.
I'm having one of those days, too.
Well, hey, say no more.
I smell smoke. Anyone else smell smoke?
OK, everyone, false alarm.
We can all go back in.
- So did you grow up in LA?
- Yeah, one of the rare natives.
- What about you?
- I was born in St George, Bermuda.
- Wow.
- Not as exciting as it sounds.
- It was the naval air station.
- Your dad was in the navy?
At first. Then he worked for a food service
company that supplied the navy.
I used to fantasise about running away
and joining the navy.
I pictured myself walking down the gangway in
my uniform like Gene Kelly in On The Town.
Who?
Never mind.
The navy sucks. When I was little, as soon as
I'd make friends, my dad would have to move.
So I was always the new kid.
Yeah, I know how that feels. I was never
the new kid. I was just the odd kid.
I think there's one in there.
- What?
- ATM.
Oh, cool.
Hey.
OK, we walk in there, you get as much cash
as you can with your ATM card.
If you try anything,
if you even breathe in a way that I don't like,
I will shoot you in the spine.
Understand?
Not 300, 500.
- I don't think you can withdraw 500.
- Yeah, you can. Do it.
I don't even have 500 in my account.
- How much?
- Maybe four.
Do four.
Let's go.
Nice try.
Oh, wow, I really hit you hard, didn't I?
- Yeah.
- I'm sorry, bro. It just...
It felt so fucking good! I didn't even know I was
gonna do that. I just fucking... I just did it.
- You got your money, just leave me alone.
- Don't be angry. Come on, get in the van.
- I'm not going anywhere with you.
- You're not dumping me after our first fight?
We're best friends forever. Get in the van
before I kick your motherfucking ass.
Let's go, cowboy.
- Where?
- That way.
Hey.
Wipe your face.
Do you want me to take you back to your car?
I don't have a car.
Where I picked you up.
That wasn't my car. I don't have a car.
Where would I get a car?
So...
where am I taking you?
Well, it's definitely party time. There are these
guys I know in Long Beach that deal meth.
Have fun all tweak-end long, you know?
No, we'll do it old school tonight. MacArthur
Park. Head on down to the crack gallery.
Oh, Jesus.
- You can just take the van.
- No, I'm drinking. You have to drive.
Friends don't let friends drive drunk.
- How do I get there?
- Just head towards downtown.
- No, what are you doing?
- Getting on the freeway.
No, stay off the fucking freeway!
Just get on Alvarado.
- OK, calm down!
- I don't like the freeway.
I had an accident on the freeway.
My father was killed right after we moved here.
- Sorry.
- On the way to a Dodger game.
We were just talking, and bam,
he ploughed into the back of this truck.
I'm really sorry.
When the car finally stopped moving,
he just...wasn't there any more.
What happened?
He went through the windshield.
He never wore his seatbelt.
It was his little "fuck you" to the world.
I lost my father in a car accident, too.
He was hit by a bus.
How old were you?
It was just three years ago.
Fuck you! That's not the same!
I was ten years old.
- Jesus, man, you fart?
- No.
Yeah, you did! Holy fucking Christ!
- It was the body.
- What?
- The body, it's releasing gas.
- What the fuck is that?
It's a body. I'm a funeral director.
I was taking it home when I picked you up.
Fuck, fuck! Get it out of here!
Stop the fucking van! Stop the fucking van!
Oh, Jesus, it's a chick.
Hey, you wanna fuck her?
I was kidding!
Oh, shit, you should see your face!
- What do you want?
- To get her the fuck out of my van.
Jesus, that is a person!
That's somebody's wife!
If she was always farting like that,
he must be happy to be rid of her.
God, that is disgusting.
Let's go.
I said, let's go!
Man, you got any Lysol?
- I can still smell her farts.
- No.
Pull in there.
Get in the back.
Lay down.
On your stomach.
You think we're gonna make out, faggot?
Give me your hands.
- Is that too tight?
- Yes.
Tough shit. I don't want you going anywhere.
I like you.
Oh, bitch.
That was so great. Your fucking cell phone!
You are so lame.
Oh, my God!
You poor thing.
You thought you were so fucking rescued.
All gone. Cops go bye-bye.
Now say you're sorry
for running away from me.
Say you're fucking sorry, pussy.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
God, I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
So...
are you really a mortician?
A funeral director.
- Man, that is so sick.
- There's nothing sick about it.
What's sick was leaving that woman
in the middle of the road.
Imagine the guy who finds her.
"What have we got here? A bag of gold?"
"It's some dead cunt!"
Come on, that's funny.
It's not funny.
What if that was someone you cared about?
- Like who?
- Like someone in your family.
Why are you doing this to me? How can you
be this way? Because your father died?
You idiot. I made that up. He's not dead. He's
doing time somewhere in Washington state.
Then why? I need to understand
how you could do this to me, to anybody.
Don't you have any fucking sympathy
for me...at all?
How can you be so completely disconnected
from another human being?
Jesus, David.
What fucking difference does it make?
Let's just get high and have some fun.
Man, look at your face.
See, you could use some crack.
You ever done it before?
- No.
- Shit, I haven't done crack in a long time.
I think about it. Sometimes I walk by a car
right after the engine's been turned off
and it has that crack smell.
Fuck, this is gonna be great.
Come on, let's go find us a crack dealer.
Him?
Too freaky. There, the little juggler.
- What you want?
- A couple rocks. How much?
- 40 each.
- 40? Shit. Just give me one.
- You bought the drugs right out of his mouth?
- Yeah, we're close that way.
Hold on a second, let me enjoy this.
Up we go.
- No, thank you.
- Come on, it's good stuff.
- No.
- Or I could put a hole in your throat
and blow the smoke in that way.
OK.
There you go. Hold it. Hold it in.
Nice, huh?
Wow, yeah!
I am so fuckin' loving life right now.
My God, I've never felt like this.
How could I have never felt like this?
- Can you drive?
- Shit, I can do anything.
- Want to have sex?
- Are you serious?
Totally. I need to suck dick, man.
- I need someone to fuck me.
- OK.
Careful, I'm driving.
Jesus!
Give me all your fuckin' money, man, before
I beat your face in, shit-faced motherfuckers!
- Will he come after us?
- No way.
Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck.
Your windshield's busted.
I swear to God, you are such a fucking hero.
- Are you gonna let me go now?
- No.
Now you're gonna go and hurt my feelings?
Man, we're best friends for life.
- You said I saved your life.
- Just talk.
That's what you do with people like you -
say nice things so they feel better.
- That guy would have killed you!
- I don't think so.
I gave you money, you got high, there's
nothing else you want. Let's just end it.
No, no, no, we gotta go to Long Beach.
- What?
- I need some meth.
Yeah, well, there's definitely
some downsides to crack.
OK, look, just take me to Long Beach
and you're done.
Really?
Really.
- Do you even know where we are?
- Not exactly.
- Am I going the right way?
- I guess.
- How will I know when I get there?
- If you hit the ocean, you've gone too far.
- I just don't know where I am.
- It's a red house. Like a barn red.
- Should I start looking?
- Yeah, when we get closer, yeah.
- Hey, that's my dog.
- What?
That's my fucking dog. Wait, stop. Stop!
Roll down your window.
Hey, Charlie. Hey, Charlie!
Here, boy! Here, boy!
- How can that be your dog?
- I used to live around here. Follow him.
Follow him!
- I think he's gone.
- Keep going.
- Just get close.
- That's what I'm doing.
Yeah, but don't scare him.
- Help me catch him.
- I don't want to.
I don't wanna shoot you.
Get out and help me get my dog
and I will let you go.
- What about getting the meth?
- Just help me get my dog and I will let you go.
- Promise?
- I swear to fucking God.
- You're scaring him.
- He's gonna get away.
Charlie. Here, boy, I've got a cookie.
I've got a cookie for you.
Don't lie to my dog!
I got him, I got him.
Charlie, here, boy. Hey, boy. Hey, Charlie.
- That's not my dog.
- What?
That's not my dog. Let him go.
- Of course it's your dog.
- I know my own dog, stupid! Let him go!
Jesus, I ask you for one thing
and you can't even do that!
- Give me your wallet.
- What?
Give it.
So they can't identify your body right away.
That's right, you fucking faggot,
you are so dead.
We'll keep looking. I'll find your dog.
Jesus, he'd be, like, 30 years old now.
Fuck it. I'm through with you, man.
It's time to end this once and for all.
No! No!
You're gonna kill me with a rock?
Please!
What'll it be? Wanna go out in a blaze of glory
or should I just shoot you?
Please don't kill me. Please don't kill me.
Please don't kill me.
Suck it.
Put it in your mouth.
That's right.
You are so fucking pathetic.
- Close your eyes.
- No.
Close your fucking eyes
before I shoot them out.
English