I did.
No.
I swear, I was like majorly, intensely...
worked up like never before.
Trust me, that's so not it.
Quit looking at me like I'm the new zoo baby.
I did come.
Honey, there's no way.
I was there, remember?
There was no funny face, no funny noises.
You didn't melt
into a smoking little puddle of Claire...
yet.
- This sucks. What is wrong with me?
- Nothing.
We're just getting started.
- You wait and see, I'll make you scream.
- I hope so.
George, come to church with me.
Agnostics don't go to church, Ruth.
That's part of the appeal.
It would make me so happy
to be there with you.
Sweetheart, this is my day to catch up.
I've got a million things to do.
- It's only an hour.
- Then you won't miss me for long.
- Morning, all.
- Hey.
- Can I get you anything? How are you?
- Orange juice. I'm great.
Well, my stomach is burning a little.
Maybe too much coffee.
For goodness' sake, you need water.
Juice would produce more acid.
No bodies in the prep room. You think
death spared Los Angeles last night?
- Doubtful.
- What are you doing here?
I don't know.
I should be here in case we get a walk-in.
What's going on with you today?
I have to work and your mother's got the spirit.
- Would you like to come to church with me?
- Yes, I'd like that very much.
I'll be ready in a minute. Here, drink your water.
Last chance.
Pray for me.
- Hello.
- Rico.
You were such a lover last night. So good.
No, it was...
It was you.
Wait, what are you doing here?
It's late. You gotta go home.
Man, it's almost 11.
- Just tell your wife you fell asleep in the car.
- She threw me out.
- Shut up. For real?
- Yeah, for real.
I don't know who else she thinks is out there.
Give up a man like you?
She's fucked up.
I don't want to talk about her.
Hey, I could stay here for a while, right?
Sorry, baby, it's just that this apartment is
so small and my cousins visit all the time.
They have to sleep over.
No problem.
Love your enemy. Turn the other cheek.
What could be more simple or more difficult?
But these are the teachings at the living heart
of Christ's message to the world.
When Peter asked Jesus, "Lord, how oft
shall I forgive my brother? Seven times?"
Seems like a lot, doesn't it? Seven times.
But Jesus said to Peter, "Not seven times,
but seventy times seven."
Whoa. Do the math.
You stupid hypocrite!
No!
How does it feel?
So it is our daily mission
to find the Christ in ourselves
and forgive our enemies.
Heartburn.
It is forgiveness that eases our suffering.
Nice ride.
God damn it.
- What?
- Let's go away for a little while.
- Where do you want to go?
- North?
- We could leave tomorrow and...
- Can't. I'm scoring the new Jet Li movie.
Next couple days
so you're hardly gonna see me.
Oh, well.
Sorry.
Afterwards, maybe.
Cambria, Carmel, Monterey.
That'd work.
If you have no interest in the past
and don't read history,
how can you comprehend the present?
George, history is not what really happened.
History is some warmongering,
patriarchal idea of what happened.
- Who gives a shit about that?
- I hope I'm not interrupting.
- Anita thinks the study of fossils is futile.
- In my humble opinion.
- Dave, we're getting a body.
- Who? How? What?
- You've forgotten part of your outfit, Anita.
- I was gonna wear a T-shirt, but fuck it.
He was sitting in the driveway
in this mint '60s Lincoln
with a pre-need form from Dad
sitting right on top of the dash.
- Where is he now?
- At the coroner's, but he'll be back soon.
I thought your day
was filled with important activities.
- Always time for healthy debate.
- I'm right, you're wrong, game over.
- Rico's gonna work on him so you don't...
- I want to. I need to do something.
Hey, Mom, can you look after Maya
for a little while?
- OK.
- There you go. Thanks, Mom.
But everything we are is built on what
went before. Our foundation is the earth.
California's made of dust.
It's falling into the ocean.
You call that a foundation?
Look who's here. Gertrude and Alice.
Well, look at her. Were we supposed
to dress '80s and nobody called?
Take a break, ladies.
The coach house would be a better place
for you all to gather.
- Don't worry, we're leaving. Come on, Anita.
- Keep up, Edie. The '80s are back.
Pretty funny.
Hilarious.
This is a $1,000 suit.
You think you've seen it all.
Somebody could have set him up in the car
and run away.
Or maybe he died in a compromising position
like...you know...
- He's 80.
- It happens.
I'm telling you, this guy drove himself
to his own funeral.
- Hi, it's me.
- Hey, you, what's up?
Nothing. Missed you.
We haven't talked since yesterday.
- What do you mean? We talked this morning.
- We did?
Yeah, I called you before I left the hotel.
Oh, yeah, right, I spaced. I'm sorry.
- You don't sound like yourself.
- No, I'm fine, it's just...
Bodies are coming in left and right today.
Nate, Rico, I'll be there in a second.
Tell me the truth. That's the only way
these long-distance things work.
I gotta go. I'll call you later or you call me.
I'm fine. Be careful. Bye.
He's not fine.
You think?
Russell's supposed to be here.
Is he bailing on this?
He's asleep.
I fucked him into unconsciousness.
It costs a lot of money to rent chainsaws.
If we accidentally chop somebody up,
they'll totally sue our ass.
- I'm not saying to do that exact thing.
- We're trying to brainstorm a dark...
Confrontational concept. Where's yours?
- Attacking with chainsaws is a total clichê.
- Machetes!
We stand at the entrance with masks
and machetes. An image of menace.
- Machetes have no resonance...
- For our culture.
What are you, conjoined twins? Jesus.
You sent the kids to the park with Cassidy?
Vanessa, I have a right to see them.
They don't need to be near your hoochie
mama. Who knows where she's been?
It was never like that.
Why don't you just listen to me?
- I'll sleep on the couch. We can talk tonight.
- No.
How could you?
Come home to us after screwing her?
I never screwed her!
Never until last night!
I mean...
Your marriage is on the rocks
and that's what you do?
You kicked me out into the street.
Yes, I went to her.
Yes, I had sex with her. It's all your fault.
- Oh, my God.
- Wait, wait, I didn't mean...
You break your vows,
you fuck that whore and you blame me?
You coward, you bastard.
You son of a bitch. You make me sick.
Papa always said, when the time came,
he'd put on his best suit
and take himself to the funeral home.
- That's what he did.
- Unbelievable.
- Not if you knew him.
- He was a civil engineer. Meticulous.
He never wanted to burden us with anything.
He always did what he said he would do.
You could always trust his word.
The whole community looked up to him.
He was the best father.
A wonderful husband.
Sounds like he was a very fine man.
He was. He was.
I'm so, so sorry.
Thank you for your sympathy, Mr Diaz.
I'm really sorry, too.
So we'll see you Tuesday for the service.
He planned all that, as well.
If there's anything else we can do...
Keys to the car?
Oh, yeah.
You look busy.
I am. I'm contemplating.
Your busy is so different from my busy.
So, what's next on your packed agenda?
Papers to grade, yard work.
I should really finish that article.
Nice of you to talk with Claire's friend
this morning.
- I guess that goes on in your classroom.
- What?
Intellectual discussions
with young women in skimpy fashions.
Well, they do love to challenge a father figure.
But if you think that's skimpy,
you should see them summer quarter.
My man.
Dog, we're still on the job. You've had enough.
- What, are you my wife?
- Kiss my ass.
Whip it out.
Hey, this boyfriend, do you love him?
- That's right.
- Is he sexy?
You see this fat guy right here?
- Does he look crazy to you?
- That's the DJ. They always look crazy.
- Big dick?
- Excuse me?
Your boyfriend, does he have a big dick?
- Is that what you like? Me, I got a big dick.
- Jesus.
If something don't happen tonight,
it's gonna break right off.
You could really help me out, know what
I'm saying? You know what I'm saying?
I know what you're saying.
I'm not helping you out.
- It's not cool.
- You're kidding.
I don't treat my man
the way you treat your woman.
All right? You're loaded. Go back to your room.
- You don't think I'm sexy?
- You should go.
- Check out my dick before you say no, man.
- Go, please.
- Phone.
- Yup.
- Nate Fisher.
- It's me.
I thought last time was our last last time.
Yeah, as far as sex goes.
I told Joe.
- About me?
- Well, I didn't name names, but yeah.
I was really scared. It was really hard.
But, yeah, we're OK.
- Well, congratulations, I'm real happy for you.
- So, listen, come see our new house.
- Brenda...
- I know what you said.
I can't just surgically remove you from my life.
It doesn't make sense.
- Come on.
- Well, I'm sorry, I've got other plans.
- I don't believe you.
- It's true. We're going to Travel Town later.
- Aren't we, Miss Pumpkin?
- With the trains? I love them! They're so little.
- Can I come with you?
- I don't know.
No ulterior motives, I just wanna ride the rails.
- Brenda, we always have ulterior motives.
- No, we don't. We don't.
Come on. Please?
Liar, liar, liar.
What kind of man spends this much money
on some chick without getting laid?
- Hello?
- Hey, what are you doing?
- I'm trying not to eat the Krispy Kremes.
- Come over as soon as you can.
- Something's different. You sound better.
- Yeah.
I'm done crying.
Ready? What do you say, Maya, huh?
Caboose?
We're getting the caboose?
We got the caboose!
Lsn't this exciting?
- All aboard! Destination Las Vegas!
- Where we going? Las Vegas!
Bye!
My goodness, what's all this?
Nothing. It's just some flowers.
What's up?
That girl Anita,
I think she should be contributing financially.
Why? She's hardly ever here.
She basically lives at Russell's.
- Your Russell? That's terrible.
- I don't care.
Still, I think she should give us a cheque.
What do you have against Anita?
If she's going to prance around the house
in underwear, she should pay for the privilege.
Mom, I guarantee you,
none of my friends prance.
You know what I mean.
Well, don't book a 5am radio thing
and three stupid TV talk shows back to back.
Remember, I sign your fucking cheques.
- I'll be in front.
- No.
You think you have job security?
I fired my own goddamn parents.
Assholes! Greedy, bloodsucking assholes!
Gimme that.
I think there may be better ways
to handle your anger.
Yeah, well, when I care what you think,
I'll let you know.
- Fine.
- God.
- Oh, my God!
- That's your picture.
I look like a fucking $2 hooker!
I was supposed to sign off on these!
Fucking stupid assholes!
Why do they do it every fucking time?
Come on, now. Listen to me.
You're beautiful, all right?
Come on, now.
Besides,
aren't you supposed to look like a hooker?
I'm starving.
Oh, Keith.
Oh, my God.
Thank you so much.
Would you stop playing gang girl?
We're only here to talk.
You don't know what she's gonna do.
She could scratch your face,
then what do you say to the PTA?
Please, I want to see what she's like.
Whatever. I'm taking out my earrings
and I'm putting away my gold.
That's her.
- Who are you?
- I'm Vanessa. I'm Rico's wife.
OK, this is not my problem.
You have no right to be here.
If you're sleeping with Rico,
it is your problem.
No, it's not my problem you don't know
how to dress and you can't keep a man.
What? I'm not finished talking to you.
- Fucking bitch! Trying to steal my husband!
- Fucking home-wrecker! Dirty whore!
- I'll kick your fucking ass!
- And your fake fucking tits!
- You're just jealous of my tits!
- Bitch, please!
- Your man paid for these, gordita!
- Who the fuck are you calling gordita?
Get her, Vanessa! Get off my sister!
Get the hell off of my sister, you sleazy pig!
Don't fuck with my husband! Do not fuck with
my kids! I swear to God, I will fucking kill you!
Fuck you! I didn't make him do nothing!
I got a kid, too!
Get outta here! I've called the cops! 911 !
He doesn't want you any more.
Oh, shit.
- We gotta go pick up the boys from school.
- Right.
- You can help me pick up if you want.
- What have you done?
- I cut back the crape myrtle.
- This is not a crape myrtle.
It's the tree Nathaniel planted for Claire
on her tenth birthday.
Can't you tell a crape myrtle
from a Bradford flowering pear?
Well, whatever it is, it looked diseased.
I've read about powdery mildew
and it's no joke.
That tree is not, nor has it ever been,
diseased.
It never gets powdery mildew
because I keep the soil dry and aerated.
- My God, you've killed it.
- I have not.
Ask anyone, you have to trim vegetation
in order to stimulate new growth.
You're a geologist. You know rocks.
This is a living thing. You chop off the branches
and you make wounds.
Ruth, please, don't anthropomorphise trees.
Wounds, that's what they're called,
and these wounds will not heal.
They'll be invaded by rot.
It will move into the core wood.
You've butchered the most beautiful tree
in my yard.
I think it'll come back
bigger and better than ever.
And if it doesn't...
we can always get another one.
You could have told me
what you were going to do.
- Hello?
- Who's this?
You called me. Who's this?
Sarge.
You gotta know me or how can I call you?
Sarge? From paintball?
Oh, my God, this is David Fisher.
David and Keith. You made us breakfast.
Hey, David, yeah.
I remember. How you doing?
- I'm fine. How are you?
- Excellent.
I found this number in my wallet and I was,
like, "Whoa, who the fuck is this?" It's you.
- Yeah, it's me.
- Came from La Habra to play a tournament.
- Kinda hanging out now, drinking some beers.
- Yeah?
- Not much happening here.
- Come over.
Hi.
Hey.
You're so damn cute.
- Too much fragrance.
- Maybe a little.
Fuck! I bought these votives.
They're supposed to be unscented.
Instead they're, like,
sandalwood, lavender, vanilla, musk.
Come here, stop it.
I don't know why...
I mean, we already kinda had sex,
but I feel like I'm at a middle school cotillion.
Well, you're not.
You're all grown-up and beautiful.
- Don't laugh at me.
- I'm not. Not at all.
I don't know what to do
to make this go right tonight.
It's already going right.
Except you have to change
this vagina music immediately.
OK.
Yeah, I definitely remember you.
And Keith's out of town?
He's on the other side of the continent.
So this time I get you all to myself.
- Yes, you do.
- I dig it.
So do I.
- Weed?
- Oh, God, yes.
Dude, what are you doing
way the fuck over there?
- I don't know.
- Come here.
- What?
- You feeling anything resembling excitement?
Of course.
I love kissing you. Your face has
these subtle curves and angles.
- Am I doing something wrong?
- No.
There's just so much more we could be doing.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Let's make it like a dance.
Where I touch you...
- which is nice, right?
- Yeah.
And then you touch me.
OK, this is not happening. Sorry, it's not.
I took one of David's Ativan.
I thought it would help.
You really want to get off, huh?
Yeah, kinda. I mean, it'd be nice.
Go ahead.
Claire Fisher.
I want to watch.
All right, yeah.
Watch me. I'll come for you.
Oh, hey.
Oh, I was waiting up for you.
Hey.
Good music?
Yeah, you know, oompah, oompah.
Love, danger.
What did you do today?
- I went to Travel Town.
- No?
Yes. Nate took his daughter
and I tagged along.
- Did you ride the train?
- Four times.
I know Griffith Gulch like the back of my hand.
That's a long trip. You must be tuckered out.
You'd think so, but not so tuckered.
Dude, yeah!
Yeah!
- Hello.
- Lock up your goddamn Vanessa or I will.
- What are you talking about?
- She and another puta tried to beat my ass.
When they couldn't,
they beat my fucking car. It's your fault.
- You'd better buy me a new one.
- It is not my fault.
You started this. I've given you enough.
My life is ruined because of you.
Fuck your car, Infinity, I'm done.
Fine. I don't need you any more, dum-dum.
I got two guys better than you.
They're not stupid enough
to tell their bitch-ass wives. Bitch!
I don't know where we are.
Oh, Tampa.
Yeah, because when I got on stage, I said,
"How much do you love me, Tampa?"
I'd better let you get some sleep.
You know when you're really tired,
but you can't stop your mind?
It just goes around and around.
Yeah.
Hey, how's your boyfriend?
Not so good.
Tell me.
He got carjacked a while ago. It was bad.
Yeah.
I'm afraid of those things, too.
Some freak out of nowhere with a gun,
those autograph hounds.
You just never know.
You sing. It's my job to worry.
Stay with me?
- Just till I fall asleep.
- Celeste...
Shut up.
- Trying to get me arrested? You're barely 18.
- Publicity. Last March I turned 21.
You ever been with a woman?
Of course.
- I don't get fucked in the ass.
- That makes one of us.
- What are you doing?
- Gotta bunk with a guy from my team.
More tourney this week. I don't wanna get
my ass lit up at the top of the action.
Gotta focus, stay tight, stay alive.
- Game on.
- Well, stay here.
You can't go already, I want you to stay.
Yeah, I get that, but...
like, no, sorry.
I'll make you breakfast. I'll go to
your tournament with you. Come back to bed.
- Or we can watch TV.
- Do you have a deafness problem? Tune in.
I gotta be someplace else.
I'll leave you a joint. You could use it.
- What do I have to do?
- What?
To get somebody to stay with me!
- Fuck this shit, man.
- Don't you go!
David, do I call a hospital?
No.
Get some help, will ya? You're losing it.
Good Lord. Federico.
Hi, Mrs. F.
- What is this?
- I...
Well, we're having problems at home
and I didn't have anywhere else to go.
What a shame. I'm sorry.
- But you can't sleep here.
- Oh, OK, I'll go.
No, dear, come upstairs. You can take Claire's
old room. We'll put these in the washer.
Thank you.
Don't cry. Your marriage has always been
so strong. You'll be home soon.
No, I cheated on Vanessa.
She'll never forgive me.
What's wrong with you men?
Always turning your back on what you have,
always sniffing around for something new.
Me? You've had three boyfriends since Mr F,
not including the affair with the hairdresser.
- You know about Hiram?
- I practically live here.
I made a mistake. I just want to take it all back.
I know, dear, I know.
- Yo.
- Hey.
Just the man I want to talk to. What's up?
- You have to come home.
- I am. The tour's on the West Coast soon.
- I got to check in with you about...
- You're not listening to me. I need you now.
- The timing's not good.
- Fuck timing, fuck you!
What's going on with you?
Do I have to explain to you that I'm losing
my mind? Can't you tell? Where is everybody?
OK, OK, I hear you.
Don't stay alone, go to your family.
I'll be there as soon as I can.
I think I've figured us out.
Me, too.
You first.
I think you are the coolest
and most beautiful person
I've ever seen in my life
and I admire you so fucking much.
- Well, of course.
- And you are totally hot.
I mean, I feel that, I really do,
and I'm, like, so pulled to you.
But when I look at
this whole thing objectively...
- The attraction's aesthetic.
- Well, yeah. It's creative and artistic...
- And intellectual and physical...
- Yes!
But not necessarily sexual.
- You're not into fucking women.
- I thought I was.
- Shit.
But after seeing your orgasm,
I really, really want one.
Fuck!
It's a beautiful place, Bren.
Peaceful.
You and Joe did good.
Could've been us.
Yeah, but it's not us.
And it is time for Maya's nap.
Ready? Time for a nap.
We gotta say goodbye.
Just let her sleep on the bed.
Come on, we can talk about safe things.
I'm going out for a couple of hours.
OK, bye.
All you do is come and go!
Ruth?
Marriage is not a gas station, George.
You can't just pull in and fill up
whenever you remember you have a wife.
That is completely unfair and inaccurate.
I have always treated you
as a partner and a friend.
If that's not marriage, I don't know what is.
- That's right, you don't.
- What about your own life?
Why do I have to be
the centre of everything for you?
Why do you have to hound me about every
detail down to the fucking subatomic level?
When I don't there's shit on my doorstep or
another child appears or another girlfriend
or you murder my favourite tree!
Sarah was wrong.
You're not like Nathaniel, you're worse!
- You are smothering me.
- Oh, bullshit!
You always do exactly what you want.
You haven't changed or grown one iota
since we met.
Well, don't say I didn't warn you.
Warn me? Are you threatening divorce?
That is not what I meant.
I'm your seventh spouse.
How much warning do you think I need?
- You jumped on him?
- I couldn't stop myself.
- What did he do?
- Put me down and sat on me.
I was like a mosquito to him. It was humiliating.
- I have to get control of myself.
- No, David.
If you were any more controlled,
you'd be a sculpture.
You know what?
Last night, I had a humiliating
homosexual experience of my own.
Seriously? What happened?
- Not much. I never even went down on her.
- You can stop there.
I just couldn't go through with it.
It pisses me off.
- It would be so much easier to be gay.
- Oh, no.
- Yeah, I'd have a really defined subculture.
- Overrated.
We're both women. I'd have some idea
of what she was thinking and feeling.
Not necessarily.
I wouldn't have to deal
with unfamiliar sex organs.
They're all unfamiliar unless they're yours.
How you doing?
- I gotta leave the tour, Duane.
- Yeah, I heard.
- There'll still be work in LA?
- Definitely, yeah.
We know it's not your fault.
What are you gonna do?
Yeah. I'll go tell Celeste.
Whoa. She's the one that told me.
- What are you talking about?
- What are you? Celeste fired your ass.
Joe. Oh, God. Fuck.
- Wait, wait, Maya's...
- Nate's daughter's in the next room.
Look...
I deserve whatever you have to say to me,
but I don't want her scared so...
- Can you give me that?
- Get out.
That's him? Your previous indiscretion, him?
- Yes.
- That depressing cripple.
You're both cripples, obviously.
I am so stupid. I was actually considering
having children with you.
- That truly frightens me.
- It's not your fault.
I know it's not my fault.
I've obviously been in denial
that I'm in recovery...
Shut the fuck up!
You neurotic, tedious, self-absorbed bitch.
You don't give a shit about me. You never did.
That's not true. I love you, Joe. I do.
I was honest with you. I have an issue.
Oh, blah-blah fucking psycho-bullshit!
It's not sex, it's betrayal.
That's your fucking addiction.
- OK, I'll get help...
- No, no, no.
Here's a question for you.
What do you call a person without character,
without integrity, without loyalty,
without respect?
I call that person a fucking waste of my time.
That's not who I am.
You think you know me, but you don't.
You'd think someone in this family
would notice when the house is on fire.
This is bullshit.
You go to bed with a woman while
your boyfriend's recovering?
- I can't trust a man like that.
- Celeste...
If you stayed with the tour, you'd distract me.
That can't happen.
Plus it's very unprofessional to fuck the boss.
Not cool, dog.
Just so you know,
I was leaving before you fired me.
Synchronicity.
Ciao, baby.
"Dear neighbour...
"You are my brother.
"I love you... "
"And yet, I feel a great sadness...
- "in my bosoml"
- Where's Mom?
"Going away. Don't contact the authorities.
"I'll be in touch when I'm ready.
Dinner is in the oven."
Apparently she's gone walkabout.
I wish this family
was as close as the Flanders.
OK, OK, all right, all right. She's right.
Let's do something together.
What does everyone say to miniature golf,
followed by a round of chocolate milkshakes?
- All rightl
- I was going to wash my hair.
English