- Piece of shit's whacked.
- Try the celly again.
And it ain't no piece of shit. The
alternator's a little temperamental.
Well, maybe the battery's dead,
like this phone.
Look, it ain't the battery.
It's the alt...
Hey, this is like one of them
Scream movies, huh?
More like Boyz N the Hood.
I'm gonna jet to that phone.
One of my dogs'll hook us up.
I know you ain't leaving
me here all alone.
Hey, look, you'll be safer in here.
Be back in three, all right?
- All right.
- Give me some love.
Ain't nobody home,
Leave a message,
Hey, Luis, pick up the phone, dog.
Hey, wake up, man.
Damn.
Fucking lazy-ass punk,
motherfucker man.
Paco! Oh, my God!
Who the fuck is it?
Hello?
Hello!
- Where you from?
- Your mama's pussy, bitch.
Paco! Paco!
Paco, no! No!
- Let's go.
- No!
No! No!
Miss Chenowith gave us her account
of your activities at the crime scene.
Crime scene? So you're
saying it was arson?
What's your story, Mr. Fisher?
The house is empty. I wanted to show
Brenda where I hung out as a kid.
I don't know why he
wanted to show it to me.
Can you tell us what you did
while you were there?
Walked around, looked at things.
You really expect us to believe you
broke into an abandoned house...
...just to walk around?
Okay. We fucked.
- You were there for an hour or so?
- Tops.
Could you walk us through what the
two of you did for that hour?
We made love.
Could you please be as
specific as possible?
Just to establish a timeline.
Well, he went down on
me for a while.
He's really good at it.
I don't exactly remember
the specifics.
He was in a state, like he had
a lot of aggression to work out.
She said that I was aggressive?
- Man, she should talk.
- Then he fell asleep.
- What happened then?
- We were exhausted, so we left.
I left to meet somebody. He was just
waking up. I don't know what he did.
- Can I go?
- I think we have everything we need.
- Thank you for your cooperation.
- Peace out, guys.
Well, yeah, she left first,
I left right after that,
Are you aware that the property was
purchased by Kroehner Service?
Yes, Matt Gilardi said they were planning
to open a cheap cremation place...
...and put us out of business.
Was that the point where you called
him a "greedy Nazi fuck"?
- Is that correct?
- Yes, that is correct.
You think I set the fire?
Well, you have to admit...
...it does seem like a beneficial
turn of events for your business.
- So, what, do I need a lawyer?
- Not yet.
You're free to go.
Actually, one more thing.
Do you know where your sister
was on the night of the fire?
No, why?
I understand she had a run-in with
the law recently. A missing foot.
If she is developing a pattern of acting
out subsequent to her father's death...
Claire had nothing to
do with that fire.
How do you know?
I knew passing the health department
inspection was too good to be true.
It just meant something
else would go wrong.
Great, there goes a month's profit.
We can live without air conditioning.
Plenty of people do.
Yeah, people in the Third World.
We can't run a business
without air conditioning.
If we lose any more funerals...
...Kroehner won't have to take
us over. We'll be bankrupt.
- How much?
- Central air, three grand easy.
Guess what.
Gilardi tipped the cops off.
- Think I'm a suspect.
- That's ridiculous.
- Where's Claire?
- School. I hope.
Do you know where
she was before the fire?
Why, what is it? Oh, dear God,
they don't think...
Oh, she couldn't have.
Good news, bad news.
Compressor's fine. Bad news is, your
pneumatic actuator assembly is shot.
Normally, I could do it in a day, but
with this heat wave, give me five days.
- Five?
- What's it gonna set us back?
Shouldn't debt you more than
3700, parts and labor.
Our 10:00.
Tell them we'll have air conditioning.
Three days.
He would have been 21 next week.
We were gonna buy him a new bed.
- Now we're buying him a coffin.
- Three in the morning.
He shouldn't have been out with
that girl in that neighborhood.
It's the worst thing that can happen,
to lose a child.
We lost him years ago.
- We'll see to it that Paco...
- His name is Manny.
- His gang name was Paco.
- He goes by Paco.
And he wasn't lost,
he was assassinated.
We'll see to it that he
has a dignified service.
We've been to three funeral
homes. No one will take us.
We don't turn people away here.
But sometimes when families lack
the funds necessary or insurance...
- I got money.
- We don't want your money.
If your son is willing to finance...
- He's not our son!
- He's a gang leader. Alvarado Kings.
- Don't you read the papers?
- My name is Powerful.
Paco's gonna have a fat-ass
funeral whatever it costs.
We got mad cash, so long as
you all can do it up right.
Now, can you all do it up right
or should we move on?
If you'll excuse me.
Nate will show you flower arrangements,
which might be to your liking.
Lilies are always nice.
Federico, I need your help,
your expertise.
- I've got a really tough one upstairs.
- Decomp? Crispy critter?
Gunshots, no facial damage,
cut and dried.
The family wants a traditional
Mexican funeral.
Okay. What's a traditional
Mexican funeral?
But there's this other guy,
the deceased's gang leader.
And what does this have
to do with me?
I was hoping you would
talk to them for me. With me.
What, because I'm Latino,
I know about gangs?
Well, you probably
know more than I do.
And why's that?
Well, I just assumed that maybe
somebody in your family might...
No, no one in my family. Never.
I've worked here for years, and you
don't know a damn thing about me.
- That's not true.
- You own an atlas?
- An atlas?
- Yeah, because if you did...
...you'd know there's 2400 miles
between Puerto Rico and Mexico.
You're Puerto Rican?
Look, Federico, I'm
sorry. I just assumed...
We can't afford to lose this funeral.
And I'm afraid if Nate and I
are the point of contact, we will.
This is our blue opal, 20 gauge
aluminum and copper...
...with a light blue,
sovereign velvet interior.
- It's nicer than our car.
- It's beautiful.
It's not good enough.
Mrs. Bolin, if this is the casket you
want for your son, you should have it.
He is your son.
Hey.
Where you from, dog?
One moment, please.
"Where you from?" Like, where
my parents were born?
San Lorenzo, Puerto Rico.
"Where you from?"
As in, what gang I belong to? Yeah,
I'll tell you what gang I belong to.
The gang that's gonna help
you bury your friend.
The gang that's gonna be there
for you and your cholos...
...when every other home doesn't
wanna deal with your bullshit.
Your friend is dead, man.
Now, do you want me to help you
or you just wanna go heads-up?
It's good.
- I don't like it. It's dangerous.
- Not if we let Rico handle everything.
David, we are so white. If we
step in, we will totally fuck up.
Language.
I'm more worried whether
Claire started that fire.
Why would she? To help us out?
She hates us.
- Is Brenda a vegetarian?
- She'll eat anything.
Did you know the night dad died,
Claire was high on crystal meth?
Oh, my God,
isn't that a horse tranquilizer?
No, it's speed, really nasty speed
that makes you crazy.
If there are things
you don't want me to hear...
...go talk about them in another room.
- I assume she drinks.
- I can call and tell her to cancel.
No, I've been looking
forward to this.
I have some errands to run. I'll pick
up a nice chardonnay while I'm out.
- What errands?
- I can give you a list if you'd like.
You guys, this kid at school today
got busted for having a taser...
...because he showed it to
his friends at lunch.
What an idiot. There were like six
cops. It was absolutely hilarious.
What?
No, it's not really
a gang funeral. It's...
They needed a home,
we needed a body. Everyone wins.
Yeah, right. Who you gonna call
when the bullets start flying?
- Anyone but you.
- Oh, you damn straight.
Claire's gonna need a lawyer.
A good one.
Look, if she set that fire,
she'll do what's right. I'll see to it.
What's right is getting her top legal
counsel and having her plead the Fifth.
I don't care what you do, just keep her
out of the system. She'll be eaten alive.
Any chance you can snoop around
and find out their game plan?
I don't know. I already
interfered once.
- Are you guys pulling out or what?
- Yeah, in a minute.
Well, let's go.
Fucking fags, man.
Keith.
Keith!
- Say it again.
- What?
I said, say it again. The next time
you call someone a fucking fag...
...you make sure that fag
isn't an L.A.P.D. Officer.
You got that?
- You understand me?
- Yeah.
Now, you got my badge,
file a complaint. I dare you.
You get your punk ass out of here,
fucking bitch.
- Tore his ass up.
- I don't think he meant anything by it.
Do you hate yourself that much?
This is some fucked up way to
make a living. You know that?
- How's your day, man?
- You don't wanna know.
You ever see sunlight?
Or you gotta avoid it?
- Hey, you checking out my dick.
- I was not.
I'm just fucking with you, man.
Hi.
A gift from my parents.
They'll freak when they find out.
- You're an hour early.
- Really?
Yeah.
Not quite as Addams Family
as I'd expected.
Dave and I used to play Addams
Family when we were kids.
I was usually Gomez.
He was always Lurch.
The kitsch factor is substantial.
Hence your well-developed
sense of irony, I suppose.
- It's hot in here.
- Do I hear voices?
- Look who's early.
- It's a pleasure to see you again.
I'm so glad you could make it, dear.
Champagne. How festive. Thank you.
Excuse me, I'm knee-deep
in marinara. I'll go chill this.
Nate, give Brenda a tour.
- She hates me.
- Why do you say that?
Because it's true.
What's the matter?
Afraid Mommy might see?
Okay, okay. Can we not turn
tonight into psych 101?
Because trust me, we'd never
make it through the evening.
Somebody's defensive.
Nate, it doesn't matter if your
mother likes me or not. I don't care.
What's that shit?
Oh, hell no. No.
Hey, how come you don't
call your bone daddy?
Still pissed at him, right?
Hey, I'm feeling you, man.
What gives him the right to get up
in your world? You know, be so...?
So fucking self-righteous?
That's what I'm saying. You don't call
him nothing, but he went off on you.
Yeah. I think he's got a problem with
that stress-management shit.
Hey, or maybe he's one of
them rage-aholics.
- I mean, that boy went off.
- Just because some kid calls him a fag.
- It's so unnecessary.
- Well, he called you a fag too.
- So?
- So, what'd you do?
Nothing.
And Simon Peter stood
and warmed himself.
They said therefore unto him,
"Art not thou one of his disciples?"
- He denied it and said, "I am not. "
- John 18:25.
No wonder he went
off on you, man. You know?
Hey, bury me naked, please.
It's a shame Diane Arbus is dead.
She could take some fucking
great photographs in here.
- What's the matter with you today?
- Nothing. I just have a lot on my mind.
- I don't wanna bore you with it.
- Thank you.
Come here.
- Why?
- Just do it.
What's wrong?
I'm about to become an undertaker,
and I'm scared to death of it.
A huge corporation wants
to put us out of business...
...and I'm worried my sister's not
only a crackhead, she's an arsonist.
- There's a lot of sadness in this house.
- It's a funeral home.
No wonder you ran away. You channel
other people's pain, you know that?
My father called it a gift.
It is a gift.
Oh, God!
- Oh, God!
- Guess dinner's ready.
So, what's it like to be interrogated?
Did you flash your crotch...
...like Sharon Stone in that movie?
- Claire.
They just keep asking the same
question different ways to trip you up.
That's cool. Was it fun?
I bet it was kind of fun.
- Not really.
- Think they'll wanna interrogate me?
No.
Nate, will you say grace?
- Wouldn't David rather?
- Please.
Thank you, Lord, for our health and
bounty through Christ. Amen.
What, are you on crack?
Squash?
Mom, Nate and I have been
working on a business plan...
...to figure out how we're
gonna fend off Kroehner.
Business plan? Your father
never had a business plan.
- Yeah, that's part of the problem.
- We'd like to go over it with you.
I don't need to see it.
It's your business, not mine.
- Is there sauce for the pasta?
- I'll get it.
- Brenda, what do you do for a living?
- She gives massages.
- Shiatsu.
- Now, what exactly is that?
It's a Japanese
bodywork technique...
...that involves pressure to points
on the acupuncture meridians.
Well, how interesting, acupuncture.
That's the pins, right?
- Yes. The pins.
- So you stick pins in people.
I use my thumbs, wrists, elbows.
So you stick your thumbs in people?
No. At least not as part of my job.
- I hope you stay for dessert.
- It's peach cobbler.
Yum.
This is a nice box. That
Federico is a good salesman, huh?
I'll say. You know what the
markup is on one of these?
Thirty-two hundred.
Hey, can I get like a nightlight up
in here? I don't like the dark.
Well, then you shouldn't have gone
and gotten yourself shot.
Shit, that's cold, man.
Mr. Powerful and his
entourage are here.
- I'll be right there.
- Who were you talking to?
Myself.
David, why did you stop
going to church with me?
I've been going to a different church
with a friend of mine.
That cop? The black man?
Don't be a pussy.
Yes, Mom, that cop, the black man.
I love you, Paco. Oh, God.
You all right?
I look like a fucking Bible
salesman. I look like you.
Man, what's up with this
whack-ass music?
- I'm not sure about the music.
- Yeah, it blows.
What about the "Ave Maria"?
- Perfect.
Honey?
God, no. No, please.
No, no, no.
No!
It's like a mad scientist lab in here.
How can you live here?
Better than a Turkish prison.
Most days.
- Jesus.
- Told you.
- Did you ever kill anybody?
- I don't know. Shot at a few.
Everybody thinks I burned down
this house across the street.
- Did you?
- What do you think?
What's it like to shoot a gun?
You wanna try some time?
- Come down to East Los, be down.
- Are you serious? Because I will.
You're some kind of
tough, little bitch, huh?
You didn't hear your road dog
calling for help on your machine.
You ain't gonna spend
the rest of your life...
...wondering why you didn't pick up
the phone the first time it rang.
You're hurting me.
You don't know shit, little girl.
Don't waste my time.
This one right here is my first one.
After that, man...
I mean, I got me this one right here
when I got jumped in. Check it out.
- That's very intricate.
- Yeah.
And this one. This one took me
three weeks to heal. Watch out.
That's the shit, huh?
- Can I help you?
- Hi, it's so good to see you again.
- How have you been?
- Fine.
So sad. I read about Manuel's death in
the Times. I had to pay my respects.
Oh, it's heartbreaking. The riots...
I mean, the uprising...
...was supposed to increase the peace
and all we have are more dead children.
Did you know him?
Oh, I feel I know all
these innocent victims.
This is not a good time. If you'd like
to forward a card to the family...
Well, maybe I could just
stay a few minutes.
A card. I'll do that.
You should have seen
my baby, so happy...
...such a smile that could
break your heart.
What kind of God lets a baby like
that get caught up in all that shit?
Drugs.
Guns.
Death.
Mrs. Bolin, I'm not gonna tell you
that it's all gonna be okay.
But it just takes time.
This is as bad as it gets.
I have nothing to live for.
You have your husband.
You have you.
You have the memory of that little
baby. You have to keep that alive.
My father died on Christmas Eve.
And there's so much I never said...
...never knew about him.
But he's a part of me.
And Manny will always
be a part of you.
Why didn't God take me
instead of my boy?
I don't know.
You gotta apologize to your boy Keith.
Otherwise, you're just a born bitch.
You're speaking like
this at your funeral?
Damn straight. I say
whatever I goddamn please.
I've been to a ton of funerals.
You seen one, you seen them all.
- Even mine.
- No gunfire, no fights.
Nah. No Sharks, no Jets.
Just like any other funeral.
- You let down, huh?
- A little.
A Detective McBride just called. They
made a determination of the house fire.
- They termed it "cause unknown. "
- So they ruled out arson.
No, they just can't tell.
Either way, the case is closed.
Which doesn't rule out the possibility
that Claire set that fire.
She didn't do that, Nate.
Well, what if she did, Mom? Pretending
it didn't happen is not gonna help.
I'm sorry about last night
with Brenda...
...when you walked in on us.
- I know what you're talking about.
- Where have you been?
- None of your business.
When did this become a police state?
I need an Altoid.
The original sin
wasn't eating the apple.
It wasn't questioning authority.
It was not giving God the chance
to give his side of the argument.
It was just taking the
serpent's word as gospel.
It was not going back to God
and saying, "Hey, what gives?
He said you are lying to us. "
It was just assuming that God lies.
I'm sorry about the other day.
Aren't you gonna say,
"Hey, man, I'm sorry too...
...for revealing my dormant psycho
side and scaring the shit out of you"?
You really think I hate myself?
- Good to see you, David.
- Hi.
I know where you are. I was there.
I'll wait for you because I love you.
But I'm not moving
backwards for anybody.
I'm not asking you to move backwards.
I'm just asking you to be patient...
...and a little calmer.
Do you have any idea what I put up
with on my job every day?
How many times the word "fag"
has been written on my locker?
How many times I wonder going into a
dangerous situation if I'll get back up?
We were stepped on
yesterday, David.
And I did something about it
because I am tired of it.
When you get tired of it,
you let me know.
- Morning.
- Hi.
You think I should make a peace
offering to your mother?
No, that'll just make things worse.
I brought it up yesterday.
She nearly bit my head off.
Oh, Jesus. It's no accident you
guys are undertakers...
...because you take every fucking feeling
you have, put it in a box and bury it.
Better that than examine every fucking
moment until the joy is drained out of it.
- Come here.
- No.
Just do it.
Sex does not solve everything, Nate.
You wouldn't have to
worry about us...
...while you're working
and we're out of school,
Right, The family that plays
together, stays together,
And it'd be a groovy way to find out
exactly what's wrong with this country,
I'd be able to see all
the injustices firsthand,
Look, kids, everything
you say makes sense...
...and it would be marvelous
if we could go, But there's one...
Claire, are you okay?
- No.
- Well, do you wanna talk about it?
Sure.
My pimp's threatening to beat me up
because I can't turn enough tricks.
What's worse is, he's threatening to
take away my smack. It's hell.
- Why do you have to be such a bitch?
- Why do you assume I'm in trouble?
Like you guys are such
shining examples. Jesus.
She's right, Mom, Do you want
Chris to pump gas all his life?
And Tracy to wait on tables
in some sleazy strip joint?
Kroehner is going to keep
strong-arming our suppliers...
...undercutting us, stealing funerals.
We're never gonna be able to compete
in terms of size or market presence.
Where we can compete
is quality of service, integrity.
- We'll give them the human touch.
- It all sounds good to me.
Is this over?
But we have to get our message out.
We'll need to market and promote.
Replace outmoded equipment
and install computers.
Fine.
In order to make this all work, we'll
need a significant financial investment.
- How much?
- Ninety-three thousand.
You want me to give you $93,000
from your father's life insurance?
Nobody else is going to do it.
We're still paying off a bank
note Dad took out years ago.
We hate to ask, Mom,
but we're desperate.
- Of course, you're not obligated.
- I know that.
When do you need it?
- You sure, Mom?
- But it's not a loan.
I'm now an investor
in Fisher & Sons.
We'll establish a fair percentage
of equity and rate of return.
I can invest in either
my boys or tech stocks.
Anything's better than the track.
David, I'd like it if you'd come with
me to church every once in a while...
...now that your father's gone.
I shouldn't have to go alone.
Okay.
Well, that was weird.
It gets weirder. There was a message
on my machine from Gilardi.
He wants to meet with us today.
Hey, dog. Getting ready
to throw some blows?
If you were me, Paco, what would you
say to Gilardi? What would you do?
If I was you?
Shit, if I was you, I wouldn't
own a fucking funeral home.
But all right.
All right, say I'm doing my thing,
selling my shit.
Some punk ass tries to
clock me from my corner.
You know what I say?
I say, "Peep this, motherfucker! 5:00,
you near me, my corner or my shit...
...I'll cut your fucking stomach,
watch your guts spill out.
I'll let you live until
you slowly bleed to death...
...in front of your fucking kids. "
Feel your heart racing?
Because when the other guy
feels like that, you won.
Come on, David.
You gotta stand up, man.
You gotta step up.
Yeah, you stepped up.
Look what happened to you.
That's right. For 20 years,
I lived my life like a man.
When are you gonna start?
- You lowered your offer.
- What can I say? The market fluctuates.
Thanks, but we don't see a need to
align ourselves with Kroehner right now.
Okay.
I'll make it simple.
You accept our offer
by the end of the day...
...or I'll make it my personal mission
to bury you by the end of the month.
David, you in on
this suicide mission?
David?
- You just threatened my family.
- Let's not be melodramatic.
What do you expect us
to do, run and hide?
- Sell and be grateful? Pack up and move?
- Lf you're smart.
You have the Kroehner organization
behind you. And what do we have?
You.
One day when your mind isn't
on Fisher & Sons...
...I will find you
or someone you love.
I'm not saying anyone
is going to die.
There are tragedies
far worse than death.
Things you couldn't even dream of, you
spineless, candy-ass, corporate fuck.
Just give me a reason.
It's your decision. Are we really
worth the trouble, Mr. Gilardi?
Lunch is over. Get lost.
Are you deaf?
- What the fuck was that?
- I think I'm gonna throw up.
Hi.
I hope you like fancy bath stuff. I went
a little crazy at the Beverly Center.
- Thank you. This wasn't necessary.
- Yes, it was.
I'm afraid you might not have seen
me in my best light the other night.
I saw more of you than I cared to.
Okay.
Look. I'm not a very
traditional person.
And I don't really know what's
happening between me and Nate...
...but every once in a while
I get a glimpse...
...of things maybe working
out for us...
...and I'm really sorry
about what happened.
Be careful with him.
He's a lot more fragile
than he'd like to think.
Aren't we all?
- Well, thank you.
- My pleasure.
Are the Fishers around?
- You need David?
- All of them and you too.
Just tell me what
you're unhappy with.
Just get them, all right?
Will you join us?
Merciful Jesus...
...please bring rest and peace
to our fallen brother...
...son...
...friend...
...Manuel Paco Bolin.
May he live with you
forever in your lightened truth.
- Almighty Father. Amen.
- Amen.
We also wanna thank the Fishers...
...who lost a father and husband.
Lord bring peace to
them in their grief...
...as you have in ours.
We'll miss you.
Hey, let go of me, you
fucking fag. I gots to go.
Jesus, you're just a kid.
So are you.
Hey, David.
Don't be a bitch.
Shit. Now, I know why you
wanted to go bowling...
...instead of a movie.
- I was state champion...
...in the Youth For Christ Bowling
League when I was 17.
- You're gonna beat the pants off me.
- That's my intent.
I got a college degree, and I still
cannot figure how this scoring works.
Hey, you fellows together?
Yeah, we are.
That's cool.
Hey, Bren, the door's unlocked.
- Brenda?
- In the bedroom.
I'm just here to deliver a pizza,
ma'am. I don't want any trouble.
I got your tip right here.
Whoa.
Where's my pizza?
Mom asked me to tell you that the
lavender bath scrub was delicious.
She's not supposed to eat it.
- What's with all the candles?
- I'm burning up.
Burning up for your love.
What?
You like some guy enough to have
his name burned in your flesh.
I would have done a lot
more than that for him.
- What's up with you?
- I had a really weird day.
Poor baby.
- Mom, are you okay?
- Fine.
Can I ask you something? And
you promise to tell me the truth?
Maybe.
- Did you set that fire?
- No.
No, I would never
do anything like that.
I may have swiped that foot, though.
Dinner's almost ready.
Subtitles by www. tv-series. nm. ru