Yo, what's up? You get it?
No, I didn't get anything. I don't know
what the fuck you're talking about.
- Anthony, go play in Mom's room.
- Why?
Because I said so,
you little shit. Go!
Get up, come on.
You suck!
Kid's got so much major attitude.
Six years old and he's
already a hard-ass.
You can get more of this stuff?
How much?
- How much money do you have?
- Oh, like I'm a fucking loaded.
Hey, Bennett and I are going to
that record release party tonight.
And then there's an
after-hours in Hollywood.
No, dude, I fucking hate that shit.
It's always a bunch of
whacked-out faggot tweakers...
...shoving glow sticks in your eyes.
- It's at Sin Sin.
Great, whacked-out Asian tweakers.
That club's weak, dude.
Anthony? An...
Oh, fuck!
Oh, shit.
- Oh, fuck.
- Fuck!
I gotta get out of here.
- What?
- I gotta get that shit out of here.
Oh, fuck. Anthony?
Morning.
Okay. What are you mad
at me about now?
I'm busy, all right? My workload
has doubled since Federico's gone.
You can't expect me to engage you
in small talk just to make you feel better.
You flunked the licensing test.
- Did you think I didn't know?
- I didn't.
You didn't apply yourself.
You think this is something people do as
a last resort...
...and therefore it can't be that difficult.
- I feel bad. You wanna make it worse?
- I don't care what you feel...
- Bullshit.
You like it when I feel bad
because misery loves company.
- How'd he die?
- Heart attack.
Fell down a flight of stairs,
dead when he hit the bottom.
- His nose supposed to look like that?
- Of course not.
I have to finish embalming him before
I can start on anything cosmetic.
- I can deal with whoever it is.
- Unless it's a walk-in.
You are choosing
to be the victim here.
I could handle an intake
and you know it.
Ladies, teacup chain.
Good.
And walk to the middle and back.
All right, very good.
Very good, ladies and gentlemen.
So we'll see you all at the same time
next week, okay? Be safe getting home.
Morning, folks.
- Hi.
Goddamn it, why hasn't anyone
answered the door? Where is Mom?
Okay, if you haven't slept with
that guy yet, would you start?
Because I think it would
do you a world of good.
Don't do that.
- Do what?
- Watch me like that.
I can't help it.
You're beautiful.
Oh, for heaven's sake.
- I want to go camping again.
- Then go camping.
- With you.
- I've got a job now, Hiram.
I can't just up and leave
whenever I feel like it.
Spring is a very busy
time of the year.
It's our anniversary tomorrow.
The first time we went camping
was two years ago tomorrow.
We don't have anniversaries.
- I never agreed to anniversaries.
- Just you and me alone in the woods.
Naked under the stars.
Just like it was at the beginning.
Tomorrow is such short notice.
I can't promise anything.
But I'll try.
My mom wants to know
how quickly we can do this.
Well, I'd suggest a viewing in
two days to allow proper restoration.
Viewing?
For friends, family. You can make it
as small or as large as you wish.
No, I can't see him in a box.
I can't.
All right.
Ms. Dimas, seeing your son before
you bury him might help you to let go.
No, I don't want to see him!
Of course. We'll arrange
for a closed-casket ceremony.
Will three days
give you enough time?
Yeah, that's gonna be fine.
- Nate will show you to the door.
- Thanks.
What happened?
A 6-year-old found a gun
and was playing with it.
- Oh, Jesus.
- Yeah.
They gave me this at the hospital.
It's some sort of receipt. I don't know...
I don't know if you need it, but...
What was he doing here?
- Gabe.
- It's okay.
Hey.
My brother just told me.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't know where else to go.
My grandmother's funeral was here.
Yeah, of course.
My mom's waiting
for me to unlock the car.
I thought we were supposed
to encourage people to have a viewing.
Well, sometimes
people don't want that.
Well, sometimes you don't
want to work any harder.
When faced with the option of
not having to restore a child's head...
...that's been blown to bits, yeah,
I don't want to do that. Do you?
We can't force someone to do
something they're not ready to do...
...because we think it's the right thing.
Because it will make us feel better.
- Can I help you?
- Roses are if you love somebody, right?
Roses are the classic choice, but other
flowers could achieve the same effect.
What if you were gonna
ask her to marry you?
Oh, how lovely.
Well, roses would be
the perfect choice.
But she turned out
to be a cheating coward...
...and ran off with some shithead
that she met at traffic school.
What color would
you give a coward?
- Yellow. Yellow.
- Great.
Twelve dozen yellow roses
sent to this address, please.
- What would you like the card to say?
- "Fuck you, cunt. "
I think it would be more
personal if you write that.
Yes. Yes.
I have to take the day off
tomorrow and Saturday.
Why?
I was supposed to have plans
with a friend and I forgot.
Is it with that man?
The one with the funny little car
that picks you up?
It's an electric car and it's
very good for the environment.
- Why are you laughing?
- Because you are not.
- You like this man?
- Can I have the days off or not?
Take! Go, I don't care.
We will miss you.
Beep, beep.
- Brenda?
- Hey there.
I'll be right out. I just
got out of the shower.
- How was work?
- It sucked.
Like I figured, I failed
that funeral director's test.
There was this intake meeting
this morning I totally fucked up.
And I just picked up a dead
6-year-old at the morgue.
All in all, it's been
a pretty bad day.
Goddamn it!
Sometimes I feel like I don't have
any fucking idea what I'm doing.
It's like I made this bullshit decision
to go into this business...
...for all the wrong reasons
and now it's too late.
- It's never too late.
- Jesus, Billy.
What, do you live here now?
No, Brenda just gave me a shiatsu.
I've been kind of tense lately.
So...
- Bad day?
- Yeah.
- Well, I've had my share of those.
- Well, I don't doubt that.
I don't really feel like cooking, so you
guys decide what we're having delivered.
That shit was all over the news.
Six years old, right?
Fuck! Some people should just
not be allowed to have kids.
She just sat there like a ghost.
Just like she'd been erased.
- I felt so fucking helpless.
- Oh, God.
That poor woman.
There's a tribe in Nigeria that
throws a dead baby's body...
...into the bush because they believe
if buried...
...the dead infant would offend the
earth gods which bring fertility and food.
The Chinese consider the death
of a child a bad death.
The parents and grandparents
aren't expected to go to the funeral.
Or the Balinese mother who's counseled
to be cheerful after her infant's death...
...because grief makes one vulnerable
to illness and malevolent demons.
Well, that was informative.
Yeah, I thought it'd be good to read
up on your boyfriend's line of work.
What a man does is...
Well, it's who he is.
Right, Nate?
Yeah.
A man should know the history
of his chosen profession...
...if he expects to be
anything but an amateur.
- So I'm an amateur.
- I prefer the term dilettante.
And what are you, Billy?
Running around with your camera,
taking pictures of people's lives?
Boys.
You think knowing a bunch of arcane
National Geographic shit is gonna...
...help me cope with a 6-year-old
who shot himself in the head?
There are plenty of places in the world
where a kid dying is pretty common.
But we can't deal with it,
because a dead child...
...is the greatest failure of a culture that
believes it's reversed the order of nature.
This was an accident.
This wasn't nature.
You know what
I find interesting?
If you lose a spouse,
you're called a widow or a widower.
If you're a child and you lose
your parents, then you're an orphan.
But what's the word to describe
a parent who loses a child?
I guess that's just too fucking
awful to even have a name.
- I was worried you weren't gonna show.
- I just got tied up at work.
Believe me, I need this
after the day I had.
This ought to help.
- Oh, what is it?
- X. Ecstasy.
- You ever done it?
- No, can't say that I have.
You're gonna love it.
- Are you gonna take one too?
- I'm already there. Let's dance.
- I'm not a very good dancer.
- You will be.
David.
David. Here,
you gotta keep drinking this.
She was only 63.
That's so young.
Isn't that young?
Have you thought about what kind
of funeral you'd like for your mother?
It has to be beautiful.
Well, we can offer you a wide
variety of services ranging from...
...simple to more formal to...
To anything you might need.
Yes, anything at all.
It's a good thing
I was there, you know?
I mean, Gabe was so wrecked
I was the one who had to trash his weed.
Seriously, if the police found that shit,
it'd be way worse, you know?
- Hey, Andy.
- Hey.
- How's Gabe?
- He's okay, I guess.
- Well, have you talked to him?
- Not really.
Well, are you gonna see him later?
I don't know. It's real weird over there.
- The mother's, like, all freaked.
- Yeah, but what about Gabe?
Look, Morticia, I'm not interfering.
It's too much to get into, you know?
- I thought you were his friend.
- Why don't you fuck off, bitch?
If you're so worried, why don't you go
fuck him again? That'll cheer him up.
Nice, that's nice.
Yeah.
By the way, Parker told me
how one of your testicles is, like...
...freakishly small, like a peanut.
- Is that true?
- That's not true.
For later.
- You have a headache, dear?
- Yeah, I thought I did.
I'm throwing in a load of laundry
if you need some done.
By the way, I'm going camping
with Hiram this weekend.
- I'm leaving this afternoon.
- Great.
I'm doing whites first.
- Fuck. David, David.
- David. David?
David! David?
Are you all right? You look pale.
No, I'm fine.
It's just a headache, that's all.
Okay, you're in this, like, total
danger zone. Gabe Dimas is a dick.
I'm sorry his brother's dead, but
don't think that means he's not a dick.
I just haven't seen him around,
so I was worried.
If you hook up with him now,
it's gonna be like total emotional rape.
Whatever he feels for you is gonna be
wrapped up in some guilt-grief fuckfest.
You better stay away from that shit.
I'm not kidding.
So you failed a test.
Big whoop.
You want to be helpful to the people
that walk in through your door...
...so you have to be
one of those people.
Okay.
I chose three funeral homes
from the yellow pages at random.
I've always felt an uncontrolled sample
group provides more reliable data.
What, you want us to pretend
to be purchasing a funeral?
Look up the first address.
I think it's in Sherman Oaks.
Come on, it'll be fun.
Hello? Gabe?
Is anybody home?
Oh, Mrs. Dimas, I'm sorry.
The door was open.
Is Gabe around?
- We can still leave.
- Why? What are you afraid of?
Humiliating myself,
wasting someone's valuable time.
Don't be so left-brained.
I'm so sorry to keep you waiting.
Now, how can I help?
It's my parents.
They were killed this morning
in an accident.
I'm terribly sorry.
It was a...
A helicopter...
...went down
and there was an explosion.
Oh, God.
I can't do this.
It's not right.
They were in the prime of their lives.
Everybody dies.
We all die.
Everything we ever care
about will disappear.
So, what's the fucking
point of living?
Can I suggest matching caskets?
That's it?
That's what you have to offer me
in my time of grief? Merchandise?
We have nothing
to learn here.
Water purifier.
Rope.
Bear bell.
Flashlight.
Toilet paper.
And, yes, it's biodegradable.
Bird caller.
Binoculars.
I'm sure you have everything. I know
you have everything. You always do.
It wouldn't be fun to get up there and
realize we forgot the matches, would it?
Or the champagne.
Hiram, that's just decadent.
Was it expensive?
We shouldn't waste it.
Waste it?
It's our anniversary.
Claire, you're home early.
You remember Hiram.
Hi.
- How was school?
- I have a headache.
Hiram and I are going camping.
Your dinner's in the refrigerator
and I'll be back tomorrow.
It's a very beautiful
time of the year.
Okay.
Well, you two have fun.
We should probably leave
if we want to beat the rush-hour traffic.
Ruth?
Honey, what's wrong?
My children don't
need me anymore.
Let's think of this as a celebration...
...of your uncle's life.
Now, the Titan is an excellent choice
for a distinguished gentleman.
It's solid mahogany. It's hand-finished.
Burlwood and nickel accents.
And Grace Field...
Grace Field
is a lovely place for interment.
It's serene.
It's pastoral.
How much?
Well, after you sign the contract,
we take care of everything.
There's no worry.
There's no pain.
How much?
It comes to just
under $20,000.
You're charging $ 12,000
for the Titan?
What is that,
like a 300 percent markup?
I could come down to 10.
And Grace Field is in between
a power station and a freeway.
There are nicer cemeteries.
But they're just a little
bit more expensive.
No, thanks.
We'll try and find somewhere that
doesn't just want to swindle us.
Nice tie.
- This business is a total racket.
- What business isn't?
You know, sometimes
I wish I could be this...
...completely selfish asshole
that didn't give a shit about anything...
...and I could just work at some mindless
job that paid me a fuckload of money.
- No, you don't.
- It would make my life a lot easier.
You don't want
your life to be easy.
Gabe?
Hi.
I didn't know if
anybody was home.
Did you ring the bell?
I just... I came by
to drop off this stuff.
Okay.
It's my brother's soccer clothes.
I thought that he might
like to get buried in them.
You think that's okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, I think that's really nice.
I went to your house.
You see my mom?
Yeah.
Just like a zombie.
Just sits there.
I don't know why she blames herself.
It's my fault. I killed him.
Gabe, no.
It was an accident.
It wouldn't have happened
if I'd been watching him.
My mom can't even find Anthony's dad
to tell him what happened.
Probably moved.
We haven't seen him in, like, two years.
Oh, that sucks.
He's a fucking drunken dipshit. He used
to kick my ass just to prove he could.
You know when people would call you
those things like...
..."cemetery girl" and "Vampira"?
Yeah.
I never thought that was funny.
I should go. Would you just
make sure your brother gets these?
Of course.
Hey, look. If you need
anything, like to talk...
...or something,
you can call me.
All right.
- Where do you want to hang the food?
- Can't it wait till after dinner?
I've already taken out what we're
going to eat. I'd rather not risk it.
I'm sorry it's inconvenient...
...but would you prefer we were mauled
in our sleep by bears?
Ruth?
You need to relax.
Hello, I'm Rosemary.
How can I help you?
Hi. I need to make
arrangements for a funeral.
All right.
My wife's in the restroom.
She'll be out in a minute.
- Can I ask who the funeral is for?
- It's for me.
Bet you don't get too many people
shopping for their own funeral.
It happens. Most people who know
they're going to die want to have a say.
Planning it with your husband could be
a meaningful process for you both.
- Is it cancer?
- Yeah.
It's everywhere.
Liver now.
- Brenda.
- My husband hates me doing this.
He wants me to spend this time
doing things I always dreamed of...
...but never gave
myself permission to...
Pardon me.
The coughing blood and pissing needles
thing kind of gets in the way.
- He just wants you to be happy.
- He just doesn't want me to die.
Okay, it's just too fucked up, Brenda.
I can't do it. I can't.
- He's not ready.
- It's hard for him.
Probably harder
than it is for you.
That was the most fucked up
thing you've ever done to me.
- Sorry.
- That was like the shit...
...you pulled on those doctors
to get a rise out of them.
- Are you gonna start barking at me?
- I might.
- What you did just now was not funny!
- Well, it wasn't meant to be.
You counsel people about
death every day, Nate...
...when death is what
you're most afraid of.
- What's wrong with this picture?
- Of course I'm afraid of it.
- What sane person isn't?
- I'm not.
Yeah, well, I said, what sane person.
- Hello.
- Hey.
- Hey, what's up?
- Nothing, I just...
I just wanted to
talk to somebody.
- What are you doing tonight?
- I don't know. What are you doing?
You.
Shit. Fuck! Shit.
- What are you looking for?
- Aspirin.
I know there was a bottle
of aspirin in here.
Yeah, I took some earlier.
You did? Are you okay?
Yeah, why?
You found it, didn't you?
You found it and kept it for yourself.
- What's going on with you?
- Nothing.
You're wearing my shirt.
- Fuck!
- What is this, like a date?
Sort of.
No way, you're dating
the square-dancing guy?
- Weird.
- Weird why?
No, I get it. He's hot in a kind of
generic, Banana Republic kind of way.
- Claire, I really need that aspirin bottle.
- David, I really don't have it.
- What was in there?
- He gave me some pills.
Now I'll have to say, "Sorry, I lost
them because I'm this old-guy geek...
...and I'm completely uncool in this world
in which you seem to thrive...
...you perfect distillation
of human evolution. "
Okay, is this split
personality thing...
...like, something that happens
when Mom goes out of town?
Because I like you
like this way better.
- Dinner was delicious.
- Food just tastes better outdoors.
Remember what we ate
the first time we went camping?
No.
- Pork chops with fire-roasted vegetables.
- Oh, yes.
The sky was so clear that night.
Just like tonight.
Did you know you're not supposed
to go camping if you're menstruating?
- What?
- It's true.
My husband buried
a young woman once.
She went on a camping trip.
She was menstruating.
A bear smelled the blood and
killed her in her sleeping bag.
Killed one of her friends too.
But we only buried her.
Not the friend.
I'm glad we're seeing
each other again.
Me too. It's nice.
- What's wrong?
- I've got a little bit of a headache.
I'm sorry I forgot those pills.
That's no big deal.
You can be my drug tonight.
So, what's with the guy who's been
staring at you since we got here?
Shit! That's Keith.
We dated.
- He's pretty hot. You guys still friends?
- Not really.
- Why not? I'm friends with my exes.
- Why doesn't that surprise me?
He's coming over.
Is he into three-ways?
He's a cop, so don't mention
the drugs or anything.
- Sure, Dad.
- David.
- Keith, hi. How's it going?
- Good. It's going good.
This is the last place
I'd ever expect to see you.
Yeah. Well, it was Kurt's idea.
Kurt, this is Keith.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Kurt teaches square dancing.
Tried to get David to go dancing
when we were together.
Told me he didn't
even like to dance.
Thanks.
- Eddie, this is David and...
- Kurt. Hi.
Hi.
- So how'd you guys meet?
- Eddie's an EMT.
Met on the job.
Newlyweds in a car crash.
He saved the bride
right in front of me.
- What about the groom?
- Didn't make it.
The bride had eternity with the man
she loved right in front of her...
...then you go save her and
she ends up left behind, alone.
That's one way
of looking at it.
Well, it's good to see you.
- Yeah, nice meeting you.
- You too.
Well, of course he's dating
Mr. Fucking Super Guy ER.
I bet they have great sex,
I mean, with the uniforms and all.
I dated a cop once. Total control freak.
Now, firemen on the other hand...
Is dating an excuse for you to figure out
who you wanna be when you grow up?
I don't know.
Is dating like an excuse...
...for you to see who you wished
you'd been when you were my age?
- Let's get out of here.
- Why?
Come on.
David. Wait, David.
Look...
- Who was that?
- Just a guy I know.
He wants to go home with us.
- I don't think so.
- Come on, you'll love him.
- I promise, he's a total fuck machine.
- I said, no.
Why not? Why are you
taking this so seriously?
Because I'm a serious guy.
I bury people for a living.
Well, that shit's in your head.
Yeah, you're right.
That shit is in my head.
Look, go. Have fun. I'm just too...
I'm sorry that I can't...
I'm sorry. Bye.
You really spooked me, Bren.
What?
The idea of me dying?
Well, yeah.
I will die someday.
We die, Nate.
We all die.
Hello?
You certainly took
your sweet time getting here.
- You'll ruin that shirt.
- Who cares?
What, you're hitting on me now?
Two guys aren't enough, you slut?
Oh, dear.
I suppose I owe you an apology.
- Why? I'm dead.
- Yes, but I was seeing Hiram before you...
I was gone long before I died.
You'd like Hiram. He's kind.
He makes me laugh.
- I got my money on the florist.
- Oh, heavens no, Nathaniel.
The man is a complete savage.
Oh, God. This is the hearse
that was always stalling, isn't it?
Remember after that funeral in Malibu
for that jazz musician?
We broke down on the side of the PCH
and we made love in the back.
If this baby could talk.
Nathaniel, what happened to us?
We were so in love once.
Life happened to us.
I buried hundreds of people
and we watched each other grow old.
- But we're not old.
- Well, technically speaking...
...I'm as old as
I'm ever gonna get.
We were such children
when we met.
Then we watched
those children disappear.
Damn it! Stalled again.
Won't go forward. Won't go back.
Well, these can't be helping.
No tears.
- I miss what we had.
- So find it again.
What a beautiful day.
You should have woken me up.
I thought you could use the sleep
after the night we had.
You've never been that
passionate with me before.
Thank you for a wonderful night.
- Last night?
- You were spectacular.
What?
- Do I just sit anywhere?
- Wherever you'd like.
- Nice suit.
- Thank you. Bought it last week.
You need more than one suit
to be a funeral director.
No, you need
to pass a test first.
You just can't let
go of that, can you?
- I failed the first time I took it.
- You did not.
Yes, I did. I fuck up a lot more
than you might think. I fuck up a lot.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- How are you holding up?
- Okay, I guess.
It's just weird.
Why are you being
so nice to me?
- You little bastard!
- Sam, we didn't think you'd show.
- Stop it!
- Stop! Leave him alone!
I'm gonna kill you,
you useless fuck!
Okay, everybody calm down.
Probably wasted out of your mind,
whacking off!
Let my kid shoot himself!
You're gonna blame him?
Where the fuck were you
for the past two years?
All right, just take it easy.
- Everything all right?
- Yeah.
- Don't worry about it, I'll deal with it.
- Thank you.
Who the fuck
was that little bitch out there?
That's my sister.
You should warn her. Gabriel has
been a fuckup his whole life.
When I lived there, he used
to drive his mother nuts...
...with all the shit that he'd do.
Staying out all night.
No fucking responsibility.
- That's my kid who's dead.
- I know.
It was my gun.
I bought it for Vickie.
Because I was gonna leave for a while,
you know? Go up north for a job.
Make some extra money.
How could he let
something like this happen?
It's not right.
It's just not fucking right!
Jesus, he was 6!
Everybody dies.
Some of us live to be 100, some never
make it through the first day.
That's just a fucking
fact of nature, pal.
Who the fuck
do you think you are?
You can punch as many
people as you want.
It's not gonna change
the fact that boy is dead.
And your chance to be
in his life is over.
Did you use that time well
or did you just piss it away?
And your own fucking life
is a ticking clock too.
Everybody's is.
- Mom, you're home. I was worried.
- Worried, why?
- Did you have a good time?
- Oh, David, you must go camping.
It's so spectacular
up there right now.
Spring is such a full time.
So much color, so much detail.
And the smells.
It's like nothing else.
And you're okay?
No sickness, no headaches?
Oh, no.
I had one on the trip...
...but I took some aspirin
and it just disappeared.
Yes, well, aspirin is
damn good stuff.
How was the service?
There was a fight that broke out,
but I let Nate take care of it.
I'm glad you boys are working
so well together now.
Claire, you look terrible.
Are you not feeling well?
I'm just a little wrecked.
We buried my friend's brother today.
He's your friend?
I had no idea.
Yeah.
He's the foot guy.
Oh, my God.
Good night.
There's so much you wish you could
protect your children from.
Night, Mom.
Night, dear.
Subtitles by www. tv-series. nm. ru