So I say to this guy, "I can't do anything
unless you give me an order number.
And I don't appreciate your taking that
tone of voice with me. "
He says he doesn't have
an order number.
And I say, "Well, you should always
write down the order number. "
Then he gets all pissy.
Says he wants to speak to the person
he ordered the Astoria floor lamp from.
And I say, "Well, do you
remember his or her... "
Right, you know? "... name?"
And he says, "Of course not. "
And I say, "Then I'm sorry,
I can't help you. "
He says this isn't the first time
he had a problem ordering from us.
Last Christmas he bought a CD holder,
and it arrived all broken.
When we told him, "Send it back"...
...he couldn't because he'd thrown
away the box it came in.
So I say... I say, "Boo-hoo, mister.
Ain't you got it bad. "
And he says, "I wanna talk
to your supervisor. "
And I say, "Of course
you can talk to him...
...but unfortunately, his hours
are only 8:30... "
So now the wife's in jail, according
to the cousin who arranged the funeral.
I bet he was abusing her. Maybe he had
some sick sexual thing he made her do.
Please, stop.
And you're wrong. All she told
the police was that he was boring.
That's it? That's all she said?
- The sick part is, I understand it.
- I do too.
- Sometimes I'm boring.
- I am too.
I should be at both intakes
with you this morning...
...but you'll have to do
the casket meeting...
...because I'm really backed up
down here.
David, maybe we need to think about
finding a replacement for Rico.
Why? We're doing just fine without him.
It's saving money, thank you very much.
Is there something you'd like to say
about my work?
Look, you do a great job...
...when it comes to people
who had peaceful farewells.
But the big reconstructions,
you're out of your league.
I see, so those who can't do, criticize?
We've got a body
that's a page-one rewrite.
We got two more coming in
from that nightclub fire in Valencia.
- How bad was that fire?
- Well, this is where they ended up.
Maybe the families want...
Open caskets. They already
put in the requests.
- I'll put an ad in the paper today.
- It's taken care of.
I've scheduled some interviews
for this afternoon.
As you can see from my r'esum'e,
I've had the good fortune to study...
...under a variety
of gifted restorative artists.
Oh, you worked over at Hope Valley.
I've known P.T. For years.
Look, that lawsuit about
the unembalmed arm was not my fault.
I took the fall for some bitch that was
supposed to cover me for leaving early.
Sometimes I wake up
with a feeling of panic...
...like my heart's gonna beat
right out of my chest.
You know what I'm talking about. But
after I spend a few extra hours in bed...
...and do my chanting,
the dark time usually passes.
I know it sounds funny,
but the first time I embalmed someone...
...it felt like I was coming home.
I just knew that this is
what I was meant to do.
That doesn't sound funny at all.
There's something very intimate about it.
I'm the last person on earth
who gets to know these people.
Anyway, I guess I take
what I do very seriously.
Well, I have no further questions.
Me neither. Thanks for coming in,
Angela. We'll be in touch.
Great.
It was very nice to meet you.
- It was nice to meet you.
- Yeah.
Okay.
I'll wait an hour before I call her.
We don't wanna look desperate.
Just find out if she can start tomorrow.
David,
David!
Why are you standing there like that?
I was thinking.
Isn't a person allowed to think?
You're gonna wish you'd
gotten high with me.
I told you, I'm never getting high again.
Oh, doesn't Billy look great?
So handsome and confident.
Yo, Billy!
Would you excuse me for one moment?
Thanks for coming. I really appreciate it.
Thank God you're here. My mouth
is really dry, and is my breath bad?
No, it's fine.
So truth. Is this show good,
or is it just pretentious bullshit?
There're so many people,
it's hard to see the pictures.
This is Billy's best work ever,
very disturbing.
- Really?
- I'm so proud of you, God!
Why is my mother here?
Oh, God.
I invited her as part of my ongoing
campaign to get her to like me.
I didn't think she'd actually turn up.
You know that some stranger
just rubbed my ass?
Isn't this fabulous?
Oh, Billy, darling.
Thanks, Mom.
You can't keep him to yourself
all the time.
Okay, no offense, but your family
is fucked up beyond comprehension.
She's completely tanked.
I brought someone.
I hope that's okay.
- Hey, Nikolai.
- Hello, Nate, how are you?
- This is Brenda.
- Good evening.
- Hello, dear.
- It's good to see you, Mrs. Fisher.
- Where's Hiram?
- He's visiting his son in Portland.
I'm serious, darling,
this new stuff is really visceral.
Not at all left-brained like your father.
Yeah. Hey, so where is Dad?
Oh, honey, Bern sends his regrets.
He's just heartsick.
Unfortunately, he's treating
one of his patients...
...who's undergoing a complete
psychotic break at the moment.
That always seems to happen whenever
there's something important in my life.
I guess that's just typical Bernard...
I'm sorry, Bernard Chenowith behavior.
Pretentious dick.
Now, you just hush.
I thought this would be paintings.
I could take photographs.
That doesn't mean they'd be any good.
Mrs. Fisher, I've never seen you
having this much fun.
Oh, no, no, no, it's great.
I am having fun just watching you.
Hey, Mr. Seattle co-op hippie boy.
Oh, Margaret Chenowith. Who are you?
- Ruth Fisher.
- Nate's mother.
That explains why
you're looking at me...
...like I just took a giant dump
on your lawn.
If I knew you were
putting on a show tonight...
...I would've bought tickets
for all my friends.
Goody, there's Dr. Feinberg.
- Hi.
- What is he doing here?
I invited him.
Gareth Feinberg, the guy
who wrote the book?
Yeah, he wrote
Charlotte-fucking-Light and Dark,
He's a fucking evil dead fish
of a fucking Nazi fuck.
Darling, try not to act so adolescent.
It only makes you look bad.
As opposed to being drunk
and slobbering all over my boyfriend...
...who, by the way,
is completely not interested.
Isn't this fun?
Billy, Billy, Billy.
It's quite powerful stuff.
It's... It's potent.
That's a word Dr. Feinberg
likes to use a lot.
Brenda, I see a lot of you
in these photographs.
Hello, Gareth.
Margaret.
Does this have a theme?
I know you like your things
to have a theme.
Mother, nothing is more tedious than
when you look for meaning in my work.
I don't need your fucking approval.
Excuse me.
- Isn't that beautiful?
- Yeah, it is.
He's good.
Yeah, he is really good.
I only wish he'd believe that.
This one's got real attitude.
- Oh, my God.
- The light's spectacular.
Brenda, that is a picture
of me urinating on a wall.
- I realize that.
- Hey, what do you think?
So now you're stalking me?
No, I just saw you one day
when I was taking pictures...
...so I followed you.
- You were just out taking pictures?
You live in Venice! There's no reason
for you to be in my neighborhood.
You think the world revolves around you.
Bren, would you tell him, please,
this isn't about him?
It's what Billy does.
He takes pictures of people
when they're off guard.
- He's got a talent. It's art.
- No, it's fucked!
Thanks a lot.
Look. That's your son
pissing against a wall.
So I should let him humiliate me
whenever he wants?
Oh, God, Nate, don't make this
about you.
Why the fuck not? This is about me.
You make enough stuff all about you.
So what? There's a picture
of you pissing on a wall.
Who got hurt? Who died?
You don't think I have a right
to not be spied upon?
You're talking to someone
who was spied on her whole life.
God, Billy is severely fucked up, Bren.
I don't like being stalked by a psycho.
Billy is not psychotic. He has a disease.
He's fine when he takes his meds.
Yeah, well, when the fuck is that?
Look, has he ever done anything weird?
Yeah, he's bipolar.
His whole life he's been weird.
Has he ever done anything dangerous?
Oh, God. Nate, no.
The only person Billy would ever
be a threat to is himself.
- Has he ever tried to...?
- Yes.
When I was 18.
I went to Europe for three months.
It was this big reward for me
winning a scholarship to Yale.
When I got back to L.A.,
my mother was at the airport.
She told me that Billy
had committed suicide.
My whole life just collapsed
in on itself in that moment.
Of course, she meant to say that Billy
had tried to commit suicide.
She was drunk,
or else it was a Freudian slip.
You never went to Yale.
Billy was in a hospital in Pasadena.
I took some classes at UCLA
in the spring.
Then in the fall, he was diagnosed
manic-depressive...
...which kicks in in adolescence...
...so it probably had nothing to do
with me getting the scholarship.
I can't believe they pressured you into
sacrificing your life for your brother.
Nobody pressured me.
I wanted to stay.
- Morning.
- Morning. Pee on any walls lately?
Shut up.
So, Mom, what's with you and Nikolai?
I don't know what you're talking about.
And Dave, what'd you do last night?
Nothing.
Saturday night, what happened to that...?
Person you're seeing?
That person is no longer in the picture.
Sorry to hear it.
What about you?
- You dating anybody?
- No.
If you are, you don't need
to hide him from us like we're lepers.
I'm not dating anyone. I've just been
hanging out a lot with somebody.
Who is this person?
Nobody.
David, I'm ready to go to church.
Thanks, guys.
- Hey, Joey, the kid's ready,
- So am I,
This is the most terrifying
shower scene since Psycho.
That football game used to make
this obnoxious noise...
...when you scored a touchdown.
Do you wanna show me how to play it?
No.
You know, there's this...
There's this little kid next door...
...and the only toy he's got...
...is this stupid Mousetrap game
from when his mom was a kid.
Maybe, you know, he'd want
some of these.
It's a beautiful day. Why would you
waste your Sunday in here watching TV?
What are you doing?
I thought that Tony Rechner next door
might want some of these.
Just keep your hands off them.
She doesn't even look me
in the eyes anymore.
Come on, I wanna show you
something funny. Come on.
Come on.
We're going on a field trip?
This is like the first day of school.
I am so excited.
Oh, and I just wanna apologize
in advance...
...because I had calamari
last night for dinner.
- What do you mean?
- Let's just say this is one time...
...where the strong smell of
formaldehyde really comes in handy.
So then I said, "I don't care
if you have a low sperm count.
I mean, I'll just shove a turkey baster
up there if I have to. "
I mean, I wanna have a child
before I turn 40. That's fair, right?
Hello, everyone.
Hi. How was church?
Nate told me you're a deacon.
That's adorable.
I see you've made yourself at home.
Angela doesn't like to feel constrained.
Well, you know, my glands
go double-time.
I find if I wear too much while I work,
I get all pitted.
Angela, we're sort of used to a more
professional appearance around here.
Give me a break, David,
they're just nipples.
I mean, we've all seen them.
We've all touched them.
We've all sucked on them. It's not like
this guy will be lying in the casket...
...and people will be saying, "Oh, my
God, the embalmer's nipples were hard. "
They'll be saying, "How did they put
his face back together...
...after he went through
the goddamn windshield?"
I told Father Jack I'd help
with the food distribution downtown.
I just wanted to make sure
that your first day was going okay.
Well, thanks. I'm all gassy,
but that's not your fault.
Angela had calamari last night.
Boy, he's a barrel of laughs.
It's hard when a new person
comes into a situation,
It throws everything off balance.
Bren, I am not threatened
by your boyfriend.
Oh, yeah? Your behavior consistently
communicates otherwise.
You want the picture
out of the show, fine.
But don't spout psychobabble at me
like fucking Margaret and Bernard.
- You're, like, becoming them.
- Fuck you!
You know what you did was wrong.
That's why you didn't show it to me.
- Why are you making it such a big deal?
- Because I love him!
You're fucking with my life, Billy,
and it's not fair.
You have to stop.
- Or what?
- Goddamn it, Billy, what is it with you?
You like fucking with my brain
like Feinberg?
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Can I get you anything else?
I can always use a good blowjob.
Hey, do I get my fucking lunch or not?
- I'm going to get a drink of water.
- Yeah, sure.
Melinda Daner, Mark Whitman...
...Darryl Heinz, Keith Charles.
Okay, well, just tell them we'll meet them
at the usual corner on Tuesday. Okay.
- Hi, Tracy.
- Oh, hi, David.
- How have you been?
- Fine.
I love your new hair.
What are you working on?
St. Stephen's is sending over
some volunteers to help out next week.
Someone told me that you
used to go to St. Stephen's.
Not that I've been asking around
about you. It just came up naturally.
So did you? Go there, I mean.
- Yeah, just for a few months last year.
- They're a very progressive church.
Yes, they are.
The guy who took these
is a total psycho.
It's good.
Well, we should probably get going
if we wanna see that movie.
I should probably get home
and check on my mom.
I'm sure she's doing fine.
I'm sorry.
It's not like I was dying
to see a movie.
That's not what I'm talking about.
I'm sorry...
...about what happened between us.
I never meant for those assholes
to write shit on your car.
I shouldn't have told Andy about us.
I was just being stupid. That was me
being really, really, really stupid...
...and I'm sorry.
Well, thank you.
Look, I don't wanna make
a big deal out of this.
All I'm saying is,
I sat around last week...
...in that stupid getup
you wanted me to wear...
...and had to say all this, you know,
"Daddy this" and "Daddy that" bullshit.
When I tell you I keep reading articles
about having this one-hour orgasm...
...well, the least you could do
is try to help me have one.
I'm sorry men can't have it.
Since you guys get everything else
on the planet...
...it seems like a fair tradeoff.
Fine.
Goodbye.
You know, Angela, my brother
likes a certain decorum...
...when you're working
with someone's loved one.
Yeah?
Well, the personal calls are
probably a little uncool.
Oh, right, got it.
I won't do it when he's around.
Hello.
Hey.
Really?
Why don't you want me to come over?
Damn it, Brenda, you always do this.
You're shutting me out.
Look, the pissing thing is
no longer an issue, I swear.
Look, maybe you'd feel better
if I came over.
All right, fine, whatever. Fine.
- Girlfriend trouble?
- Not really trouble.
Tell me what the fight was about,
and I'll tell you what to say to fix it.
I mean, trust me, this is my thing.
We didn't have a fight.
She just pulls away from me
at the weirdest times.
Well, maybe she senses that
you're pulling away...
...so she just does it first.
Maybe you should
mind your own business.
Shoot. I guess this means
I can't ask about the pissing?
Because I had an ex who wanted to pee
on me, and I wasn't grossed out.
I mean, I just thought it was
kind of silly. But that's me.
Thank you for taking me to
the art gallery last night.
I thought you hated those pictures.
No, no, it's just that I don't
like them, that's all.
But it was nice to be
spending time with you.
I mean, outside of working together.
Would you like to go
to dinner sometime?
- Is that like a date?
- Of course not.
Good, I pick you up
tomorrow night, 8:00.
I don't wanna go, okay?
Just stop asking me.
Okay, fine. I was only inviting you
to be nice.
Nobody even wants you there because
you've been acting so weird lately.
Gabe?
- We have to be someplace.
- Get lost, Morticia.
Shut up, peanut-testicle.
Fuck off, the both of you.
What's his problem?
Nothing. He wants me to go to this party
tomorrow. I'm just not in the mood.
We can do something if you want.
Actually, I gotta go to Barstow tomorrow
and spend the night at my dad's.
I gotta ask him for money for my mom.
Not that he's gonna give it to me, but...
Well, do you want company?
Claire, you don't have
to keep taking care of me.
I'm not.
I just like hanging out.
We could just go for the drive.
Then you go see your dad...
...and I'll stay in some, like, creepy motel
and read a Stephen King book.
Okay.
Meet me after fifth period
tomorrow by the gym.
Oh, this is just what I need today.
I see this is payback time
for my missing your opening.
Just shut up!
Both of you, for once,
just shut your fucking mouths.
All that comes out of you
is garbage, garbage, garbage!
Okay.
Good, we have a dialogue.
- Where did you get this?
- From his office.
It's all the data Feinberg has
on Brenda. It's all destroyed.
He can go to where he came from
before he fucked her up.
You're off the hook. Obviously, this has
nothing to do with you missing his show.
Don't fucking talk about me
like I'm not here!
Even though I'm not
and never have been.
Son, what's wrong? Just tell us.
There's nothing wrong with me.
I didn't sell my daughter to some smug,
star-fucking psychiatrist...
...so he could pick her apart
like a goddamn cadaver...
...and turn her into shit and garbage
just like everything you touch!
- Billy, sweetheart...
- You bitch!
You're the fucking nurse. You wanna tie
us up, lock us in a room, leave us to die.
Well, you're the one that should die,
you and him!
You don't get to touch the children.
I refuse to be an audience for this.
Oh, boy. You can juice her, but you
better let me take care of that skin.
This guy has a really sinewy neck.
Sinewy. I love saying that word,
don't you?
- I don't know.
- I went out with this guy once...
...he had a really sinewy neck.
He was a total animal in bed.
I mean, the things he could do
with his tongue.
He thought he was God's gift to women.
I guess in that one respect he was.
- So do you like sinewy necks, David?
- I never really thought about it.
Hey, I'm just trying to figure out
your type.
Believe me, I can tell you're single.
And I know about a million people
I can set you up with.
So, what kind of guys do you like?
What makes you think that I like men?
Oh, please, let's not play that game.
- I think we should fire her.
- I'm thinking the same thing.
- Has she made a lot of mistakes?
- No.
She's a little hard to take.
She's a lot hard to take.
Sometimes people are hard to take...
...but only because the first side they
present is annoying or aggressive...
...because they're nervous.
After you spend some time
with them...
...you realize maybe there's another side
to them that's worth knowing.
Or not. I have no idea
what I'm talking about.
Sorry I'm late.
By the way, I won't be here for dinner
tomorrow, so everyone's on their own.
Actually, I'm going to be volunteering
with the food distribution.
Well, that leaves you and me, Claire.
You wanna go to the Apple Pan?
Can't. I have to do
this astronomy overnight thing...
...at the observatory for school.
- I didn't hear about this.
I told you.
You probably weren't listening.
That's the type of thing I would listen to.
David and Nate did it
when they went to Bonaventure.
David, you did this?
- Yeah, I had to.
- You too, Nate?
Back then we thought
Pluto was a planet.
- When did Pluto stop being a planet?
- A few months ago.
Well, I suppose it's okay for you to go.
Luckily, Gareth isn't going
to press charges.
But I did promise him that steps
would be taken to remedy the situation.
I wish I'd been there to see
the look on Feinberg's face.
I'm sure he started with
his whole blinking thing.
Brenda, we have a serious problem.
Okay, I'll talk to Billy's doctor, see if
he needs to be on different medication.
We were thinking of something
a little more involved.
Your mother and I feel that he needs
to go away for intensive therapy.
There's a very good facility in Colorado.
You wanna put Billy in an institution?
Oh, please, let's not turn this
into a 1950s B-movie.
This place is run
by excellent psychiatric specialists...
...who may have some creative solution
to help Billy.
You wanna give him shock treatment.
Darling, really, this dramatic streak,
aren't you a little old for it?
And just for the record, electroconvulsive
therapy's had a real resurgence...
...in the last 10 years
with very impressive results.
- You can't do this.
- We think it's best.
It certainly makes your lives easier.
God forbid Billy should embarrass you in
front of your stupid celebrity friends.
Unfortunately, he's an adult
which means you can't...
...have him committed
unless he does something dangerous.
Darling?
We were thinking if you talked to him,
explained how it would help him...
Fuck you both.
You're out of your minds.
Hi, I'm Angela. You must be Ruth.
Yes.
I spilled some beet salad
on someone's wig...
...so David said I should eat up here.
I got the stains out.
Everyone in my family gets cancer,
so I know tons about taking care of wigs.
Is that yours? The hair, I mean.
As far as I know.
It's beautiful.
Thank you.
I don't wanna be one
of those menopausal women...
...that goes all dykey
with the butch haircut.
So Nate says that
you're dating a hairdresser.
That is so lucky.
If he's good, I'd love to know
if he can do anything with this mop.
Does your boyfriend come around?
He's not exactly my boyfriend.
Oh, come on, you're blushing.
Must be pretty serious. Is it?
Is it serious, or is it just hot sex?
I'm really not in the mood
to discuss my personal life.
You have one new message,
Hey, it's me,
Look, it's better if I just go by myself,
You should probably just
not worry about it, okay?
Thank you for trying to... To...
Look, just... Thank you,
So that's... That's it, I guess,
Goodbye, Claire,
This is disgusting.
You have crap in here from the '80s.
Billy, I'll get a plumber, somebody
who actually knows what they're doing.
Would you look at me?
I'd really like to talk to you.
I take it you spoke to Mom and Dad.
Look, I don't know what
happened that day.
You know, I was on new meds.
They weren't working.
It wasn't my fault.
But don't worry. I've already been
to my doctor and changed my dosage.
And I already feel more even.
Billy, I need to know if I should be
worried about you.
You shouldn't.
I swear.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
My God, you could eat off this skin.
Angela does her job perfectly.
What about the hairs in her mole?
Rico would've never left those there.
Angela had a long philosophical debate
about it...
...and decided the nieces would wanna
remember her exactly how she was.
I'd like to know the meaning of this.
Nikolai is picking me up
to go to dinner...
...and I was planning to serve him
sherry beforehand.
I wanted to use the goblets I got
from my cousin Hannah's trip to Dresden.
Now I can't because someone broke this
and hoped I wouldn't notice it.
- Which one of you did this?
- It wasn't me.
Well, it wasn't me.
- It was Angela.
- Oh, it was definitely Angela.
Hi.
David. What are you doing here?
I volunteer with these guys
a couple times a week.
Oh, I just started.
- You need some help?
- Yeah, sure.
David. David!
- David.
- I'm dying.
No, you can't, not before we
make love one last time.
Okay.
I thought you were gonna help.
- So how've you been?
- Good. You?
I'm okay.
I've driven by hundreds of times,
but I never knew this place existed.
Is best restaurant in all of Los Angeles,
and not outrageous prices too.
- Lotte, Irina.
- What a surprise this is.
You usually do not come in
on Tuesday night.
- Well, I...
- Can we join you?
Please.
Maybe another time.
No, no, she says it's okay.
So you must be Nicky's special friend
we all keep hearing about.
You must be thinking of someone else.
No. You lost your husband.
You work for Nicky.
You used to fix dead people.
Oh, I suppose that is me.
This is Ruth.
So that guy I saw you with
at the club, is that a serious thing?
Eddie?
Not really. Not yet.
Those drugs I saw you taking,
is that a serious thing?
No, no. I just tried them once.
I don't think I'll be trying them again.
I'm glad to hear you say that.
You know what that shit
has done to my sister.
It can seriously fuck up your life, David.
I'd hate to see that happen.
It was stupid, I know. I was just...
You know, Rico left.
It was just Nate and me.
Not that it's an excuse.
What's up with that kid
I saw you with at the club?
Let's just say it was
a learning experience.
Everyone else has gone home. I don't
know what you two are waiting for.
David, this isn't one
of your regular shifts.
Is there any special reason
you showed up here tonight?
No.
Oh, well...
Well, good night, you two.
Good night.
You hungry?
I'm always hungry.
You fucking bitch!
I would like to tear your heart out
like you have torn out mine.
There's supposed to be a picture
of Nate peeing on a wall.
- I see it.
- I don't.
Four from the left.
Oh, my God.
What'd your mom say
when she saw that?
She was kind of horrified, I think.
How is your mom?
She's dating. It's weird.
- Why?
- Because she's my mother.
She's not supposed to date.
People should be with people.
Yeah, sometimes people are
just too stupid to know it.
How's your taco?
Disgusting.
I had no idea about you and Nikolai.
For six years, every Saturday night,
I cook for him dinner.
And then he take me
to a $2.50 movie on Fairfax.
Then you come along,
and he stop calling.
I have to see every goddamn film
this Freddie Prinze Jr. Does...
...and what do I have to show for it?
I'm sorry.
Do you want to marry Nicky or not?
Marriage is the last thing
I would ever want again.
Maybe I have an amusing flirtation
with Nikolai...
...but he scares me.
Best of all, I have this job...
...something I never would have
predicted for myself.
And I love it...
...because it's mine.
And I would never do anything
to jeopardize that...
...which means I should probably just
finish dinner with Nikolai...
...and go home.
Thank you. I've had the best time
coming to this funny restaurant...
...and having you yell at me
in the bathroom.
Do you realize the whole time
we were going out...
...I was never in your bedroom at night?
- Well...
...you're here now, aren't you?
Whoa, this is not the David I know.
Maybe this is the real me.
- I'm not sure we should...
- Why not?
Well, I'm kind of seeing somebody
right now.
- I don't care.
- Well, I do.
Come on, David!
Why'd you come up here,
if you weren't into something happening?
To talk to you, to see how you
were doing, to be friends.
- I don't wanna be friends. I wanna fuck.
- Well, I'm not into that.
Can't we just have sex?
It doesn't have to mean anything.
It's getting late.
I should just go.
You take care of yourself.
Claire, what are you doing here?
I thought David and I covered for you,
so you could be out having fun.
What's wrong?
Shit, there's this really big hole
in my sock.
- Maybe Gabe just wanted to be alone.
- I know.
- Is he your boyfriend?
- No.
It's just...
...he needs me.
For the first time in my life, I felt
important, like someone needed me...
...you know, like, not just like some
annoying extra person...
...just lumped in with everyone else.
No one's ever needed me.
I need you.
Right.
I felt this really intense connection.
Now it's just gone.
And I want it back.
I want him back.
Is there something wrong with me?
Is there something about me that makes
me deserve something like this?
Deserve what?
Just feeling really close to someone
then having them just disappear...
...like I mean nothing.
Claire, Gabe just went to visit
his father for a day.
I think you're talking about Dad.
Look, we never talk about him.
And that's okay, if that's what you want.
But at some point you're gonna
have to deal with how you feel.
Oh, God, can't I just get upset...
...without having to focus on
what's really making me upset?
Well, it worked for me for 34 years.
Hey.
Hey, who's this?
Jim. Who's this?
Steve, So, what do you look like?
I'm 6'2", 190 pounds.
I'm a professional boxer.
- Yeah? What's your dick like?
- Nine and a half inches, uncut.
- So, what are you looking for?
- A nasty top to fuck my brains out,
Found him. Now, get on your knees
and suck my cock, boy.
Oh, fuck, Yes, sir, Oh, yes,
I don't care what time it is,
I need to be with someone,
Someone, that's comforting.
Okay, I wanna talk to you.
If this is about Billy, I can't.
I've done nothing but talk about Billy
for two days.
Well, what's happening with him?
Look...
...I know this is really hard for you.
I've had some time to calm down
about the picture...
...so you can just spill your guts
to me, okay?
I promise not to make it about me.
I'm too tired.
You know what?
I love you, and I need you.
And it's okay for you to need me too.
I want you to need me.
I'm doing the best I can.
Rough night, stud?
You're fired.
Fuck.
Yoo-hoo, Brenda!
Brenda, I know you're home.
Your car's out front.
I don't know what's so strange about
a spontaneous brunch. I think it's fun.
It's weird.
You don't do things like this.
You pay people to do things like this.
- Oh, hello, Nate.
- Hey.
Now I see why you're so upset
that I'm here.
My mother's come over to see
if I talked Billy into committing himself.
She just loves saying that. It makes her
father and I sound more like monsters.
Well, I didn't do it, and I'm not going to.
Goddamn it!
I asked for chives,
and they give me this veggie crap.
Brenda...
...there's something
you don't know about Billy.
Oh, here we go.
You know when you were
in Europe that summer?
Billy didn't try to kill himself.
What?
Your father and I had gotten back from
a conference to find our house on fire.
It started right below the family room.
Remember, we had it redone
when you were away?
Yeah, but Billy was...
I went to visit him in the hospital.
He was there all summer.
Your father and I put him there.
We had no choice.
That fire wasn't accidental, Brenda.
He was making a bomb.
This is getting really fucking desperate.
What, now Billy's the Unabomber?
He had written things. Ugly, violent
things about your father and me...
...about you. He was dangerous.
You let me believe for all these years
that Billy tried to kill himself.
We were only trying
to protect you, honey.
Get out of my house.
Get out of my house,
you fucking lunatic!
- It's a wonder I'm even alive.
- Hello?
- You're like fucking Medea!
- Dave, this is a really bad time.
You know what the really
sick thing is, Mother?
You have no idea
what you've done to me.
Brenda.
- Brenda, hang on.
- I'll call you later, Nate...
...when that asshole's out of my house.
Dave, I gotta go.
What, you fired her already?
Oh, for chrissake.
You should've lined up somebody.
Why are you whispering?
I'm hiding up here
until she finishes Mrs. Sarno.
So which of those other people
did you like best?
Look, let's not make
any quick decisions.
I guess I could probably live
with the panic-attack guy.
I've got a better idea,
Hey, Rico.
Bad time?
No, everyone's at lunch
except me and Pam.
You're one of the Fishers, aren't you?
Cigarette break.
But I gotta be back in 10...
...because I told Gilardi I'd have
this one done when he got back.
The subscriber you've called
is outside the service...
Oh, great. Fucking hell.
Here, let me help you.
Shit.
I don't know why I brought
so much stuff here.
I guess I'm just a nester.
I should've told you
that I broke the goblet.
- It was a gift from my cousin.
- Yeah, trip to Dresden. I heard.
I don't know why I didn't just tell you.
It's totally unlike me.
I usually just say whatever I'm thinking.
I noticed.
But I saw that broken glass...
...and I just was overcome
with this feeling that it was...
...better to just ignore it...
...just pretend that it didn't happen.
I get that feeling...
...from all of you here.
Everyone is so fragile...
...and can't bear to hear anything.
Is that everything?
I mean, all I did was try
to fix David up with this guy...
...and I thought he was gonna kill me.
I never met anyone...
...who was so uptight about being gay.
Thanks.
You know something?
I never worked in a funeral home
that was this depressing.
Tell me you're happier here, and I'll go.
It's not perfect. These body farms
are a fucking assembly line.
And I've got like 12 idiots
breathing down my neck.
At Fisher & Sons you only get
two of those at the most.
And Gilardi lied to me.
My hours are nothing
like he said they'd be.
And the work here is not even
as challenging, you know?
Nate...
...it was Kroehner who burned down
the house across the street.
Gilardi's told people that he's not done
trying to drive you guys out of business.
Does that mean it doesn't make sense
for you to come back?
No, but if I do, you have to match
what I'm making here...
...plus guarantee me flexible hours
for picking up Julio...
...and helping when the baby comes.
- Done.
And if I do decide to come back...
...it's not for good.
I'm never gonna become a partner, am I?
I can't offer you that...
...unless you wanna marry Claire.
No, thank you.
Okay, I can start in a couple of days.
Thank you. That makes me very happy,
and it will make David very happy.
Yeah. Hey, I heard there's some picture
of you in a gallery peeing.
Is that true?
I just wanted to get Gabe's father's
number, so I could talk to him.
Well, why would Gabe's stepfather
know where Gabe was?
No, his father, the one
who lives in Barstow.
Yeah, Gabe's father died
when he was 4.
Yeah.
Oh, if you should run into Gabe...
...would you tell him I really don't
appreciate his staying out all night?
So that's... That's it, I guess,
Goodbye, Claire,
Mrs. Dimas?
Mrs. Dimas? Mrs. Dimas?
Subtitles by www. tv-series. nm. ru