Hi, Mom. And Paul and Patricia.
Well, I'm here.
It's not exactly the Holiday Inn,
as you can see.
Mostly... Mostly we're filling sandbags
and cleaning vehicle filters.
In this war, it's important
to keep the mechanisms clean...
...because of all the sand,
which can be as much of a threat...
...as any missile that Saddam can send,
Capt. Sommers says.
I can't say much, but pretty soon
we're gonna get into the real action...
...and we're well-prepared, I'll tell you.
Guys, can you...? Do you mind?
I'm sending this home to my folks.
I'll be done in a minute! Just...
I'm sorry.
What else?
We're protecting your ass, folks!
I love you, America. Thank you!
Bailey, come on, I'm just...
- You want to say hello to Victor's folks?
- Hi, Mom!
Come on, you guys, damn it!
Sorry, Mom,
Some of these guys are kind of crazy,
They're good soldiers,
I'm getting a lot of responsibility here,
I think it's been very beneficial, in terms
of personal leadership skills...
...and getting a job,
A lot more than had I stayed at home,
Well, I've got a lot to do before
lights out, so until next time...
...this is Pvt, 1st Class
Victor Kovitch signing off,
Hey, buddy,
brought you the latest South Park,
Fuck, David.
Hey, sleepyhead.
You know, I had the weirdest dream.
- Really?
- Yeah.
This guy comes into my house
at, like, 4 a. m.
He climbs into my bed,
but instead of having his way with me...
...he just passes out!
And all night long, he keeps jerking.
That is weird.
- And he talked in his sleep.
- Yeah, what did he say?
It was completely unintelligible,
but angry.
- There was even teeth-grinding.
- Well, that explains the headaches.
I was thinking that exposure
to formaldehyde gives me a brain tumor.
Would you like some caffeine
with that tumor?
Okay.
- David, I can't.
- Why not?
Because last night, I drove Mr. Senopolis'
body to San Jose, then straight back.
I barely got four hours' sleep,
and frankly...
...I'm tired of getting the shitty jobs
you don't want.
- I'm half-owner of the business,
- You can't legally do intake without me.
You're not a licensed funeral director.
- I'm getting my license next month,
- If you pass the test.
Thanks for the vote of confidence.
How am I supposed to study
for that test on four hours' sleep?
Coffee and diet pills worked for me.
I can't pick her up,
I've got a deacon's meeting...
...and Rico's got Vanessa's ultrasound.
- Shit,
Last time I picked somebody up
at a nursing home...
...nobody told the roommate
she was dead. I had to.
Just be thankful we've got the business.
Just thankful I'm not you.
What?
Oh, it's Mr. Senopolis, sorry.
Fuck, I smell like a dead guy!
No, you smell fine. Your life stinks,
you complain all the time...
...and that's really dull.
- Didn't realize I was boring you.
- Nate, you need to take a break.
Some major stress release that's not me.
It's too much responsibility.
I thought you liked being
an undertaker's girlfriend.
Is that what I am to you?
Your girlfriend?
I like to think of you as my mistress.
Well, then, you better start
buying me a lot more shit, mister.
God, I love you.
Okay.
I said it. Let's just move on.
Let's go to Two Bunch Palms
this weekend.
- What?
- Fuck it, yes.
I'm gonna take the weekend off,
and David can bite me.
- This weekend?
- Yeah, we'll sit in hot mud...
...we'll get massages,
we'll eat like pigs, we'll drink a lot.
If we leave Friday night,
we can be naked for two whole days.
- I got three clients this Saturday.
- Well, postpone, cancel, lie.
Come on, we've never taken
a trip together. We need to do this.
Two whole days?
- What if we drive each other crazy?
- Well, we don't.
Hovering.
Claire, I've invited a friend of mine
over for dinner tonight.
- Okay.
- And I want you to be nice to him.
Is this the guy?
- The guy that...?
- Yes.
Okay.
Thanks for your patience, everybody.
I know we're running late.
By the way, I spoke to Father Clark
this morning. He's holding up well.
He says you folks are the most thorough
search committee...
...he has ever encountered.
David, I understand you're the last one
to meet with him.
- This afternoon.
- Good.
We've been interviewing
associate priests for three months.
It'll be nice to have an open mind.
Clark struck me as a player, man of God,
wants to listen, but there's ego there.
You didn't want Jack.
Connie, you say that so easily,
and you know it's not true.
I've never seen you so desperate.
Listen, you folks have to represent
the whole congregation.
And believe me, if Clark's not right...
...I'm ready to start from the beginning.
- Let's vote right now.
You know him, David. He's been
a visiting rector. You've got his r'esum'e.
All the deacons are here. You can vote
now. I'll be happy to leave the room.
No, I want to meet
with Father Clark myself...
...so I can make
the most informed decision.
This how it works? You bring in
the new-generation deacon...
...the new deacon brings in
the radical priest you want?
I can assure you there's
no agenda here, Mr. Kriegenthaler.
Except yours.
Don't worry, Dave. I had a parish
in Ohio where punches got thrown.
Steelworkers.
St. Bart's doesn't even come close.
Actually, David,
your father was against Jack here.
And as I said at the time,
your father was wrong.
Roll over,
Okay, okay.
There you go, there you go.
Shit! Fuck, Billy!
- Fuck you!
- I've seen pictures on the Internet, but...
The rule is, you call before
you come over, okay?
Sorry, I was biking down the boardwalk.
I didn't have my cell phone.
Good morning, Nate.
Bill.
I got some great shots of these hookers
on Sunset I want to show you.
Real human tragedy shit.
I think they're really good.
Well, your mom walked in on us once...
...so I guess we're even.
This chick has seen
the fucking worst life has to offer.
- Jesus, Billy, these are incredible.
- And what is that thing on her neck?
She's got, like, this big tumor,
and she's still turning tricks.
And you just know there is some freak
for whom that is a big turn-on.
I love the Bank of America
in the background.
- Well, I have to go to work.
- Bring out your dead!
They're great.
Don't forget,
cancel those appointments on Saturday.
See you later.
So, what's Saturday?
We're going to California Cactus World
out on Rosemead Boulevard.
I want to get something really weird
to plant out back.
- Yo, Dave!
- In here!
I'm sorry, there was an accident
on the 405. Both cars totaled.
I should've handed out cards.
This is Paul Kovitch.
His brother, Victor, just passed away.
- I'm sorry.
- This is my brother, Nate.
Paul Kovitch,
you went to Bonaventure High.
- Yeah.
- I was there when you pinned that guy...
...and won the wrestling championship.
You were the man!
Me and my friends were jealous
because we knew you were getting laid.
- You wrestle?
- No, played baseball, but we always lost.
- So, what are you doing now?
- I run Kovitch Trucking up in Camarillo.
Why, so you know how expensive
you can be?
- No...
- Paul and I were just going over...
...the options for his brother's funeral.
Okay, I run a business too.
Let's just cut right to it.
- Of course.
- I buried both my parents...
...and, no offense,
but I hate you guys. I hate what you do.
The whole thing of "let's gather
and look at this plastic...
...dead version of our loved one. "
It's really twisted.
I want Victor cremated.
No coffin.
Put him in one of those cardboard boxes
you charge 100 bucks for.
I'll take him up to where
our mother's buried up in Tehachapi...
...and let his ashes blow away.
I see Victor's a veteran. If you like, we
can research benefits he might be due.
No, Vic hated the Army. Me and him
been fighting the Army for seven years.
His unit cleaned up a place
called Bunker 73 in the Iraqi desert.
Chemicals all over,
Saddam's stuff we blew up.
As soon as he came back, he got sick.
Lung cancer at the age of 29,
never smoked a day in his life.
Still, no one will say the words
"Gulf War Syndrome. "
He just wasted away
in and out of that hospital.
So fuck the Army.
Let them keep their fucking money.
I gotta fly up to Idaho Falls
to tell my stepfather.
He's got Alzheimer's.
I don't know if he'll hear me or not.
You're absolutely sure
you wouldn't like the opportunity...
...to say goodbye to Victor before...?
- I already said goodbye.
Just do it.
And as for a receptacle
for his cremains...?
A paper sack ought to do just fine.
Nine hundred bucks.
Well, he obviously doesn't
know about the Poseidon Society...
...or that's 900 we'd be out of.
That guy was the shit
when I was in high school.
You know,
I never knew he had a brother.
It's time you introduced yourself.
He's at the VA Hospital.
First, I just gotta talk to you
about something.
It's out of the question. I cannot spare
you. We have three bodies right now.
Mr. Jacobsen's going
into the ground tomorrow...
...and Vic Kovitch
will be toast by the weekend.
What if we get another body? Or two?
We cannot afford to turn down business.
- No, I'm sorry.
- I don't need your permission.
Do you know how long it's been
since I've had two days off?
See, here's the difference.
You're willing to live like that, I'm not.
I've invited my friend Hiram Gunderson
over to dinner tonight.
You're welcome to join us.
Wouldn't a restaurant be better?
This is our home.
This is my home.
Oh, the camping guy. Okay.
Can I bring Brenda?
Hiram will be cooking.
He spent 17 years
as a top chef in Chicago.
The critic of the Sun-Times called him
the "father of the new rustic cuisine. "
And then, he gave it all up
to become a hairdresser.
And he has never been happier!
You're multiplying differing variables,
so you have to simplify.
Okay, and then finally,
oops, look at that.
Same variable, okay?
Four and four gives us what?
Eight! And finally, these two binomials...
...right here, are exactly the same...
...so we what?
Combine!
Two X to the third,
Y to the fourth.
Okay?
Any questions?
Claire Fisher.
What?
Can you explain this formula
to the class?
Not really.
Maybe if you paid attention
instead of reading.
Maybe if you talked about something
that was gonna be useful to me, I would.
Oh, algebra is useless?
I know a lot of physicists
who'd beg to differ.
Well, I don't want to be a physicist.
Algebra forces your mind
to solve problems logically.
- It's one of the only perfect sciences...
- You think the world runs on logic?
- Come on, open your eyes.
- I'll see you after class, Miss Fisher.
What are you doing?
All right, now let's try another one,
and I'm gonna make this a little tougher.
Okay, X to the A power
times Y to the B power.
Okay, now we've got two...
Of course we have catalogs
for wedding package...
...but you have to come in and look.
I can't show you over the phone.
Website? What website?
We don't have website.
Mister, you have to come into my shop
and look at my work.
Website.
- The day just gets brighter.
- Hush.
So who's dead now,
and what do you need?
Nobody's dead.
I came to return these vases.
You should recycle them,
save a little money.
So thoughtful. I am touched.
Don't be silly. It's wasteful, that's all.
Here.
- You still have that sign in the window.
- Yes, you know somebody good?
- I do. Me.
- You?
I am interested. Let's talk.
Robbie, I going to lunch.
I'm not going to lunch with you, Nikolai.
I'm seeing someone.
- So what? This is business.
- I hope so.
- Because otherwise, I withdraw my offer.
- Tell me, why I should hire you?
I've been working with people for
30 years, and I treat them with respect.
I respect people too.
You're pompous and arrogant
and you're full of yourself.
- You act like the customer needs you.
- Of course the customer needs me.
- I have what he wants.
- You'll never build a business that way.
I'm better with people
and I know about flowers.
If you don't think so,
you can fire me.
Fire you? How I can fire you?
You don't even work yet.
My parish in New Mexico,
I think they were afraid of me.
- They recommend you highly.
- They always do after I'm gone.
I won't lie to you, David,
I'll push for some change at St. Bart's.
This is one of those congregations
that thinks sitting through church...
...absolves them of moral responsibility
and they can ignore the plight of others.
Don't get me wrong,
they're good people.
They're just lazy.
I don't think that's entirely fair, Clark.
We have a homeless outreach...
You know you're the swing vote.
I've been a deacon three weeks. I'm still
getting used to how political this is.
Religion is politics, David.
Jesus was a revolutionary.
He threatened those in power,
and they had him assassinated.
They'd do the same thing
to him today.
I'm not sure how much luck you'll
have getting St. Bart's to stage a coup.
The last thing that God
wants from us is complacency.
- You should be in the Peace Corps.
- Already done it.
Three years in Nicaragua,
fresh out of divinity school.
That's where I lost my wife.
I'm sorry.
The hardest part about my work
is the fact...
...that most people don't want
a real relationship with God.
Sure, they'll pray
to a man nailed to a cross...
...but they'll ignore the gay kid
who gets strung up...
...or the black man
who gets dragged behind a car...
...or someone's mother living in a box.
Were you this forthcoming
with the other deacons?
Hardly.
What did you and Walter Kriegenthaler
talk about?
Golf.
So why did you decide
to be so honest with me?
Because I can tell that right and wrong
actually matter to you.
Fuck.
This is medieval. We gotta get it fixed
before somebody loses a finger.
You never cared until it was your finger.
- Rico, a little help?
- Why should I?
You know, it's because of you I'm gonna
work double shifts this weekend.
That's just David being dramatic.
We'd have to get at least two new
bodies for that to be necessary.
They come in bigger numbers than that.
Just forget it. I know the score.
It's never gonna be
Fisher & Sons & Diaz. I know that.
- Let's see what we got.
- This one's a cremation.
- Nothing for you.
- Oh, fuck, what is that?
Shouldn't just burn people
like they're garbage.
What the...?
Look, it came with fries.
Look at this.
Doesn't even look like the same guy,
does it?
This says he applied to be buried
at the National Cemetery.
He signed requests
for a flag fold, military escort.
Oh, man.
Then you can't burn him.
I can make him look like that again.
Well, almost.
You could ace algebra, Claire,
and we both know it.
"Power rests on the kind
of knowledge one holds. "
What's the use of knowing
something useless?
- Don't quote Castaneda at me.
- Why not? You quote Bob Dylan at me.
- You need algebra for college.
- You're assuming I'm going to college.
You're taking the PSAT tomorrow.
That means you're thinking about it.
Is that the only option? Go to college,
get a job, be a good consumer...
...until you drop dead of exhaustion.
I don't want that!
So, what do you want?
I just want something to matter.
Maybe I should wander around the desert
and eat peyote and see God.
Yeah, be a homeless drug addict.
You'd get bored with that pretty fast.
Hey, have you heard
of the Sierra Crossroads program?
What's that, like,
bungee jumping for Jesus?
No, no, it's not affiliated with any
religion. It's actually a great program.
I spent a couple of years there
as an instructor.
- I think you might really like it.
- Why?
Because it would get you out of yourself,
get you out of your head.
Now, I'll warn you,
it's hard but exhilarating.
It might give you the challenge
you're looking for.
There's an expedition over spring break.
I could pull some strings,
see if I could get you in.
- Why do you care what happens to me?
- Because I like you.
And I want to see good things
happen for you, and I know they can.
We had to dig his service records
out of St. Louis.
Then there's the question of whether
his cancer was service related.
That means finding a doctor
who thinks it was.
It took me four months
to get all the approvals...
...but it means a burial allowance
of up to 1500 from the VA.
Might as well take that stuff too.
I packed it up for him.
That's too bad nobody
told his brother what he wanted.
I did.
Oh, yeah. I gave Paul the forms.
I found them later in the trash.
It's mostly somebody else's writing
on the forms.
It doesn't match Victor's signature at all.
I filled them out for him.
He tried to do it himself,
but those boxes are pretty small...
...and he shook a lot.
Gulf War Victory Parade?
Victor said marching in it
was the proudest moment of his life.
Why would he keep it and watch it
over and over if he hated the Army?
- Did Paul visit him much?
- Yeah, three or four times a week.
He was really good about it.
- So how come he...?
- He couldn't.
Paul would say,
"The fucking Army stole your life, Vic. "
And Vic would keep his mouth shut.
I can tell you this.
Victor wanted to believe that what
he did in the Gulf meant something...
...that his life was not a waste.
I only counsel. I'm not supposed
to interfere with what the family wants.
So you taped his medals to him, fished
his files out and passed them to me.
Well, you can always blow it off.
I mean, you didn't
even know the guy, right?
What are you doing?
There was a form that said
he's getting a military funeral.
- Who authorized this? Nate?
- Yeah.
How many times have I told you...
...when Nate gives you instructions,
check with me?
Turn him off.
I'll drive him
to the crematorium right now.
Do I have to do it myself?
Fucking Nate. Paul Kovitch
is who our contract is with...
...and if he finds out about this,
he will either sue us or break our legs.
- Tomatoes right there.
- Okay.
- Look who's here.
- Hello, Mrs. Fisher.
Hello, dear.
- Hello, I'm Brenda.
- Hiram Gunderson.
I understand you like to camp.
Why, yes, I do.
I wish I could tell you where Nate is,
but I have no idea.
It's okay. I can exist without him.
- Toasted sesame seeds in the salad?
- Yes, that would be lovely.
There's my little girl.
Claire, honey, this is Hiram Gunderson.
Pleasure to meet you, Claire.
Hi.
This is delicious, Mrs. Fisher.
Hiram is a chef.
I can't get enough of his cock!
Mom, I need $ 1200 so I can go
to Sierra Crossroads over spring break.
And I need you to sign this form,
like, in case I die or something.
Is this a school trip?
No, you go to the mountains
and confront fear...
...and get in touch
with your most basic self.
It looks good on your college application.
Sorry I'm late. There was an
accident on the Long Beach Freeway.
You always seem to hit
the bad traffic.
- Hi, I'm Nate.
- Hiram, I've heard a lot about you.
Well, don't believe a word of it.
Hey, I'm sorry.
Don't be. I'm having fun.
- So, what did I miss?
- I want to go to Sierra Crossroads.
We'll talk about it later, Claire.
Mom, you should let her go.
Crossroads is great.
- You went?
- Yeah.
We went kayaking down the Colorado
River the summer I was, what, 17?
- I don't think you were even born yet.
- I don't remember this.
That's because I lied to you and Dad.
Dad would never let me go, so I told you
I was going to Sacramento...
...to witness state government in action.
Oh, by the way, everyone, I got a job.
- Cool.
- I'll be working at Nikolai's flower shop.
I start tomorrow.
It's just part-time.
- You didn't tell me about that.
- Didn't I?
Need some help?
Incidentally, I dropped Victor Kovitch off
at the Oak Valley Crematory.
I need you to pick him up tomorrow.
Oh, fuck, David, he wanted
a military funeral. He filled out the forms.
Is he paying our bill?
You were with his brother. It was clear
he did not want the body embalmed.
He could sue us,
and we wouldn't have a case.
Okay, you know what?
When you talk to me like this,
it makes me want to not listen to you.
You and I could lose everything.
Mom could lose her home.
Vic is eligible for a bigger allowance
from the VA than we thought.
Really?
- I'm leaving.
- I'll walk you down.
- Bye, David.
- Bye.
Why don't you come over,
spend the night?
I've gotta be in Pasadena tomorrow.
It would add an extra hour to my trip.
Okay.
Give me five minutes. I'll follow you.
- Tonight wasn't so bad, was it?
- I suppose not.
I don't know why I was so nervous.
I mean, for heaven's sake,
I gave birth to those people.
You know what occurred to me tonight
that's really strange?
I wish you'd known my husband.
I think the two of you
would've liked each other.
Oh, Ruth.
Who would get me a gift basket?
It's probably some Hollywood bigwig
that secretly wants to sleep with you.
It's from my brother,
and it is addressed to both of us.
"Sorry about this morning.
Have fun at Cactus World. "
Who knows.
This is nice. We can take it
with us this weekend.
I cannot wait to get out of here. I'm in
dire need of some serious relaxation.
- Oh, fabulous.
- Smoked oysters.
Really, is there any caviar?
No, but there are condoms.
- And, okay, edible underpants.
- That's a little scary.
- I'd say this whole thing's a little scary.
- No, it just means he likes you.
Believe me, there are guys Billy
didn't like. It's much better this way.
I've been meaning to ask you.
What's up with those matching tattoos
you and he have?
We were in Vegas,
we were very drunk, and...
Oh, dear.
These things always struck me
as kind of ridiculous.
Would you just stop that?
What does he think we're gonna do
with this? This is, like, hostile.
Look, Billy's bipolar. He's medicated.
His sense of what's appropriate
can be a little off at times.
Look, you have no idea
what he's been through.
Don't judge him, please.
All right.
Thank you.
You're never gonna get out of this one,
I was nowhere near the latrine, sir,
I promise,
- Give it up, private, Your ass is busted,
- Yeah, you're in big trouble,
But my father's
on the Joint Chiefs of Staff,
Well, maybe we can't court-martial you,
but there is something else we can do,
Yeah, come on, private, yeah,
You love that, don't you?
- Hello?
- David, Walter Kriegenthaler.
- Did you meet with Father Clark?
- Yes, today.
We'd like to meet at 9:30 tomorrow
and vote,
- Can you make it?
- Absolutely.
Let me ask you a question, David.
Do you think Clark is gay?
I don't think so. He mentioned something
about having a deceased wife.
I mean, I don't care if he is, I just don't
want him to push that agenda,
You know, marriage, that whole thing,
I have a cousin in D.C.
Whose church split because of that.
Literally half the congregation left.
I don't want that to happen to St, Bart's,
I've been going there for 40 years,
Well, it's late, I'll see you
tomorrow morning, Good night,
Okay, I got Victor, but I called
the National Cemetery from the car...
...and you know what?
They can bury an urn.
They call it "inurnment. "
We can do it today at 3.
Why are you so determined
to sabotage our business?
I don't think Paul knew
how his brother really felt.
- Nate, why do you even care?
- Because it's what Victor wanted.
And he deserves it.
He got a raw fucking deal.
Victor Kovitch did not hate the Army.
Watch these tapes he made in the Gulf.
Yes, sir, fuck me, sergeant,
- Fuck, yeah, Give it to me,
- Come on, private,
Oh, come on!
Come on, that was funny!
I have someplace I have to be.
Dave, Dave, it's okay!
I watch porn too!
So you guys taking the PSAT
this afternoon too?
Yeah.
So, what happens to you guys?
I go to UC Irvine
and Northwestern Law...
...meet a totally great guy,
he's a triathlete...
...we get married
and I practice law for eight years...
...and we get really rich,
and then I have two great kids.
- So you're, like, unbelievably happy?
- Kind of.
I get a master's in French
and then live in Paris for 6 months...
...and hate it, so I come back,
become a TV development executive...
...and I work out all the time.
I'm fairly miserable and have
a slight substance-abuse problem.
- But you look great.
- Thanks.
I start an interior-lighting design firm
with my college roommate...
...and it totally takes off...
...and then I die of ovarian cancer
before I'm 30.
- Oh, that sucks.
- Tell me about it.
Well, good luck.
What a freak.
- Father Jack?
- David. Come in, sit.
And call me "Jack. " We're beyond that.
- Meeting over already?
- Yes.
- Damn.
- We all admire Clark's energy...
...but there is some concern
that he may end up being divisive.
As you said yourself, if we have
to start over from the beginning...
And find some conservative lap dog,
who won't challenge anybody?
Yeah, that's what we need here.
Scotch?
No, thank you.
- Clark thought he came on too strong.
- I liked him, Jack.
The world would be better
if there were more like him.
I just don't think that he's a good fit
for St. Bart's.
Do you really think that Father Clark
would be happy here?
Why should he be happy?
How happy are you?
You're right, I'm not happy.
My life is very complicated
and confusing.
I've experienced a lot of loss
recently, my father and my...
And the thing that helps me deal with it
is having a place...
...that hasn't changed
like everything else in my life.
There's a reason they call it
a sanctuary.
I think the majority of our congregation
feels the same way...
...and my responsibility
is to them, not you.
Well, I've got a business to run.
Yo.
Speaking.
Yes.
What can I do for you, Mr. Gilardi?
- Here, this is good choice here.
- I don't like yellow.
The bridesmaids' dresses are lilac.
If the flowers are yellow,
it's gonna look like an Easter egg hunt.
How about white tulips? Very simple.
Just bunched together with a ribbon.
I was kind of thinking I would be
the only one with white flowers.
Or you could be the only one holding
a gorgeous bouquet of color...
...against your white dress.
- People do that?
It's your day.
You can do whatever you want.
Don't you think that would be pretty?
- I love the tulips thing.
- Tulips are one of my favorite flowers.
So graceful and classic,
like little ballerinas.
Only reason I even met Victor was I
jumped off a humvee and broke my feet.
Here I am in the hospital with this guy
who's dying, listening to me complain.
Playing cards, giving me his dessert.
I wish he didn't die. It sucks.
Thank you.
Have you heard from Paul yet?
Not since I told him his brother
was ready to be picked up.
Well, without his consent in writing,
I cannot allow this funeral to take place.
Fine.
At least we'll know
we made an effort.
When we were in the Gulf...
...Victor used to make these videotapes
to send home to his family.
We were always giving him a hard time...
...messing him up.
He was a real good sport.
The perpetual optimist.
- So my brother ready?
- Yes, he's right in here.
- What is this?
- Victor's friends wanted to say goodbye.
The hospital referred them.
It's no problem for us.
And no charge to you.
- Excuse me, are you his brother?
- Yes, I'm Paul.
This man here, I don't know
if you people know it...
...was like a lion for Victor.
He made federal waves
over Victor's disability case.
I found a couple pictures of us
playing baseball.
Vic was a lousy batter
but a pretty good infielder.
He's grinning like such a fool in these.
I thought you might like them.
- Is that you?
- Yeah.
- You sick?
- No.
Never got sick. I don't know why.
A lot of guys I knew over there did.
Thanks.
Thank you for letting Victor
have his military burial.
Even though I know
you were against it.
I'm sure this means a lot to him.
What the fuck is this military burial shit?
It's an option that can
easily be canceled at no charge to you.
Vic didn't want a military funeral.
You think I'm lying?
I think he was afraid to tell you
what he wanted.
He filled out those forms,
he kept the videos.
They filled out those forms.
This is all fucking Army PR.
- I threw those forms in the trash.
- I'll call the service off.
He kept Saudi Arabian candy
for 10 years.
- You just want to jack up your price.
- No, it's paid for.
I want your brother to have
the funeral he wanted for himself...
...because that's his right.
Victor wanted to believe he died for
something. You wanna take that away?
Jesus.
He's the only family I had left.
And he can't even tell me
what he wants when he's dead?
He thought
I would've talked him out of this.
And he's right, I would've.
Why don't you sit with his friends.
Glad to have you here, man.
- Where is Ruth?
- She's in the back.
Crying.
What is wrong?
It's the smell of the flowers.
- You'll get used to it.
- I am used to it!
Today, I helped people choose flowers
for weddings...
...for anniversaries, for new babies.
I can't remember being surrounded
by so much happiness.
I'm used to the smell of flowers meaning
something completely different.
I'm used to people crying
and being exhausted.
People being shattered!
Do not worry. We get funerals too.
I'm so happy. I can't wait
to come back tomorrow.
You're not going to be like this
every day, though, right?
This flag is presented on behalf
of a grateful nation as a token...
...of our appreciation for honorable
and faithful services...
...rendered by your loved one.
Give it to one of his friends.
I love you, David.
I always will.
I could get hit by a bus on the way
to the desert tonight.
Just wanted to make sure
you knew that.
I love you too.
- You did the right thing today.
- I know. Feels kind of good, doesn't it?
- Hello.
- She can't go.
Why not?
She has to help me pick prints.
- Does she have to do it tonight?
- Yes, she does.
Billy's got a show coming up
at a gallery in Westwood.
Sometimes she gives me her eyes
because sometimes I go blind.
Forty-six hours I've been looking
at these pictures...
...and sometimes I see amazing things...
...and sometimes I just see shapes,
and that's when I go blind.
Because what if I lost the ability
to tell the difference?
For real.
- For good.
- You won't.
You say that and give me your eyes.
But what if one day,
I can't give them back to you?
Well, that won't happen.
We won't let that happen.
God, this is crap!
This is pretentious, derivative crap!
Well, then that's one less
you have to consider. Right?
Right.
Billy, I'm gonna talk to Nate
on the porch, okay?
All right. Then he's gonna go away.
We'll be right outside.
Pick out five you like...
...and show me when I come back.
- Only five?
- Or 10 or 20.
And I'll look at them,
and I'll tell you what I see.
Okay.
You can fuck her some other time.
Sorry. He's obviously off his meds.
- Intentionally?
- No, it happens occasionally.
It's been a while.
- Brenda, come on.
- Sorry, Nate, I can't.
I'm all he has when he's like this.
- You are letting him manipulate you.
- You don't know him.
- You don't know what he's doing.
- I know he doesn't like me.
I have a feeling he doesn't like
any man in your life. Am I right?
- Answer me!
- What, you think I fucked my brother?
- Jesus, I never said that!
- Nate, he's sick!
He's my brother, and he's sick
and he needs me!
This is who I am,
this is what you get.
Fuck you.
You have no idea how much
I wanted to go with you.
- Can I do anything to help?
- Yeah.
You can go to the desert and sit in mud
and relax and forget about everything...
...including us.
Oh, shit.
Just go, okay? Goddamn it.
Subtitles by www. tv-series. nm. ru