The Eye Inside
Original title:
Another voice
Original Air Date
16- MAR- 2003
Hey, baby! Where you goin’ with that ass!
Come here, we’re talkin’ to you!
Slow down, bitch!
Hey, we just want to have a good time.
You know you want some of this!
Bitch, you know it’s gonna happen!
Hey, Callie. It’s just us!
Goddammit, Zach!
Oh, shit! Callie! Callie! Callie!
“It’s only a paper moon
Sailing over a cardboard sea
But it wouldn’t be make believe
If you believed in me
Yes, it’s only a canvas sky
Hanging over a muslin tree
But it wouldn’t be make believe
If you believed in me. ”
Perfect! That’s exactly how I want it to sound in Pasadena.
Uch! That’s just horrible!
Baritones, someone among you was singing a “B- flat, ” of all inappropriate notes.
And, um, well, there was a certain tenor who’s sharp on the “G”…a lot.
I can only pray to Jesus you know who you are,...Evan!
Lose the emotion, Dennis! That’s touching, but no one cares!
Okay. Sadly for our audiences who have paid $25 to hear,
we do not have time to work on that tonight.
But please, and I am begging you from a place of raw desperation,
learn your parts this weekend.
For them, if not for me.
Dismissed.
Hey, are you going to Evan’s open house tomorrow?
No. I’d love to, but I can’t.
I promise, it won’t be one of those sloppy scenes where everybody ends up naked in the pool,
and you have to deal with image of their soggy pubic hair in your mind for the rest of your life.
Well, that’s good.
Yeah, it’s just, I’m going away.
Oh. Well, I’m sure he’ll have another.
I hope so, because I’d really love to go.
Okay. Well, see you next week.
Shhh!!!
Shut up. My mom is a really light sleeper.
Sorry. That was—It was a really great one.
It was?
Mmm. How were yours?
Good.
Just good? Both?
It was just one…but it was good.
It was very good.
I think we can do better.
- Are you tired?
- It’s really late.
I was thinking I’d sleep over.
I don’t know…I guess.
Is that cool?
Yeah, fuck it.
Don’t go to the bathroom, though, ‘cause my mom gets up to pee like 500 times a night!
Now I have to pee.
Just go out the window. That’s what Nate used to do when this was his room.
Just try to avoid the avocado tree ‘cause we eat those.
Just do it.
Almost there.
My ass is killing me!
Sciatica?
No! It’s used to being nestled in a nice soft car seat for this trip!
I just love the fresh air!
It smells a lot like dog crap.
We had a little dog years ago,
a terrier we got for Nate when I was pregnant for David so he wouldn’t be jealous of the baby, y’know?
Yippie, he called him.
But he had some kind of a rare heart defect,
so, the day we came home with David,
Yippie crawled under Nate’s old bed and died!
That’s how my last husband went. Heart defect.
Jogged 5 miles every morning, then one day…poof!
46 years old.
Oh, that’s awful!
That’s better than with my first husband.
Melanoma at 25.
Then it was in and out of the hospital for 10 years.
Chemo 3 times.
That was hard. I really loved him.
I really loved him.
I’m so sorry!
When did you remarry?
Well…there was one in between the two that died.
He was just a dog.
He tried to sleep with every single one of my girlfriends.
He probably live to be a hundred! And screwing other people’s wives the whole time!
Son of a bitch!
Oh, I’m so sorry.
No, it’s okay. It is funny.
I just never thought of myself as lucky having only buried one husband before.
Lucky, unlucky. I don’t know.
I’m unlucky I ran through 3 husbands. I’m lucky I got to retire early off the insurance.
I’m unlucky my son set fire to the house.
I’m lucky I never had a urinary tract infection.
I don’t even care if it works out fair in the end. I’m sure it doesn’t.
I still have to haul my own ass out of bed in the morning.
I went to this…
I took a kind of seminar that was about that…
Oh, EST? Lifespring? The Plan?
The Plan.
My daughter was into that for years.
She was a group leader.
She inspired thousands of people to change their lives.
Now, she’s hoarding firearms in a compound in Montana.
No!
She’s always been very susceptible to group mentality.
Maybe I could’ve given her a stronger sense of self, but, you know,
I did my best. Some things are just genetic.
Well, what are you going to do?
Can’t you get some kind of a de- programmer to go in and rescue her?
You know what? She’s an adult.
I mean, it’s her life now.
Maybe I screwed her up, maybe I didn’t.
My son turned out fine.
How are your kids?
Fine…I think.
I have to go. I have a job interview in two hours, and I have to shower.
What kind of job?
As an accountant for a chain of dry cleaners. I’ve always been good with books.
Oooh, sounds fun!
Oh, I know. But I need the extra income, and it’s good for me to get out of the house.
You’re out of the house right now!
- That’s true.
- I think it’d be better to go to breakfast.
The French Marketplace has a 3. 99 special.
She was running from a group of boys who were whistling,
and she got scared that they were…
following her into a parking structure. So…
she ran into the street.
The car was speeding, it was dark…
I’m so sorry.
Did they catch the boys?
They were the ones who called the ambulance.
They were her friends.
I’m sorry. I don’t quite understand.
They were just playing around.
They were all in a state of shock
that a woman could be terrified by a group of men chasing her at night.
Of course you don’t think it’s your friends!
When they saw her running, they tried calling her name.
But it was too late.
It was an accident.
I’m here with your cake.
Thanks. Just pass it in here.
In…where?
Are you okay?
I just need to have my cake in a safe, white place today.
Did something happen?
I had a very upsetting conference call with Kate Hudson’s people.
It’s unbelievably demeaning to have these little girls in their $800 shoes
who grew up watching music videos telling me what a movie is.
I’ve been in this business for 20 years.
I’ve worked with Stallone, Ellen Barkin, Melanie fucking Griffith!
My work is everything to me! I haven’t even had a life!
No, I’m on the fuckin’ set, dealing with everyone else’s crisis!
Roping in the director, firing the writer, wrangling the star!
And who takes care of me?
Who even wants to take care of me?
That sounds really hard.
Uch, it’s so bright out here!
Careful, Lisa! These sheets are new from Pratesi!
Do you have your cake towel?
It’s in here.
Okay, I’ll come back later for the cake plate.
I still need my poopy shake at two.
Right.
Lisa, honey? Your husband’s car was parked again in the driveway last night.
I don’t think he understands how much of a problem this is.
He came home so late, I’m sure he just thought you wouldn’t need to get out.
What if I did, though?
You would’ve called us.
No, I don’t want to bother you in your private time at home! No!
- I’ll tell him.
- It’s not that challenging to find street parking!
Is it a snake? Or some kind of tropical vine?
It’s kind of a combination of Maori Ta Moko
and also Japanese Kanji for, like, inner wisdom, I think.
This, right here.
Oh, my!
I thought you were going to an interview.
I decided that job wasn’t really me.
Well, there’s eggs and bacon in the fridge, and I think there are still some frozen waffles.
Yeah, they’ve been there since like 1992.
That’s not true! They’re perfectly fresh.
I’ll take a waffle.
Let’s say…you’ve just met someone,
a month or so ago, and after a few weeks of exchanging messages,
you finally get together for a nice activity, like a hike, for example,
and you have a delightful time, and you think the other person did too.
How long would you wait to call the person to set up another date?
Who called who first?
Is this another boyfriend?
No, it is not! And I don’t appreciate that tone.
I did originally.
Wait. It’s his turn.
It’s really bad to be, like, begging for it.
The waffles are in the toaster. Nice to meet you, dear.
You don’t want to eat those. I can make you some toast.
That’s okay. I’ll grab something on the way to work.
Oh, do you want to see “A Clockwork Orange” tomorrow night?
I’ve never seen it, and Russell says it’s like mandatory viewing for all humans.
I can’t. We’re playing at The Snell.
Really? What time do you guys go on?
We probably won’t start till, like, 11…
But it may not be that fun for you.
I have these other friends coming who you don’t know…
So, can’t I meet them?
I don’t…think you really want to.
But Friday’s awesome, if you want to see the movie then.
No, it’s only tomorrow. Friday’s “Eyes Wide Shut. ”
Do you want to see that?
I did.
Okay, so…we’ll do something else.
“Private balconies, invigorating pool and Jacuzzis, gourmet cuisine,
and an array of activities are just some of the pleasures
awaiting our guests at the romantic refuge that is Los Lomos. ”
I hope there’s shuffleboard.
I’m serious!
They had it at this place in Santa Barbara my parents used to take us when we were kids.
I really had a knack for it.
It’s the only thing I could ever beat Nate at.
“The picturesque village nearby offers visitors sophisticated restaurants,
art galleries, antique and specialty shops. ”
I just want to sit by the pool and drink Pina Coladas all day.
“If you like Pina Coladas,
and getting caught in the… Whoops!
Does that count?
- Yes, it does.
- But I stopped!
- You owe me a dollar!
- I stopped!
All right, 50 cents.
I should get a dollar every time you say the word “calorie” or “carb. ”
How often do I say those?
A lot! More than I sing.
I don’t think so.
- Whatcha doin’?
- Pumping.
Thanks for helping me feel even sexier than I already do at this moment.
You’re crazy.
You couldn’t be more beautiful. You’re like a fountain of life.
Is she still sleeping?
What, Carol slip in here and give her some cognac?
Hardly. She missed her early nap because I had to use the blender all morning.
- Where did you park?
- In the street.
And she could’ve totally gotten out this morning.
Of course. The reality is,
she has trouble driving in reverse, so it makes her nervous having cars in the driveway.
she just doesn’t want people to think she drives an American car.
Whatever. Let’s do our part for peace.
“Hi, homos! ”
“That’s my son! You can’t have him! ”
“Fudgepackers! ”
“Pillow biters! ”
“God, I thought this was a family place! ”
“Butt pirates! ”
“Twinkle toes! ”
“Faggoty- ass faggots! ”
Here’s some shade for you right here, honey.
Oh, don’t worry about him! He can sleep through a dirty bomb!
- You don’t have to get up.
- Please, I need the exercise.
All we’ve done since we’ve gotten here is eat, and the food’s not even that good.
Oh, that’s too bad.
But I heard the girl who does the aqua hip- hop class is terrific!
If you can get yourself into the pool at 7:30 in the morning.
- Thanks for the tip.
- I’m Sheila, by the way.
Hi.
Hey, smile!
So you ready for your Pina Colada?
God, no. Then they’ll really know we’re gay!
We can’t have that.
I just think people here are a little uncomfortable with it.
Oh, yeah? Like who? Wasn’t that lady over there nice to you?
Yes, we have an aerobics date tomorrow morning, and then afterwards
we’re all going to the beauty parlor.
I’ll just take a beer. Not Lite.
- Hey, would you mind taking a picture of us?
- No problem.
Smile!
Oh, no, I’m glad you called. I was on the verge of getting an impulse haircut!
Those never work out.
Who do you use? I have to find someone new.
I just go to Supercuts.
You can’t do that! Bettina!
A woman’s hair is the gateway to her sensuality.
Not the hair on her head, honey!
What do you think?
- I think you should try it on.
- No, no, it’s for you.
that’s not exactly my style.
Sweetie, I say this with a heart full of love, but your style could use a tiny shot of adrenaline.
I like a classic look.
Try it. Just for fun.
Niiiice!
I don’t know. Isn’t it a little trendy?
Are you kidding me? It’s perfect!
And 30% off!
Okay, now try the gold silk number.
I’m so psyched for Valerie Doane. Her sculpture is amazing.
You didn’t hear? She’s not coming this semester.
What do you mean? That’s the whole reason I took this course!
Yeah, I know. You and everybody. But she got some kind of travel grant,
so she’s in Israel and now we have some other guy coming.
That sucks! This place is fucking lame!
It’s just one class.
I know, but nothing’s turning out to be as good as it looked in the catalog.
Who’s this other guy?
Oliver Something Something.
It’s Olivier Castro- Staal.
He’s supposed to be awesome.
Really? ‘Cause I heard he was kind of on his own trip.
Well, Valerie Doane is incoherent.
I took a seminar with her at BAMF. It was garbage.
Was that him?
This is the wrong room!
Are you here for “Form in Space”?
This is the right room.
It’s supposed to be a studio class.
The catalog said “lecture. ”
Well, that’s bullshit.
I don’t do lectures, so this is going to be a studio class.
If anyone needs a lecture for whatever reason people have for these things, then go now.
I won’t be offended.
Oh, you can just talk.
Um…I need a lecture to balance out my course load.
Okay.
We’re going to make art in this class.
And in the end, I’ll put “lecture” on the forms for people who need lecture
and “studio” on the forms for people who need studio. And that’s it.
If this upsets your sense of order, then you can go now. I won’t be offended.
But go now, so we don’t have to deal with ambivalence in this room.
Ambivalence is poison for art.
If I ever see anyone tormented over some decision, this way or that way,
I will be offended and I will throw you out, for the sake of the class.
Good. That was a bad vibe.
Okay, there are no easels in this stupid room, so everyone get on the floor!
Get on the floor!
Do you have your drawing pads?
We thought this was a lecture class.
Take one and pass it.
If you have a pencil, you’re lucky. If you only have a pen, you’re luckier.
All right, you have five minutes to draw a picture of the day in your life
that was the most horrible.
Go!
Wait, what do you mean, “ a picture of the day”?
Go, I said!
She juiced yet?
Yeah, just about. Hey, you file that certificate?
Claire’s gonna do it tomorrow.
Stupid kids.
Doesn’t it seem like she really sort of panicked, though?
Maybe something happened to her before…
I don’t know.
You know, Vanessa gets scared all the time.
Even when she’s out with the kids, she gets it.
Ask Lisa.
I’m not sure Lisa gets it that much.
I mean, she doesn’t wear high heels or tight skirts or anything.
Vanessa says she gets it even when she’s wearing her big fat sweatpants.
But, you know, she’s pretty hot.
Lisa’s hot.
Yeah, L- Lisa’s hot. I just
I don’t want to talk about your wife like that.
When does it stop sounding weird that someone’s your wife?
Vanessa felt like my wife already when we were 16 years old.
Hey, listen, Nate,
the first year of marriage, for most people, is the hardest,
especially with a baby on top, too.
That can be tough for anyone.
It’s great.
It is! I’m totally into it!
Alright, I’m just saying…y’know, even if sometimes you’re not.
that’s normal.
I’m into it.
Come in.
Are you feeling better?
You’re a little late with this.
I had to go and get more Psyllium.
Oh, God! The baby’s here.
I’m sorry. We haven’t quite figured out the childcare thing.
I tried to call Nate’s mom, but I guess she was hurt when
I got so angry about the peanut butter,
but it really could have made Maya sick—
Sweetie, I’m sorry. You know I love your little girl, and Nate’s fine.
But I just, I can’t get into all this.
Okay. Let’s talk about dinner.
Marlo’s assistant said she is only eating raw foods at the moment.
I really feel...that you are not being sensitive...to me at all.
I’m sorry. I thought you wanted to talk about dinner.
God, Lisa! I mean,
I’ve obviously had a very difficult morning, and you’re all about your own agenda.
I didn’t mean…
You’re rushing me through the menu so you can go deal with your baby.
She’s fine. I don’t have to deal with her at all right now.
Well, I really felt it earlier when I was in a lot of pain,
but the baby was crying, and that was clearly your priority.
No one was watching her.
That is not my problem!
When I hired you for this job, you were totally unencumbered.
And now, now there’s Nate and his dirty car and the...her! And her needs, and...
Nate and the baby have not affected my cooking at all.
They have affected your ability to support me emotionally!
And you live in my house!!
What do you suggest I do? Put Maya up for adoption?
Oh, I’ve discussed this with my therapist,
and she’s very concerned by the way that I allow you to treat me, because—
Oh my God!
…I require, and I fucking deserve, a lot more attention, and you know what?
I will not feel ashamed about that!
If I had known you were hiring me to be your fucking wet nurse,
I would’ve asked for health insurance!
Where are you going? Lisa? Lisa?
Lisa, goddammit!!!
The moment was of when my friend ODed.
Write down on a piece of paper your favorite artist.
In fact, everyone do this.
Is it Kandinsky?
Let’s see.
Because you’re using Kandinsky’s language here. It’s the same with most of these drawings.
We despise ourselves so much that we consider our own point of view as trivial,
but that’s bullshit! That’s your father talking,
or whatever bad teachers you had before me.
You, with the red hair, who did you write? Hopper?
No. I wrote Modigliani.
Were you lying?
No, but I also wrote Nan Goldin, because I’m really more into photography—
When did you see the Hopper show at MOCA?
- Last week.
- Okay, that’s exactly what I’m saying.
She sees 50 paintings by Hopper, she starts to draw like him,
because it’s easier than drawing from the eye inside.
Yeah, but artists get influenced by art. That’s part of the process.
Until you locate the inside eye, it’s all bullshit.
It’s like a coloring book.
Every work you make has to be a surprise to the Earth,
a seeing that never happened before.
Because it’s what happens when exactly what is inside of you
confronts exactly what is outside of you.
Okay, next.
Definitely! And the black suit, and the cocktail dress.
Oh, I’m not buying anything.
- Why not?
- Nothing was perfect.
Nothing in life is perfect.
Well, that makes it easy to stay within a budget.
If you don’t buy this black suit, I’m gonna buy it for you!
That is the sweetest thing I’ve ever heard! But I’d just return it and give you the money.
Fine! I’m gonna go back for the sandals.
Where did you find this?
Oh, just leave that there. They’ll take care of it for you.
I know, but it seems so rude.
Wonderful color for you!
How much?
Too much.
What are you doing?
It’s one of my little pleasures.
It’s only fair. If they’re gonna charge $350 for a piece of fabric that costs $20 to make,
they should lose a few! Do you want one?
I certainly do not!
It would be a great help to me if you tried to look a little less suspicious.
Fortunately, women our age are invisible, so we can really get away with murder.
What?
I don’t want to go to this stupid fiesta barbecue.
Oh, come on, it’ll be fun.
What’s fun about standing around a pool with a bunch of straight people shaking maracas?
There’s gonna be a mariachi band.
Why can’t there be just one other gay couple?
Some lesbians from the Bay Area?
Hey, that kid in the pool was gay.
The 11- year- old?
Oh, David, relax! You’re letting this matter too much.
Well, I’m sorry, but sometimes I just get exhausted by the running commentary
in my head all day long about how to be.
“Is this shirt too tight? ”
“Is that gesture too flamboyant? ”
“Who am I offending just by being here? ”
Maybe you’re beyond all that, but I would’ve thought you’d at least understand.
It would just be nice on vacation to not have to deal with that.
So don’t. Offend people! Who cares? We paid for our room, right?
I can’t just turn it on and off.
Well, maybe you should try.
No one gets a break from their reality, ya know?
Mexican food gives me the runs.
And what about what Frank said?
It makes me feel like I have the runs.
No, about us being less isolated.
I’m not doing a limbo contest.
- That’s Hawaiian.
- Well, good.
But if there is one, you’d be a fool not to enter it. You know you’d win that thing.
It makes you look 20. Get it.
Do I want to look 20?
Okay, it makes you look 30!
For $15, I could buy a bag of groceries.
Oh, yeah? But a bag of groceries doesn’t make you want to look at yourself!
Excuse me? Excuse me? I’d like to get this.
“Flirtation. ” Let me see if we have any left. It’s very popular.
We may be out.
Oh, she found it!
No, no, sorry, wrong one. Keep looking.
We’re all sold out.
Oh, all right then. Thank you so much.
Bye.
David! Salsa! Come on!
Well, what do we want to do for dinner? Go to that cheesy town?
It’s just a bunch of outlet malls and chain restaurants.
The room service menu looked like heaven.
Good, let’s go.
And if we don’t have to drive, we can get really drunk!
What’s going on?
I quit. We have to move.
Whoa, whoa, whoa…what?
I would rather live on the street and beg for rice with a bowl
than spend one more night under this roof!
All right, what, what happened?
She just unleashed so much insanity at us.
It’s not good for Maya to be around that kind of hostile dementia.
If that’s what I’d wanted for her, I’d be living with my mother!
I’m not sure Maya’s really that in touch with—
She’s very absorbent!
Okay.
I kind of wish we could have talked this through before you quit.
Did you actually quit?
Yes, I actually quit! We have to leave tomorrow morning!
So, what were you thinking, that we’d go stay at my mom’s, I guess?
Well, yeah, for now.
It’s not the worst thing that could ever happen, is it?
No.
It’s not the best thing that ever happened either.
I’m sorry. I snapped. My humanity just rose up.
Come here.
It’s alright.
OH MY GOD!!!
These walls are like paper.
So fucking what? We’re on vacation, dammit!
YEAH, WE’RE GAY IN HERE!!!
COME ON, COWBOY!! BRING IT ON HOME!!! WA- HOO!!
WE’RE HAVING SOME HOT MAN- ON- MAN LOVE ACTION!!
HALLELUJAH! HALLELUJAH!!!
Hold it, hold it, hold it. You sing, I sing.
BABY, EVERYTHING IS ALRIGHT/UPTIGHT, OUT OF SIGHT
I’M A POOR MAN’S SON FROM ACROSS THE RAILROAD TRACKS
THE ONLY SHIRT I HAVE IS HANGING ON MY BACK
BUT I’M THE ENVY OF EV’RY SINGLE GUY
’CAUSE I’M THE APPLE OF MY MAN’S EYE
HE SAYS BABY, EVERYTHING IS ALRIGHT…
Oh, you’re losing your pillow.
Oh, dammit!
Would you be careful?
Sorry.
Lisa, you’re carrying too much.
It’s fine. I just didn’t realize how tall it was.
I don’t know how much of David’s furniture you need,
but he has some lovely pieces stored in the garage.
We don’t really have anything, just that rocking chair…
It’s a much better space than Carol’s. It’s bigger.
Yeah. There’s no kitchen.
I told Lisa, you’re welcome to cook in the house whenever you’d like.
Thanks.
It won’t be for too long, Ruth.
I’m happy to have you.
Ruth, you can pick her up.
That’s nice lipstick, Mom.
Why, thank you, dear. It’s new.
When you’re done, put down your charcoal.
Okay. This is it.
Can you see why this is good?
Because it’s in her own language.
Yes, but the way I tell if something is good is…
does it make me want to throw up?
This drawing instantly makes me feel nauseous.
You can tell if something is truthful, even if you don’t understand it, if it affects your body.
Your liver and your bowels are more important as an artist than your eyes,
because they are so far away from your brain.
I don’t know. I think it seems kind of obvious.
Because you’re embarrassed by yourself.
In the beginning, if you hate something, it’s good,
because you don’t recognize the beauty of your own truth.
You’re used to being a normal, pathetic human who does only what other people want.
But what the other people really want is to fuck you
and to make money off of you and to hang you in the living room with the fancy security system.
Like this! Who did you make this to please? Me? Your mother, your boyfriend?
Does anyone feel sick from this?
No! So who the fuck cares?
I’m a friend of Callie’s.
And I was there, the night…she died.
I wanted to speak, because I really loved her,
and I wanted to talk about who she was to me…and to us.
Which is this brave, brazen, totally heroic person.
This rock climbing, body surfing, back talking, truth- or- dare champion.
I never even once saw her scared…before.
I guess what I really want to say to her is…
we were just pretending to be this thing that we’re not,
I don’t think, and then she was this thing that she’s not…
I’m sorry.
But when she saw that it was us, she had this look like,
“How could this be you? ”
Mrs. Mortimer?
I’m sorry, but…I just didn’t know what to say.
What?
The mother, Mrs. Mortimer, y’know? I just—I don’t—I didn’t know what to say to her.
You didn’t really have to say anything. I didn’t.
Yeah, but, like…hug her? Don’t hug her, y’know? I freeze up.
You can’t think about it. You just have to really be there with them. Just…be present.
I don’t think I can.
Sure you can.
No. Downstairs, y’know, it’s just a body.
But up here, like this young girl, y’know, she’s someone’s sister and someone’s daughter,
and I can’t help but to think, “Well, what if it was Julio?
Or Vanessa, even? ”
Y’know, and I just can’t…
You don’t ever think, “What if it was Maya? What if it was Lisa? ”
I don’t, actually.
Not them.
I can’t bring them in here with me, ya know?
I just want them to be what’s good about life. That way I can come here and deal with what isn’t.
That way I can come here and deal with what isn’t.
Well, you’re lucky, then.
So how’d it go last night?
Awesome. I mean, we screwed up a lot, but no one noticed.
It was fucking loud.
Everyone was walking around with, like, cocktail napkins in their ears.
So, listen,
I kind of want to talk about this whole “seeing other people” thing.
I’m not that into it.
I mean…it makes me feel weird, you know, it’s like…
if people are into each other, then that should be pretty much enough, y’know?
At some point, yeah.
What do you mean?
Like when it gets really serious or whatever.
Well, when does that usually happen for you?
It depends.
Okay. Well, how about, like, after a couple of months?
You mean like us, now?
Yeah.
I don’t know.
I mean, do you?
Well, yeah, that’s what I’m saying.
It’s just not really my thing to like sleep around.
I’m not sleeping around.
I just mean, I’m kind of a like one- at- a- time sexual person, I think.
So…what do you think?
I don’t think I’m there.
Just not at this exact point in time.
Well, why not? Is it ‘cause you like someone else better?
No! So totally not!
It’s just…it kind of has to be more organic for me,
like not some kind of contract or whatever.
It has to evolve.
But I’m not saying it won’t.
It so totally could.
Well, not for me. Not when it’s like
“You can’t come hear me play because there’s some other girl that’s gonna be there. ”
Yeah.
So…that’s like it for you?
I guess.
Well, can I have a hug or something?
No. I’m just gonna go.
Hey, what are you doing?
Nothing. Just watching this.
Okay, but you can watch with us.
Isn’t Maya sleeping?
Yeah, but she doesn’t mind the TV, if it’s low, and I have a million things I need to ask you.
Like what?
Like, when do you want to do the child- proofing?
And how should we deal with Maya while I look for a job?
Because I don’t even know how to start thinking about—
Then don’t. Not yet, just take a break. We’re not paying rent.
Yeah, but we can’t stay here forever.
Not forever, but we can relax for a few days, can’t we?
Oh, also I need to talk to you about vaccinating.
I’ve downloaded a ton of information from the Internet, and I’m still really against it, but..
you haven’t really weighed in. God knows your mother wants it.
Okay, print it out. I’ll take a look at it later tonight.
Are you coming?
Uh, okay, yeah.
I do, I want to hear it!
Elton John’s “Rocket Man. ”
“I miss the Earth so much,
I miss my life. ”
“Miss my life. ”
“It’s lonely out in space. ”
That’s me!
You sound good.
Yes, I happen to have a very nice voice.
Well, did I ever say you didn’t?
Well, practically.
I just don’t like it when you sing at me.
“And I think it’s gonna be a long, long time
Till touchdown brings me round again to find.
“I’m not the man they think I am at home
Oh, I’m a rocket man
Rocket man, burning out a fuse up here alone. ”
Oh, shit! We’re supposed to be going against traffic.
There might be an accident.
It looks like it might be picking up.
Not much.
Who knows when we’re gonna get home now?
I knew we shouldn’t have stopped for food.
It’s lucky we did. We’re going to get home too late to make anything now.
It’s not my fault!
You had to spend an hour at the Mikasa outlet store.
And I gotta do laundry tonight. My uniform stinks.
I really have to learn this.
These are cold.
“And I think it’s gonna be a long, long time
Till touchdown brings me round again to find
I’m not the man they think I am at home
Oh, no, I’m a rocket man…”
sync: youyoup
www.forom.com