Saison 5 Episode 1
"A Coat of White Primer"
Have you ever told
her how you really feel?
Of course not.
Why not?
Because she'd
start screaming at me.
Or cry.
When else have you chosen
not express your feelings
So that someone wouldn't
start screaming at you,
Or cry?
You mean, like with my dad?
And?
My sister.
Oh, and leonard.
So pretty much everyone.
Andrea, would it be so bad
If someone screamed or cried?
Yes.
- Horrible.
- Really?
Worse than feeling
"isolated and invisible,
Like an empty gaping
hole in the universe"?
Sometimes you talk about your life...
In a way that makes me feel sort of bad.
Okay, like, you make a lot of money,
Your house is a palace.
And you wear a size four...
When you're bloated.
So, when you get upset
because you gain a few pounds,
Or you complain about
how high your taxes are
With no comment on how much worse
those situations are for me.
makes me feel like
I'm not a real person to you.
I am... I am so sorry.
I guess I get wrapped
up in my own drama,
Or something and...
I am so glad you
finally said something.
I'm just asking you to
think about how what you say
might feel to me sometimes.
When you tell me that you
only want to hear good news...
It makes me feel like
you only, sort of...
Love me if I get engaged
Or promoted at work.
And that makes me really
not want to call you
when I don't have good news,
Which is, you know,
most of the time.
Dad?
God, that is so not true.
I'm just telling you how I feel.
That I never think
about your feelings?
I shower you with
gifts. I mean...
God, Andrea!
Look at this apartment! Look at all
the beautiful things I've given you!
That antique mirror?
The Italian Gondola ashtrays.
The Queen Anne
Brass andirons!
Honey, I don't smoke.
I don't have a fireplace.
And I don't like antiques.
You like antiques. I like
modern decor, which you know.
Your modern stuff just isn't as nice.
I like it.
But it doesn't matter what I like.
Fine. You know what? I'll
take it all back then.
Leonard!
It's not about the things.
It's not even about your reaction.
- It's about me being able to express...
- Give me the chair!
- Give me the chair! Get up!
- What are you doing?
You hate it so much, give it back!
I'm trying to tell you how I feel.
Lenny!
Andrea?
Oh, jesus!
Andrea, don't do this to me!
Oh, god.
Oh Jesus, now
what am I gonna do?
So how do you feel?
Alive, uh, glad about that.
Can you get this to stay on?
This pin is defective.
It won't prick.
Looks like Nate may have to
get married without a prick.
What do you think, Ma?
You got any advice?
Advice?
Oh, Claire, I don't know.
Don't give up.
Even when things get hard.
And they always do eventually.
Never stop trying.
Oh my god! I nearly got
killed on the way out here.
Some crazy old lapdog lady
almost ran me off the road
With her Lexus SUV!
Claire, where's David?
I need the rings.
I think he's over there.
David, we're starting!
The twins need to get
the rings on the pillows.
I just don't want
them to get lost.
Thanks. Come on.
Oh yes, you can't stand
Being away from mommy
for moment, can you?
- How do you feel?
- Like...
Every moment of my life
had led up to this one.
Like all of it makes sense
Like this is the destiny
that's been waiting for me.
I know it's stupid to think in
terms of "happily ever after,"
But that's what it feels
like right now.
Okay, let's do this thing.
"Let's do this thing"?
- No analyzing.
- I'm not analyzing.
I'm loving. Thanks.
Coffee-- I can't even smell it.
Sorry.
We come together
on this beautiful day,
To witness and celebrate
the union of Nate and lisa.
- I vow to love and nurture you...
- I'll skip the vows.
- No, you can watch the vows.
- I'll watch them later.
Have you learned all kinds
of interesting things?
I just wanted to
see it, you know?
So that I didn't do the same
thing in some weird way,
Make everyone
uncomfortable.
I was the first
one to shoot this location.
We used it in "pack up your
sorrows: the mimi farina story."
- Isn't it gorgeous?
- This is going to be different.
I want it to be perfect.
It's already perfect, even if it rains
- And everybody gets soaked.
- That's why I got the tent.
Even if the band sucks
and the food is rancid.
That's why we're only
having hors d'oeuvres.
I love how weddings erase the past.
Like a coat of white primer.
Slap a veil on her and the
biggest slutbag on the planet
Becomes a fresh-faced ingenue.
Oh, I'm gonna puke.
Sorry. Is it the coffee?
You okay, Bren?
God damn it!
Yeah well, that's not
what she told me.
Who wanted tuna fish?
Hold the mercury!
- Well, you're an idiot!
- George?
If you want mercury,
i'll give you mercury.
Hell, our bloodstream's
already full of it.
It's in all the water. The rivers
are poisoned. The ocean's poisoned!
- George.
- No.
No!
No! No!
I just don't know how
this could have happened.
I mean, they had such a
good relationship, I thought.
They never fought.
I just don't understand.
Some things in life...
We can never understand
exactly why they happened.
But it's so unfair. She was just
starting to really be herself
For the first time in her life.
That's rough...
When people are just starting over.
I know. I know.
Your husband is suffering
from a condition
Called "depressive psychosis."
The hallucinations,
paranoia and delusions
Are all characteristic.
We generally get good
results from a combination
of tricyclic antidepressants
and antipsychotic medications.
But how did this happen?
Any kind of stress can
trigger this type of condition.
A death in the family,
pressures at work,
Marital conflicts.
But he was fine when we met.
He was so... lovely.
It can come and go
throughout one's lifetime.
And, according to his daughter,
Your husband has had a long
history of mental illness.
What I'd like to do is get him
started on the meds right away.
And we'll keep him here for
observation for a couple of days
And see how he takes to it.
I liked that girl janine.
What do you think?
- About what?
- Her sister.
She was nice, I thought.
I guess she was nice.
She was in shock,
So it's a little hard to tell
what she'd be like on a date,
- If that's what you're asking.
- Jeez.
What'd he do, stab her in the eye?
That's what happens to couples
who never learn how to fight.
"Ricky, are you there?"
- Uh, ricky?
- Oh, shit.
I gotta deal with this girl.
- What girl?
- Just someone I dated a few times.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I signed up on match.com just to...
- You know, get out there a little.
- Good for you, dude.
- I got to break up with her now.
- On an instant message?
I don't want to lead her on.
What do you think?
"I'm looking for someone with a
more positive attitude about life."
That's a little harsh, dude.
She should know for her other
dates. She was a downer, man.
That's very thoughtful, "ricky."
Doctor: we're not getting the response
to the medications I was hoping for.
George and I have discussed it,
And we agreed our best
option is to move on to e.C.T.
- e.C.T.?
- what's...?
Electroconvulsive therapy.
- Shock treatments?
- It sounds much worse than it is.
We administer a slight
shock to the brain to
reboot the circuits as it were.
But isn't that?
It's a very effective treatment
for this type of depression.
Nothing else is working.
George?
- How's he doing?
- Much better.
They think he'll only
need a few more sessions.
Tonight? But he's still sleeping.
He should wake up
in about a half hour.
He may have some nausea
or mild confusion,
But he'll be fine to go home tonight.
- Are you sure?
- It's fine.
Worst case scenario, he'll have some
short-term memory loss but nothing too severe.
I think he should be
observed one more night.
- It's not necessary.
- I am not bringing him home tonight!
He's not ready.
All right, one night more.
But tomorrow, he has to go home.
We need the bed.
Fuck, I forgot to buy wine.
Maybe it's rude to bring
wine to a pregnant house.
Maybe we should just
pick up some ice cream?
No, we should definitely buy wine,
In case they forgot that
other people still drink.
Can I wear this, or will everyone
think I'm a total indigent?
What about that purple
thing in the closet?
- That's here?
- Yeah.
Oh, good. I totally
thought that was lost.
Maybe you should just move in.
Really?
- You mean, like, totally?
- Wouldn't it just be easier?
You're in my darkroom all day long
- And you sleep over every night.
- Is that annoying?
Yeah, it's annoying, that's
why I want you to move in,
Because I'm a total masochist.
Yeah, but how would
we both work in here?
It's been fine so far.
Okay, 'cause I totally
took over your space.
I could use my studio at school
If I ever get inspired
to make anything again.
Oh, come on.
It would be a relief to never
have to see my mother again.
You're going to have
to see her tonight.
Would you be terribly disappointed
If I couldn't make
it tonight, dear?
No. Is everything all right?
I'm just feeling a little tired.
Is George okay?
- He's coming home tomorrow.
- That's great.
Is he going to be able
to make it to the wedding?
Make it to the wedding?
Do you have any idea what
kind of state he's in?
I'm sorry. I thought
he was better.
He is better.
He's just not himself yet.
You sure you don't want to join us?
Yes.
I just need one last quiet night.
I'll be in by 9:00 tomorrow
if you need help with anything.
All right. Bye.
You look great!
Thank you. I feel like shit!
Hey. Welcome.
Non-Alcoholic sparkling cider.
- Thank you very much.
- So mom's not coming.
- Why not?
- Because she hates me.
- She doesn't hate you anymore.
- Now she hates Claire.
Why does she hate Claire?
Mom thinks she's flushing
her life down the toilet.
Because she's taking
the semester off.
Not because she's
dating my brother.
Uh, no! Just the school thing.
Brenda: because she's
taking off one semester?
I think she's terrified
that Claire won't go back,
And mom's biggest regret in life
is that she never went to college.
So if Claire doesn't
graduate, it's like she...
Failed twice or something.
It's time for somebody
to take a bath.
- I'll do it.
- You sure?
Yeah! I got to pee anyway
for the billionth time today.
Where does it all come from?
- Bye!
We'll go have a bath.
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
She knows we all think Billy's
a bomb waiting to go off.
What does she think?
She thinks he's fine when
he's on his medication
And he's been taking it for
a long time, so whatever.
I could almost deal with the guy if
he wasn't fucking my little sister.
He's better than gabe.
Come on, he was
a drug-crazed killer.
He didn't kill the
guy, he shot at him.
She should have stayed
with her nice gay boyfriend.
That guy was an asshole.
She knows how to pick them.
- They're here!
- Hey, Billy!
Come on in!
- How you doing, Billy?
- Good.
- Hello.
- Hey.
- Hey, guys!
- Where's mom?
- She's not coming.
- Do your parents still live in ohio?
- Columbus, yeah.
- Where did you grow up?
- L.A.
West adams area,
near where I work.
I don't know
L.A. that well.
- How long have you been here?
- Four years, But it's so big!
My hours are
crazy at the dentist,
Because people schedule
their appointments
Before and after regular work
hours, and on weekends too. So...
- Yeah, my business too.
You're never off.
You could always get a call.
That must be
convenient for dating.
- Uh, what?
- Like, when you want to get out of a date,
You can have a friend call you and
pretend to be a dead person or whatever.
Come on.
I wouldn't do that!
How's it going
with the adoption thing?
We have two interviews
left for the home study.
Then we just have
to wait for a referral.
What's a referral?
- A kid.
- Wow. How long will you have to wait?
- Anywhere from a week to many years.
- That's got to be hard.
Yeah. But they all say sometimes
being gay helps you get chosen faster.
In this backward country?
The birth mothers have to
look at thousands of pictures of
- straight white people.
- So we kind of pop out.
It's so weird to imagine
going through all that--
Nine months and a delivery and
you don't even want the kid.
I mean, who would do that?
- Christians.
- No, not only.
Some women just can't deal
with making a decision,
And they leave it too long.
But they don't even
get money, right?
We'll have to pay
the hospital bills.
That's where they
can scam you.
If they change their mind,
you're left with the bill.
That rarely happens.
It really makes you see
the appeal of a surrogate.
It does?
Yeah.
That and wanting to have your own kid.
Yeah, but there are so many kids
who already exist who need homes,
Why would we want
to make another one?
For the same reason
straight people do.
But given that it's not
quite as easy for us,
Why would we do
something so extreme?
Why should we be the ones who
don't get to have our own kids,
Just because we're gay?
It's not because we're gay.
I just don't think a
child has to have my genes
For me to feel like it's mine.
I'm sure people love adopted
kids as much as their own.
I mean, obviously.
Maybe. It's easy to say
when you have your own.
I love Maya.
And you still wanted
one of your own.
You just think you don't deserve
to have what everyone else has.
Would anybody have more wine
if I open another bottle?
Yes.
You think you're the only one
with dreams that don't work out?
We both got what we settled for.
I think you just don't love
me anymore.
- I do love you.
- Hello!
You're home early.
Yeah, well, first
date, you know.
How was it?
It was okay.
Well, good night.
Would you like
some Sambuca?
Sure.
Unless...
- I don't want to disturb you.
- Oh no.
I want to hear about it.
Was this the dental hygienist
or the investment banker?
The hygienist. Sharon.
The banker was too... shiny.
You know...
It may have just been
an unfortunate lotion.
But let's hear about sharon.
Well, uh, she was nice.
I liked her, I guess.
Did you get a sense of
what kind of person she was?
Does she seem solid?
Yeah, definitely solid.
It's so important. To feel
you could rely on someone.
Yeah. It's interesting,
this whole dating thing.
I never really did it before vanessa.
Enjoy it, dear.
But try not to be blinded
by lust, if you can.
Hey, do you guys
want to get high?
I could get high.
I've got some really good pot.
- I've got some.
- I actually have some in my jacket.
You do?
It's left over from when we
went to the hollywood bowl.
That's too old.
I just got this.
Mine cost $200
for an eighth.
- Let's smoke that.
- It's inside.
Don't tell Keith we're smoking.
He gets really
annoying when he's high.
I don't want to make a big deal
about it in front of Brenda.
I know what you mean. Billy can't
smoke because of all his medications.
So how's mom?
When was the last
time you talked to her?
You might want to call her
tomorrow before the wedding
- So it's not tense.
- She can call me.
There you go.
So, um, what do you
guys think about Billy?
He's in a pretty good
place, you think?
Yeah. Definitely.
Good place, what
does that mean?
Just that he's doing really well.
It doesn't mean I won't
lay awake at night worrying
About the fact you're in his bed.
That's a nice thing to say
about your wife's brother.
She knows how I feel.
It is so unfair to hold
things that happened
years ago against someone.
That's saying that
people can't change!
I mean, you changed!
Yeah, I've changed,
But I'm not totally
fucking insane.
I didn't try and carve a
tattoo off somebody's ass.
Shut up!
Here.
What?
I don't know.
Did you have
a bad dream?
Maybe.
Yeah.
What?
Oh my god,
I'm bleeding.
- Oh, Nate!
- Okay okay okay. It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
I'm going to try to schedule
the d&c for tomorrow morning.
We can't do it tomorrow.
We're getting married.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
- Bren, we can cancel.
- No, we have to do it today.
I can't get an anesthesiologist today.
We have to do
it tomorrow, Bren.
Oh, fuck.
Can it wait till monday?
Sure, monday's fine.
Then we'll do it monday.
Hey, how's it going?
Good.
Is that me?
No, it's Nate.
No, these pieces?
That's Brenda. Narcissist.
Well, it looks like me.
Well, they're not. This
is a wedding present.
Why would I
have you in there?
Because she can marry Nate,
but she'll always love me.
She is me!
No!
Are you upset with me?
No, I was just concentrating.
All right.
I'll leave you alone.
I'm sorry.
How do I get
to my room?
You mean our room?
Our bedroom?
If that's what it is.
Come on upstairs now.
We'll get you unpacked.
David: you made it clear we're
only considering a surrogate?
Yeah. Now what
about Tamara?
She's got your
forehead, an I.Q. of 120.
She's 5'2" and
she weighs 160 lbs.
Maybe that's why she costs
less than the other ones.
It's not like I wouldn't
love an obese child,
But I'd rather not sign up
for a lifetime of body issues,
Especially if we get a girl.
If we get a girl, you
better hope she's obese.
I'm not having some
12-Year-Old hottie
Running around sunset boulevard
with her ass crack showing.
Hey, Rog, what's up?
Yeah. I can do a couple
of nights next week.
Let me get my calendar.
What nights were you thinking of?
I know I'm free tuesday.
Are you ready to
meet the bachelorettes?
Uh, I guess so.
Ladies.
Hi. I'm Sierra.
I'm 20.
I have a combined
S.A.T. Score of 675.
And I want to be your
egg donor-surrogate
Because, although I'm not ready
to start a family of my own,
I want to put as many versions of
myself on the planet as I possibly can.
Hi! I'm Deedee
from san pedro.
I'm 27 years old.
I love outdoor sports, and
i'm your dream surrogate
Because I've given birth
to nine healthy babies.
And it's my personal
mission to have children
For Bourgeois narcissists who
can't conceive on their own.
Hi.
I'm Lindsay.
I've got a degree in
applied science from yale,
A masters from M.I.T. And
$60,000 of school loans to repay.
I'm hoping you pick me
so I won't have to resort
To more obvious forms of
prostitution to get out of debt.
So, have you found her?
I can't do this, Keith. I'm sorry.
I can't just rent out some woman's
uterus like it's a storage locker.
Okay.
Hi, guys!
Daddy got us a gamecube!
- You could say hello!
- Hi.
Share with your
brother, Julio!
You're spoiling them.
Can you take them tomorrow
for a couple of hours?
I can't. It's Nate's wedding.
Oh, that's right. I forgot.
Who are you bringing?
No one. You want to come?
No, thank you.
I'm happy for Nate,
But I have a week
of errands to do.
- You should bring a real date.
- To a wedding?
Isn't that weird?
You should bring someone
so it won't be boring.
What happened with that makeup
artist dana? She sounded nice.
Yeah, she was too... I don't
know, cheerful or something.
Nobody's perfect. You have to give
people a chance to grow on you.
Yeah.
Don't take this the wrong way, but...
No one's you.
That's sweet, but I
was never me either.
- Yes, you were...
- No, if you were this picky
when we were going out,
you never would have married me.
You just have to find someone
you like and be nice to them.
Is that how it is with kenny?
Oh. That didn't work out.
Really? What happened?
Ugh, he's a pig. I don't
even want to talk about it.
But I'm too busy
for all that now.
It's okay for me. I don't
need someone as much as you do.
Oh really?
It's not a bad thing, Rico.
You're just...
A person who does
better with someone.
So tomorrow, while
I'm at the wedding
I'm going to have a home
aide come stay with you
So you won't be
alone, all right?
- Whose wedding?
- Nate's. My son.
I know who Nate is.
Who is he marrying?
Brenda... his girlfriend?
That's wonderful!
Of course I'll be there.
This is an important
passage for Nate
From being a widower to
starting again as a householder.
- I want to support him.
- If you don't think it's too much for you.
Too much? My only son
is getting married!
Well, why don't we see
how you feel tomorrow?
I wouldn't miss it for the world.
The splendid young man
who came to the throne in 1509,
By 1547 had become a revolting
swollen mass of putrefying flesh.
You want the vicodin or some naproxen?
- Vicodin please.
- All right.
Here.
Cramps are pretty bad, huh?
I just want to get a whole lot number.
God, this is so not the vision I had
of the night before my wedding.
Where is the stripper?
It would be so easy to postpone
this for a couple of weeks.
It would not be easy.
And it would cost a fortune.
So what? It's just money.
I'd rather not even have a wedding
Than have to deal with
rescheduling everything.
Yeah. Yeah.
Let's just-- We can
run off to vegas.
- Yeah right.
- Come on, you loved that idea.
That was before I spent six months
planning my stupid fucking dream wedding.
That's why I think we should reschedule.
It's only going to be depressing.
- For you?
- Yeah, for me!
And it's going to be
depressing for you too, I think.
It's not as depressing
as calling 100 people
And telling them that it's canceled
because I lost my fucking baby,
Which I just told the
whole world I was having.
Why did you let me tell
so many fucking people?
I just... I don't
think that you...
I don't think you
realize how upset you are.
Don't tell me how I feel! I
think I know how upset I am!
Then why are we going through with this?
Because when I think about not doing it,
I want to throw myself under a bus.
I want to swallow razor blades.
I'm gonna have to take
every painkiller in the house
Just so I could pick up the
phone and cancel the caterer.
Then fuck it!
Let's get married.
Okay?
It will be a great day.
Yeah.
You can have one of
my vicodin if you want.
Thank you.
Just make sure you leave
enough for tomorrow.
... which meant
that he constantly stank
of rotting flesh.
Oh god.
Are these big granny-panties
your "something old"?
Because they really kill the mood.
You can't see them
through the dress, can you?
No, but they're hideous, sweetie.
Would it kill you to wear a thong?
These are fine.
What's the matter?
Nothing's the matter.
I just don't want to wear a thong.
Did something happen? Is it the baby?
What is it? What happened?
Oh, baby.
I don't want to fuck up my makeup.
Oh, honey. We'll ean you
up with a good powder.
I've got chanel in my purse.
I don't want to be late.
You don't have to worry about
everything going right anymore.
That boat has sailed.
You know it happens all the time
So many of my friends...
Joanie, Celia, aunt
Mary before she had Deb.
Even Teresa Heinz Kerry
had one.
And God knows,
she looks terrific.
- Aunt mary did?
- I'm telling you,
More women have miscarried
Than they have masturbated with
a dildo. They just don't talk about it.
And then they
have a baby,
And then they're
fine, sweetie.
I'd better change
this fucking pad.
If I get blood on this dress
I'm gonna kill myself.
- I'm so sorry, Nate.
- Yeah, well...
Just don't tell anybody, all right?
We want to keep today kind of nice, you know?
Are you going to try again?
Yeah, of course, as soon as we can.
- You might want to give it some time.
- No no no. I don't want to wait.
No, I mean, to grieve.
With all the fucked up shit
that's happened in my life,
I don't want to grieve
anymore. I can't.
I can't! I don't
have it in me.
Well, maybe
Brenda needs to--
What Brenda needs to do is
get pregnant again. Soon.
'Cause it's not like she's 20.
Yeah, but...
With all the stuff Keith
and I have been reading,
It seems psychological stress
can affect a woman's chances--
It's the only thing that's gonna make
her feel better! Why should I wait?
Why put it off? Because bad shit
happened and we need to feel bad?
Bad shit happens every day.
You of all people should know that.
Move fucking on, you know?
Anyway, I've already got
Maya so it's not for me.
But it'll be your child,
your flesh and blood.
- How could it not be for you?
- Because it's what Brenda wants
More than anything, and i
can make that happen for her.
Listen, the justice
of the peace is here.
I take you, Nate,
With all your strengths and faults
As I offer myself to you
With all my strengths and faults.
From this day forward,
I will be there
when you need help
And turn to you
When I need help.
I promise myself
to you forever.
I vow to trust,
To honor and to cherish,
To share and support your hopes,
Your thoughts and your dreams
As long as we both shall live.
By the power vested in me
from the state of california,
I now pronounce
you husband and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
So is it weird to see
Brenda get married?
"Weird"?
No, it's great.
I mean, because you
guys used to be so close?
I'm really happy.
I'm happy we're both in
healthy relationships.
With siblings.
It's funny how you both ended
up with another set of siblings.
Yeah, yeah.
It's funny that you
and Nate did too.
God, what do you think it means?
- It was a nice ceremony.
- It was.
You got a little
choked up, didn't you?
Yeah.
I love weddings.
Don't you?
Sure. If it's right.
The last one I went to,
the people hated each other,
- So it was depressing.
- God damn it!
It's so frustrating to
not be able to help her!
But you did help her.
You helped her as much as anyone
could under the circumstances.
I don't know. I really
believe in marriage.
A lot of guys today don't even
know how to make a commitment,
But I was married 11 years.
I'm the kind of person
who's better with someone.
Someone special, I mean.
That's sweet.
They couldn't have
picked a prettier location.
It looks beautiful.
- All right, that's enough of that one.
- All right.
Lovely! A family portrait
with two new Fishers.
- Okay, what's next?
- How about mom and George?
Okay, I'm just gonna freshen up.
Okay, mom. You guys wanna
get over here in the light?
- Let me take that glass.
- Mom, it's fine.
Sorry.
- What are you doing?
- What?
Have a little respect!
Oh my god.
It's not funny!
Oh my.
- May I have some seltzer please, no ice?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Mom, are you okay?
- I'm fine.
- What happened with Claire?
- She's in such a terrible phase.
She's so out of control in her life,
She doesn't care about
anyone else's feelings.
- What did she do?
- She took a rude picture of George
In an extremely compromised
state. There's ice in this.
- Sorry.
- I'm sure she didn't mean it that way.
She's always trying
to make some statement!
Yes, this is her way
of saying I'm the fool
Who has to take care of a crazy
person for the rest of my life!
I don't think she was
trying to say that.
I don't need a photograph to see that.
I don't need to have my face shoved in it.
Mom, we'll get you some help,
a nurse or something.
God! No! I'm still the one who has to
be there all day and every night.
- Why do you ?
- Because there's no one else!
Excuse me, dear. I have to clean
the stain on his jacket before it sets.
Oh, thank you.
- Who's the third one for?
- That's to put under our pillow.
So who do you dream of
if you're already married?
You dream of a future love.
You mean our second husbands?
No. We could dream of our child.
Or just get frosting in our ears.
I think we should go
forward with the surrogate.
Really? Why?
Because you want your own child.
And...
I don't want to be the
one who denies you that.
Want to be the one who helps
you to have what you want.
What about the kids who need homes?
We can do both. I
think we should do both.
One of each?
Which one comes first?
Whichever shows up first.
What if they both show
up at the same time?
Then we'll be really busy.
You're serious.
All right then.
You don't have to worry about
it being like my wedding.
I had a three-Month-Old
baby when I got married,
So it was a much
happier event, obviously.
Really joyful.
It all came very naturally to me.
But I was always maternal, unlike you.
I'm fucking maternal.
Oh, come on. Look at your past.
What about my past?
You're a slutbag! You were.
- That's got nothing to do with it.
- Of course it does.
All the moments of your
life have led to this one.
- You're being punished.
- I don't believe in that.
Your insides must have gotten
damaged from all that anonymous cock.
Oh, come on. That's why
this happened to you.
Look at that nice woman over there.
She's got her baby.
Everybody treated her like a
princess for the whole nine months.
There's a pregnant
goddess, due in six weeks.
She has two at home.
She doesn't know it
yet, but she's pregnant.
She wasn't even trying!
Boy, is she going to be thrilled. Twins!
They'll be here in june.
I'm gonna get my baby, you bitch.
I got pregnant the fourth time I tried.
I didn't have to try.
But I never partied like you did.
It's a miracle you even conceived!
A lot of women have miscarriages!
They don't talk about it
so people don't realize.
None of the women at this wedding have.
Except you, of course.
You're just bitter because you had to
get pregnant to get Nate to marry you.
I'm bitter? Who's drunk
and yelling at a dead woman?
And she might not even be his daughter!
You were having an affair
with your sister's husband!
That was purely a spiritual thing.
Nate is Maya's father.
He's my husband, and he always will be.
You will never feel his
arms around you again.
You'll never feel the air on your skin,
Or wake up in a warm bed.
You're done.
You don't get the chance
to try again for anything.
- So what?
- So I can.
Oh, please.
Every time you try to
have a nice normal life,
You fuck it up.
You're never going to have
your happily-Ever-After moment,
No matter how many
white veils you put on.
You're just too
fucked up for all that.
Maybe you should just accept that,
Instead of trying to
be something you're not.
Are you okay?
- Bren?
- You were right.
I should never have tried
to have this stupid day,
This idiotic tent, the
dumb-Ass wedding band.
It's such a fucking cliche.
Just to prove that I deserve
my own special fucking day,
Which I don't.
Brenda, the
only reason--
- The only reason why i...
- No, come on!
You knew. It was a pathetic attempt to
become something I'm not, that we're not.
I thought you might be
too upset to enjoy the day.
But it's so perfect this
way! It's so perfect.
The only way that I get to get
married in a long white gown
Is to have my dead baby
leaking out of me all day.
That's me. That's what
i get for my wedding.
You're really upset,
maybe you shouldn't be drinking.
Are you kidding me? This glass
of champagne is the only thing
in my universe right now.
You have me.
You don't really fucking want me.
Not that I blame you.
Who would?
I do.
Well then, you're a
very disturbed person.
Maybe.
Don't be nice to me!
What do you want me to do?
You want me to hit you?
Yes! That would feel fucking fantastic!
Come here.
I thought you were going to hit me.
No. I'm disturbed, I'm not violent.
You were when you threw your ring at me.
Oh, memories.
I'm glad
today sucked--
'Cause I wouldn't want the
happiest day of our life
To be over already, would you?
No.
It's coming, right? It's coming.
It fucking better be.
Brenda?
Oh, I'm sorry. You
can't come in for this.
Can you hold this?
Sous-titres par
la Fisher Team
Transcript:
Raceman
Synchronisation :
EZ, Occeane
Relecture et corrections finales :
Guzo
http://www.sixfeetunder-france.com
http://www.forom.com