Sous-titres par
la Fisher Team
Transcript:
Raceman
Synchronisation :
EZ, Occeane
Traduction :
Sylvain, Petrushka, Spooky et Bibipupuce
Relecture et corrections finales :
Guzo
http://www.sixfeetunder-france.com
http://www.forom.com
Saison 5 Episode 4
"Time Flies"
Once again no rain,
but mostly high clouds.
Since you got so much
information, can you tell us
Why it smells like
skunk outside the studio
- In hollywood here?
- It does?
Sam, do you know why that is?
Okay. Okay, now!
Happy birthday!
Well, thank you.
Thank you very much.
- Happy birthday.
- Thank you.
- Are you excited to see all your friends at daycare?
- Yeah.
Did you notice anything in the bathroom?
Aside from a few new wrinkles, no.
It was right by the toilet.
Are you pregnant?
Yes.
That's great! Congratulations!
Congratulations? To whom?
- Come on, what am I supposed to say?
- Nothing.
- To you, to all of us!
- No no, whatever comes up in your head.
- Brenda, what's the matter?
- No, nothing.
Thank you for your
hearty congratulations.
- Come on, honey.
- Are you sure it's positive?
There you go, honey bun.
Maya's gonna be late.
Brenda, I'm happy, I...
Come on, grab hold. Come on, baby.
- Brenda- - See you tonight,
i gotta get ready for work.
I'm happy, just tell me again.
Fuck!
Have you seen my ski
iraq shirt anywhere?
- You had that on last night.
- Yeah, I didn't ask
Whether I had it on last night,
i asked whether you've seen it.
I haven't.
Shit!
What is your problem?!
Nothing, I just don't think
I can wear clothes today.
Don't you have class?
Yeah, well, nothing feels right.
Look, maybe you should like
see a doctor or something.
For what?
I don't know, dry skin?
- Are you fucking serious?
- Well, yeah,
Look, I don't know, every day with
you it's like a bigger problem.
Not everything is something
that you can medicate, Claire!
I know that.
It's just my clothes are...
All heavy today...
Or something. I want my ski iraq shirt.
Okay, I'll help you find it.
Okay, thanks.
That's all
i wanted was some help.
Okay.
Shit, I feel like I still
have something on.
Mary, keith and david have
something they want to ask you.
I'm on pins and needles.
We've decided that we
want y to be our egg donor
And our surrogate.
- Both?
- Is that okay?
Yeah, it's just I've never
been proposed to like this.
Most people are so businesslike.
You guys are so sweet.
- Whose seed will it be?
- His.
So this is something that you would
want to do for Keith and David?
Yeah, I'd love it.
- I didn't say yes?
- Uh, no.
Oh, then yes yes, of course, yes!
Well, good.
Can I ask a question?
Please, david.
We're in this together. Ask ask ask.
Is there caffeine in that?
We're into that already.
Okay. It was so nice for a minute there.
No, I was just thinking-
I've read some books
That say caffeine makes
it harder to conceive...
Sometimes, that's all. Just curious.
Maybe you've read something different.
I get pregnant super-easily,
David, trust me.
It's kind of unsettling.
- Okay.
- But I assure you,
Once we've signed the
papers I will look forward
To working very close
with you to make sure
Our baby is healthy and gets conceived.
Thank you.
Gosh, I'm extra excited. Aren't you?
Well, I think we're all very excited.
- Are you finished with your eggs?
- I'm done, thank you.
When I saw the built-ins,
I fell totally in love,
And I put my name on the
list. The owner calls me
Yesterday morning, he said
I could have the place.
But then he called back
an hour later and said
He wasn't renting it,
he was gonna sell it.
Oh, that's so annoying.
Whatever, I'll find a place, I guess.
- It's all good.
- Time's up.
Oh, I was just finding my rhythm.
Next week we start our capelets,
So pick out some colorful
stuff and get ready.
And remember your class fees include
Unlimited knitting circle time,
So feel free to drop in whenever.
- See you next time.
- Ciao-Ciao, victoria.
Ciao.
Suddenly one "ciao" was not enough.
She says everything twice.
So...
Give us the george report.
Well, this week has not been a cakewalk
You don't know what a relief it was
To walk in here and sit down.
What happened?
Oh, he started another
round of electroshock,
Because George and
Maggie think it helps.
But the days after the treatments are
Such a challenge for me.
He comes home so scattered. It's
like dealing with a sleepwalker.
I don't know where you find
the strength to deal with it.
Clearly, I don't either.
Have you signed up
for next week's class?
I haven't yet, no.
Oh, ruth, you must. You're
the only version of my mother
- I can talk to.
- I'll try and make it.
It's all good, right?
Yeah, it is.
Well, I have errands to run,
and Maggie's waiting.
- Bye.
Lila was the most active
person I ever met in my life.
I mean, I try to stay busy
With bridge and the angels.
I'm a big angel fan.
- I can see that.
- But lila,
She was a runaway train!
It's so hard to believe
that she won't be outside
Messing around with her
flowers when I get home.
Are you sure she never
married or had any children?
Oh, she was going to,
But her beau died very young.
After that she ran a resort
Up in Ojal all on her own.
There were families that
came there every year,
And then their kids would come
And their kids would come
And they all kept up with her.
No one in the neighborhood
Got more christmas cards
or visits than Lila.
- Sounds like a good life.
- It was.
Today would have been her 95th birthday.
What?
Well, today is his birthday too.
Oh, how old are you?
- I'm 40.
- Oh, you don't look that old.
- Thank you.
- Are you doing something special?
- Not today,
But my wife and daughter are gonna
take me up to Big Sur next weekend.
Oh. Big sur.
It's so beautiful up there.
So stunning!
I suppose I'll be gone soon too.
I will.
That's okay.
It happens.
Couldn't you say, "roger, partner and
I plan to spend the morning together,
I can't pick up your cat at the vet"?
David, let it go.
Why can't he get one of
his abercrombie & fitch
Party boys to do something like this?
You're a bodyguard,
And I'd like to get to
work at some point today.
Do you like your new plasma tv?
- I do.
- Then let it go.
That cat stinks.
Keith charles!
- And you must be David!
- Yes.
Sissy pasquese.
Come on in. Roger's making kir royales.
- Sister?
- I don't know.
- The kids are almost ready.
- Kids? Ex-Wife?
- I don't know!
- How could you not know?
David, we're married,
Roger's gay, and I'm fine with it.
But we keep it quiet, because
we're very private people.
Thank you.
- That's all I needed.
- Honey, guess who's here.
- Hello.
- Mr. Diaz?
Yes, who is this?
Agnes, I work for the campbells.
Julio came home with lucas after school.
Well, he kind of needs to be picked up.
Okay, my wife vanessa should be
there in a little bit, I think
No, we called her like 10 times,
And she's not answering
her phone or something,
And the campbells left for
arrowhead like an hour ago.
I'm sorry. I'll be right over.
And I told roger 10 years ago,
"Roger, I want out of this goddamn L.A.
It's a plague. I want to go home."
I haven't been back here since,
Except for two-Day trips,
three-Day trips, right?
I miss her when she's gone.
I'm an aspen girl, what can I say?
So, what brings you to town?
A pedunculated fibroid.
Shit for me, huh?
And Tate and Enzo need haircuts.
So, Roger tells me you two
are thinking of adopting.
Looks like that's not happening anymore.
Because you bit roger?
No.
It got complicated.
Shit for you guys, huh?
Keith, you think you could
run the kids by laissez-Faire
While I take sissy to the doctor?
Uh, we actually have an errand
That we need to run at some point.
It's on the way. We'll take them.
Thanks.
Honey, the cat still reeks.
I know, I know.
People do things for
other people. That's okay.
Well, I don't want him
to do it just for me.
- Why the hell not?
- Because I want him
To want to have our baby,
Not to do me the favor
of letting me have mine.
Don't be weirder about this
than you absolutely have to be.
But he should want to
have this as much as I do.
- He has maya already.
- No, it's not the same thing.
Then maybe he's afraid
of losing another one.
You know? And anyway,
Let's say he is doing it just
for you. Is that so terrible?
We had sylvia for all
the perfect both-of-us reasons,
And I had Josh for Mark,
Because he couldn't
imagine life without a boy.
I was happy with one.
Can you not tell anyone
about the pregnancy?
- Fuck you.
- No, I want to wait this time
Until I know everything
is gonna be all right.
Brenda, stop.
I swear, sometimes you're like eeyore.
Check it out.
Oh, that's a good one.
10,000 to go.
But jason is only in
town for tonight, charese.
You have to be there, all right?
You have to! He just
got done with basic,
And he's going, like, in two days!
Then get off work.
I'm trying!
I'm leaving as soon as I can.
Don't get a tone with me
When you can't even get
your butt out of pizza hut.
Oh, hey, mr. Diaz. No, I said the 110.
- Come on, let's go home.
- The 110 to the 710.
Stop for a second and listen to me.
I'm giving you the directions.
For crying out loud!
Next new message:
Today at 2:54 p.M.
Claire, it's Billy.
Uh, sorry about this morning.
Give me a call.
Next new message:
Today at 2:58 p.M.
Claire, hey, it's me.
Are you still at Amoeba?
Because if you are, I really need
to hear some Brian Eno today,
Or I'm going to tear my eyes out.
Oh, shut up.
Next new message:
Today at 3:01
Please, get a life
for one minute, please!
Do you guys have wives
besides being gay?
No.
We're a married couple, essentially.
Well, when our dad married our mom,
He was completely homosexual
in his orientation.
Only he was in such denial about it
Because of the social pressure, it was
like he didn't even know he was gay.
That happens.
Well, it wasn't until he became
a success in his chosen field
That his ego felt, you know,
strong enough to face the truth.
Do you ever have sex with chicks?
- I don't.
- So, you do?
I've had sex with a few women.
- Have you had sex with our dad?
- You are kind of his type.
- Do you guys have orgies?
- Okay, that's enough.
No more talking until
we get to the salon.
They have orgies.
- He was waiting with that girl...
- I'm sorry.
- ... For more than an hour!
- They were gonna be there until 4:00.
- They left early, and she called you.
- My phone didn't ring.
- Oh, bullshit.
- Don't pretend you don't know that shit happens.
I don't have to pretend anything.
The way it is is bad enough.
- If we were still together
- Oh, this wouldn't happen? Bullshit!
- It would happen less!
- Really? What a good point.
I know it's all my fault, vanessa.
Whenever anything goes
wrong with the boys
From now until the end of time
it will be because I went out
And fucked some whore,
oka iaknow, I know, I know!
- Look.
- What?
You wanna hang out for a while?
You wanna stay for dinner?
I was supposed to go to this, hum...
But you know, I can call and change it.
No, you're not doing me any favors.
Oh, god, I didn't say I was
doing you any favors. Shit.
I'm feeling pretty secure now,
But I went through a phase last year
Where, you know,
I was so shy around chicks
Tthat I thought maybe I was gay, too.
I think it's pretty normal to
go through a phase like that.
Yeah it is, but then we had
some group sessions
With our therapists and
dad, and it turned out
What I was really afraid
of was not being gay.
I mean, if I wasn't gay,
Would dad still love me?
So, that cleared it up. I'm not gay,
and I have a girlfriend in Aspen.
- Oh, what's her name?
- Alison. She's bi.
Keith, does this look
completely deviant?
No! Looks good.
We're almost done.
Thank you.
My mom has a friend
back home named vernon,
But she doesn't feel like he'd
be a good sexual partner for her.
I have to say I kind of agree.
You know what? I think I'm gonna
stay here and get a haircut
while you take these two back home.
- If that's okay.
- Sure.
I'll come back and pick you
up after I drop the kids off.
Thanks.
- So how is he doing?
- Not great.
He's been asking to go down
to the bomb shelter again.
I don't think it's a good idea.
I told him I would ask you.
No, I don't want to risk
going through all that again.
We should board that place
up and forget it's there.
Maybe it would be good for him
- To have somewhere
- No.
Did u have a nice time out in the world?
I did. It was a very
nice day, thank you.
- Happy birthday.
Thanks.
The day I turned 40 you were in europe.
I spent the whole day
wondering if you'd call.
Sorry.
Don't apologize, you
did what you had to do.
You little fucker.
So much crazy shit has happened
Since these pictures were taken.
So much.
The idea of
40 more years-
Oh, but the next 40 fly by much faster.
It will be over before you know it.
Time flies when you're having fun, huh?
No, huh-Uh.
Time flies when you're
pretending to have fun.
Time flies when you're pretending to love
Brenda and that baby she wants so much.
Time flies when you're pretending to
know what people mean when they say...
"Love."
Let's face it, buddy boy, there's
two kinds of people in the world
There's you and there's everybody else,
And never the twain shall meat.
Take it.
I got time.
- Hey.
What are you doing?
Still at work. Is everything okay?
Yeah, everything is fine.
- How's the baby?
- Well, I haven't lost it
Since this morning, if
that's what you're asking.
That's not what I meant.
Could you stop by whole
foods on the way home
And pick up some
chocolate silk for maya?
- Yeah, sure.
- And can you call me from there
In case I've forgotten anything?
Look, I'm not gonna come
home to some big fight, am i?
No.
All right.
- Bye.
It's not the size of the animal that makes it deadly,
It's the size of its mouth.
The bigger the mouth
And then we go to the vet,
And then back to the house,
and then all over beverly hills,
And then finally we come here.
It's like his job came and
found my day and ate it.
Well, I learned
when I was a kid-
Don't go to work with
dad, it's never fun.
But saying no is the hardest thing
in the world.
- At least for me.
- Me too.
- Just wait a second.
- What's the matter?
I don't think I should do this.
- All right.
- I mean, you seem really nice...
- That's not a problem.
- ... but keith and I are doing this whole
Surrogacy thing, it's
really confusing, and hard,
And plus I got like abducted last year
Okay, David, you don't have to explain.
Just stay in here a second.
Get your shit together.
Surprise!
Happy birthday!
Happy birthday.
- Hey, thank you
- Give daddy a kiss.
"Oh lordy, nate's
40." Is that your idea?
This is jackie from work.
- Oh, family dinner jackie.
- Yes.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
So the Big Sur thing was just a ruse?
- Why, are you disappointed?
- No no no, not at all.
- You need a beer.
- Yeah, a beer would be great.
Mazel tov, by the way, on the baby.
- Oh, thank you, thank you.
- Yeah, that's great.
- Thank you very much.
- Yeah.
Thank you, god, for this food.
- Amen.
That's it?
"Thank you, god, for this food. Amen"?
Whatever happened to "bless us, o lord,
And these thy gifts which
we are about to receive"?
- We shortened it up. Didn't we?
- Are we sure it's right?
- Yeah, we are.
Want some fritos?
Breakfast in bed.
No, thank you, papito.
I'm good.
Ruth, would you like a refill for that?
Thank you very much.
We're right in
the boondocks, okay?
Pretty soon I saw her
turning into social events
During the week, and
i'd be like "can I come along"?
And she'd be like, "it's
kind of just us, todd,
It's just the club." Next thing I know
She's fucking this guy with nut cancer.
- Jesus!
- Yeah, she's fucking lance armstrong.
No! She's fucking lance armstrong?!
No no, of course not,
but in essence, yeah,
She's fucking lance armstrong.
Here's the keeper. This divorce is
the best thing that ever happened to me.
I've had more ass In the last year
than I've had in my life.
I hate you.
Moral of the story- 40
is only the beginning.
It's just the fucking beginning.
- Here's how, man.
- Cheers.
I used to mountain
bike in griffith park,
And I saw this guy once
who had totally endo'd, you know?
And he was laying 12
fucking feet from his bike.
His ball sack was
completely ripped open.
It was like, uh, two pink eggs
kind of vibrating
In this totally shredded mess.
It was insane.
- Fuck.
- Jesus, billy.
What the fuck, man?
No, I was just thinking
about the guy with nut cancer.
- Yeah, I got you.
- Oh, yeah.
Happy birthday. Sorry we're late.
He had to get a haircut.
- What, for this?
- Yeah, that's what I thought.
- Well, it looks good, I guess.
- Thanks.
So how long have you two
fuckers known about this?
Couple of weeks.
- Yeah, what else aren't you telling me?
- Nothing.
- What?
- I think it's cake time.
- Hey, did you meet him, man?
- Meet who?
- Lance armstrong.
- Dude, I was speaking metaphorically.
Oh, god, where did you
guys get this amazing cake?
This cuban place in atwater.
Porto's. It's in glendale.
Light from a cake is such a great light.
We should just live in cake light.
Yeah, okay, here we go.
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, dear Nate
Happy birthday to you.
Come on, make a wish.
Speech speech speech!
- No.
- Aw, come on, man.
Look, I'm sorry. Seriously,
i don't know what to say
You know, that wouldn't sound lame.
I have something to
say, if that's all right.
Please.
It is the most difcult
thing in the world
To watch your children
grow up and move on.
And when you left home, my firstborn,
I was very sad. Here we go.
This is not about you!
These past five years with
you have been a gift, nate.
That's all I wanted
to say. Happy birthday.
Thank you, mom.
Well, I can't think of
anything to say to add to that, so...
Can I tell 'em?
You're pregnant?
Uh... yeah.
Fantastic!
- Congratulations, my man.
- Thank you.
That's great. Congratulations.
What the fuck?
- Wait, where's maya?
- I've got her.
Sounds like something fell.
- How did it get in?
- Through the window.
So blue.
- It's a good omen.
- Sci-Fi channel says it's a bad omen.
- It's not an omen. It's a bird.
- Amen.
- No, omen, it's pronounced omen.
- Thanks.
Birds don't usually fly at
night. It's probably sick.
Do you think it has avian flu?
Obviously, we don't know.
just open the window, close the door,
And it'll find its own way out.
But he'll poop all over everything
in the meantime.
Well, seriously, what
kind of plan is that,
To let a sick bird run
wild in the house pooping?
You know what, mom? I think
george is right. I am just gonna...
Open the window.
I'm gonna open this door.
Somebody close that door.
- Hey, nate, grab the beer, okay?
- Yeah, I'll grab the beer, tom.
- Thank you.
- It's a beautiful bird.
God, it's fucking cerulean.
So let's just close this door
And see what happens.
Jesus.
- Thanks for letting me stay.
- Sure.
I haven't put the
boys to bed for awhile.
- I miss that.
- Yeah, they miss it too.
What are you doing?
I gotta get the fuck out of here.
- Why?
- I just do.
We'll cruise mulholland.
We'll go to the lookout.
No, I don't want to go.
It's my brother's birthday.
There's a bird in the kitchen.
Isn't being with other people
ever too much for you to deal with?
Yeah, like right now.
Look, there it is.
- Shoo it out the window.
- Wait a second.
- Don't touch it.
- David, shut up.
Good job.
- You're not coming?
- No, I already told you that.
Here. You keep the car.
- You can't walk home.
- Well, if it's too far, I'll take a cab.
Stop it! Just relax and stay, please.
I want you to stay.
Please.
All right.
- But just for a little while, okay?
- Fine.
Fucking-
Fuck!
Shit! God!
Fuck! Shit!
It's just a bird. What is your problem?
I'm just kinda freaked out by things that
are moving around that I can't control.
It's not a problem.
Did you stop taking your medication?
Yeah, but that's a good thing.
- Why?
- Because, claire, okay,
I'm sick of feeling like
i'm living every moment
Inside a giant xeroxed
fucking cotton ball.
- I gotta go outside.
- No, don't go.
I'm just going outside. Will
you fucking listen when I talk?
- Hey, what's going on?
- I'm just going outside.
- Jesus christ.
- What the fuck is going on?
Nothing. Everything is fine.
- He didn't just hit you, did he?
- No.
Would you please stop
being such a freak?
By the way, the bird
is in the bedroom now.
Yeah, well, how did the
bird get in the bedroom?
It flew in the door. Stop fucking up.
She used to be the wife on
that big fat husband show.
- Which one?
- "More for me."
Are you sure this is
the same victoria adams?
Oh, yeah yeah, that show was
a huge hit for seven years,
And then when they finally shut down,
- She opened that knitting store.
- She never mentions it.
Well, then I bet she still
does that winking thing, right?
She does do that winking thing.
Well, that was her
thing on the show, yeah.
- Hey, are you okay?
- Oh, yeah.
"Max the poet, and he's the dog."
What are you reading?
We are reading a book
about a dog who is also a poet.
- Excuse me.
- You are? Great.
Yeah, doggie doggie doggie.
- He's a dog.
- Yep yep.
By the way, just for the record,
I don't know what sissy pasquese
means when she says "private,"
But those kids of hers know
way too much about everything.
I think it's nice they've
been given some perspective.
Yeah, in exchange for a childhood.
Whatever we do, we're not
gonna put our kids through that.
Parents can have a few
secrets. It's not a bad thing.
- I'm serious.
- Fine. We'll have secrets.
You got it.
Okay.
"Paris, the city of
dreams, the city of lights,
The city of love."
You're gonna wake the boys.
No, they sleep through it now.
Okay.
Is this the line to pee?
So the bird's in there now?
- How'd it get in there?
- I don't know.
What did you say to billy?
He was really upset.
I didn't say anything to Billy.
He had some thing with Claire,
- He got mad and he walked out.
- Well, what happened?
You know, I don't know what happened,
Brenda. I guess what usually happens.
- Your brother went fucking mental.
- What did you
Hey, you might want to wait a few
seconds before you go in there.
Thanks.
Why did you fucking invite that guy?
- I thought he was your friend.
- He's not.
- You know, it really...
Excuse me.
I hate that you're always jumping
to conclusions about Billy.
You will never believe
that he's getting better.
No, I won't. I hate that he's
with Claire and in our fucking house.
Yeah, well, at least he
knows how to keep a secret.
Look, I know that you told jackie,
so what's the big fucking deal?
There is a very big difference
between me telling my supervisor,
And you telling our entire
family, who are now looking at me
- Wondering when I'm gonna lose this baby.
- Jesus christ!
This morning I wasn't excited enough,
now I'm too excited.
- What the fuck do you want ?
- No, that wasn't excitement.
- That was macho, aggressive male bullshit.
- What the fuck is this?
When you do stuff like that, it makes me
wonder if we should be together.
We just got married.
Yeah, well, if it's not
right, it's not right.
You might want to light a
match in there. It wasn't me.
You're freaked out right now because
you're pregnant. You see that, don't you?
Yeah, with a baby that
you don't even want.
- Bullshit!
- You don't respect me enough
To wait until we know
that everything's all right
- Before you tell the whole world.
- Shut the fuck up!
I need to pee.
Nate!
Tequila shots in the kitchen.
Get in here!
So you stopped taking it?
- Just like that?
- Yeah.
And you feel...?
I feel a little tingly.
That's about it.
What do they got you on these days?
Well, they just switched
me from lithium to tofranil,
In between the shock treatments.
What are those like?
Honestly... I don't know.
I go in. They put me on a
bed. Ey give me some oxygen.
They say, "you're gonna feel a little prick
in your hand." That always makes me laugh.
And then the next thing I know I wake up
with the worst headache
I've ever had in my life.
Do you think it's helping?
I think that...
As émile coué used to say,
"Every day in every way, i
am getting better and better."
But not everyone agrees.
Yeah, it's hard to
get your shit together
With someone watching all the time.
Yeah, it is.
But when no one's watching,
then where are you?
Where the fuck are you then?
Daddy sang bass
Mama sang tenor
Me and little brother
would join right in there
Singin' seemed to
help a troubled soul...
I'm gonna take off.
Why don't you give these to claire?
- Yeah, sure.
- Thanks.
Happy birthday.
"Louie's wearing the green hat."
- Who's that?
- Louis.
Louis. That's right.
- Hey.
You must be looking
forward to this routine.
Yeah, I think it's gonna be wonderful.
Oh, come on.
Who's got on the blue coat?
- Who's that?
- Bear.
- The bear, the bear.
- The bear.
For so many years,
David was always the one saying,
"Come on, let's have kids."
And I was the one on the fence,
But now that it's actually gonna happen,
I'm finally realizing that
I'm gonna be disappointed
if it doesn't work out.
Oh, it'll work out.
It's like I'm already missing this
kid that we don't even have yet.
I mean, don't get me
wrong, david's excited too.
Oh, yeah, you know, Nate too.
It's a team effort.
- I'll let you guys have your moment.
- Say "good night, uncle Keith."
- Good night, uncle keith.
- Good night.
Are you sleepy, little one?
- Could you turn the light off?
- Oh, yeah, sure.
And close the door, thanks.
Okay, little one, I think
that's enough for tonight.
Raspberry.
Everything tastes like beer right now.
- Hey.
Hey.
George told me
That billy told him to
tell you to give you these.
Billy left?
That's what george said.
- I'm sorry. You want some cake?
- No.
- Come on, have some.
- Hey, dude, leave her alone.
I can take care of myself, thanks.
Looks like it's cake time.
- I've been saving up for this.
- Oh, good.
Fuck. All right, fine,
i'll have a piece.
Here you go.
I'm in here.
- Hey.
- Sorry.
No, that's okay. It's cool.
I just needed a moment.
Yeah, me, too.
- Is it gone ?
- Yeah
Finally.
You know, mom and george, they left.
I'm getting a ride from Keith and David.
Oh.
- Tequila?
- Sure.
Thanks.
"Para riva, para bajo,
para centro, para dentro."
Impressive.
Yeah, many years in
arizona, much tequila.
Oh.
Good birthday?
Yeah, it's okay.
Feel like all I can
get out of this birthday
Is that life is really fucking lonely.
You have this wonderful family
- And a baby on the way.
- I know.
And it's really fucking lonely.
I just feel like all I do all day long
Is manage myself,
Try to fucking connect with people.
But it's like no matter how much energy
You pour into,
getting to the station on time
Or getting on the right train,
There's still no fucking guarantee
that anybody's gonna be there for you
To pick you up when you get there.
You know what I mean?
Well, I know that
if you think life's a vending machine,
Where you put in virtue
And you get out happiness,
Then you're probably
gonna be disappointed.
I know that.
- Is that how I sound?
- A little.
Nate! Nate! Get in here!
- Fuck!
- I don't think believe it.
Oh my god!
- Well, how the fuck did it get in again?
- Through the window.
- Yeah, why was the window open?
'Cause you said it was in the
bedroom. Don't be such a jerk.
Fuck off.
I have to do every
littlefucking thing myself.
I have tried all night long
To do the right thing by this bird,
But it just keeps fucking with me.
- Try not to take it personally.
- Shut up, David.
Nate!
Get out!
Jesus christ, chill.
Get the motherfuck out!
How many times do I have
to fucking apologize?
Sorry.
I'm so sorry that I'm putting
you through all of this.
- It's not your fault. I know that.
- No, you don't.
You say that you do, but I can
tell by the way you look at me,
You think that all of this is my fault.
You don't wanna make love to
me. You don't wanna kiss me.
- You don't wanna be in the same room with me!
- That's not true.
Oh, yes, it is!
Ruth... Don't you understand?
Nobody grows up thinking this is
the way they're gonna turn out to be.
If I could change just
by snapping my fingers,
- I'd do it.
- I know you would, George.
I am trying...
So hard to get better.
- And you are.
- But not fast enough for you!
You're getting better as
fast as you can. I know that.
I am so lucky.
I hate that I'm the lucky one.
No one's ever lucky to have me.
Nobody's ever been lucky to have me.
It's good, right?
Rico, wake up.
Baby, hurry up. You
gotta get out of here.
Why?
I don't want the boys to
see you. It'll confuse them.
Oh.
All right.
I know there's beautiful snow there
- No, that's great.
I just, you know...
Thank you.
Okay, bye.
Who was that?
- Roger.
- What did he want?
It turns out sissy was the board chair
- Of an adoption agency once.
- Yeah...
She called in a favor, and she
said we could adopt through them,
- If we still wanted to.
- We kind of made a commitment to mary.
I know, but we don't know for sure
that that's really going to work out.
We always said we'd pursue both options
Until it made sense to stop, right?
Yeah, I guess so.
So now roger's your hero?
A little.
So you got like almost no
haircut yesterday, right?
He just took a little off the top.
Where have you been?
Nowhere. I stayed at my house.
You fucked somebody.
It's okay.
I'm not mad.
Just tell me who it was.
Was it that divorced guy?
- Billy, come on.
- I forgive you, Claire.
You can just admit it.
Just- Just be
honest with me.
Yeah, it was him.
Okay.
Will you fuck me now?
- Please.
- No.
- You know I forgive you, claire, hmm?
It's okay.
Just fuck me now.
- Come on, take off your pants.
- No!
- Please? Come on.
- Get the fuck away from me!
But I forgive you.
- Come on, I need to be inside you.
- No!
I'm sorry.