Sous-titres par la Fisher Team
Transcript : RaceMan
Adaptation :
Sylvain, Petrushka, Paqui, KB
Sous-titrage : EZ, Occeane, KB
Relecture et corrections finales :
KB, Guzo
www.sixfeetunder-france.com
www.forom.com
EVERYONE'S WAITING
She's crowning. She's crowning.
Okay, you're doing great.
Just relax. Easy.
Breathe.
You're doing fine. Just keep breathing.
Why isn't she crying ?
She just needs a little help
getting her airways open.
- She's not breathing !
- We're gonna help get her breathing.
Okay...
- Is she alive ?
- Yes, she's alive.
Where are they taking her ?
She's so small. So tiny.
Only 2 Ibs. 4 oz.
A very kind nurse told me she's
seen plenty of premature births
And she could usually tell which ones...
I don't know if I could...
I-
I can't take another child dying.
Anyway, I'm at Cedars-Sinai.
Brenda's in room...
913.
Poor thing, her mother
won't be back until tomorrow.
It's only me here.
I'm sure you'll want to come too.
Okay, bye.
I hope you're okay.
And I hope you will please
call me and let me know you are.
I know you're mad about
me taking the keys,
But don't be stupid, claire.
Yeah, the world is fucked up,
But you ending up in a wheelchair
isn't going to make it any better.
You're too smart.
You're too good.
Don't waste that.
Okay, I just turned into my father...
Like exactly. That was my father.
This is what you do to me.
Call me please.
When you said go away,
I didn't think you meant "Go away ! "
This is bullshit and you know it.
So this is what happens
when I really need you.
It's nice to know I can
depend on you in a crisis.
This is for us.
No, this is for you,
you arrogant macho fuck !
You think everybody's supposed to
be so fucking strong all the time !
You can't stand to
see me weak like this.
You're revolted by me.
"This is for us. ". Fucking liar !
I meant all four of us,
you fuckin' idiot !
- You never even wanted those kids...
- That's not fair.
...and now you honestly think you
can take care of them on your own ?
You're not up to being
a single parent, Keith.
Well, you're not up to
being a parent at all.
You are using this as
an excuse to dump me,
Which you've wanted to do ever
since Anthony and Durrell came here !
Don't touch me.
Come here !
- God !
- David, I love you.
But I am those boys' father,
And right now I have to take
care of them, because you can't.
You are sick, and I don't
think you can get well here.
Jesus, when am I gonna find a
fucking medication that works ?
She has a pretty severe lack
of surfactant in her lungs,
But she is breathing
steadily with a ventilator.
I wanna see her. Why hasn't
somebody brought her in ?
Well, she's in an incubator, and she's
hooked up to monitors, a feeding tube.
Then why doesn't
somebody take me to her ?
She's my baby. You
can't keep her from me.
We're still looking for sepsis,
possible bleeds in the brain.
- Oh god.
- Most babies born before 30 weeks
Experience cranial bleeding
with varying degrees of severity.
- When can I see her ?
- As soon as she's ready.
I promise you someone
will come take you to her.
Oh god.
Don't you worry.
Willa is going to get
through this and be healthy,
And she's going to
be home with you soon.
And Maya is gonna be home with you too.
I know you don't like kiwi...
But, really, I think you need
to give it a second chance.
What ?
Was that pushy ?
No.
No, it's just I'm eating fruit salad
In bed with a naked frat boy
who voted for George Bush.
We're listening to what sounds
suspiciously like... christian music ?
It is christian music.
What ?
I just hear songs on the radio
And if I like them, I buy the cd.
Oh my god,
You might be the most deeply
un-Hip person I've ever met.
Ah, seeing how being hip is
primarily an adolescent concern,
I'll take that as a compliment.
You know, if you really are christian...
Um, I should probably
tell you I had an abortion.
That's okay...
I sort of paid for one.
Well i... didn't really pay for it.
I still have to send her the check.
God, I feel like I'm trapped underwater.
And it's not just Nate dying.
I mean, I have absolutely no idea
What I am supposed to do with my life.
Don't you still wanna be an artist ?
Yeah.
But I'm scared that
maybe I'm not good enough.
Is that true ?
- Maybe.
- So get better.
I really don't want
to go back to school.
I mean, even though it's art, I still
feel that I'm just being programmed.
Just take pictures. If you're
good enough, you'll find out.
And if you're not,
you'll get good enough.
Or you'll find out you can't.
But I bet you are, though.
Maybe I should take
pictures of you naked.
Okay.
But you have to promise that you
won't post them on the internet.
I might want to run for
public office some day.
- Are you serious ?
- Yeah.
Aren't you ?
Too bad you don't
believe in anything...
Or you could pray.
This is exactly what I was afraid of.
Fuck !
Come on, charles. You're our hero !
- I'm no hero.
- Sure you are.
You've gotta snap out of it. You
have to remember the good times !
- Like when ?
- Like over there !
Uh, boys...
I'm gonna be taking off for a few days.
- Why ?
- Well-
'Cause y'all are splittin' up,
And you're gonna leave us
with him. That's why.
- Like we don't know.
- Durrell.
- I'm not leaving,
- Yeah, well, why you have a suitcase ?
look...
I have to go away for now...
Because there's a funeral
directors' conference in portland.
Do you want me to bring
you something back ?
Yeah, bring me a silver Escalade.
Durrell, I promise
you I am coming back-
I heard that before !
Are you gonna bathe yours ?
Fuffle with it.
- Tulips.
- Pretty !
You leave your door open like that ?
We were just outside picking flowers.
Ruth, it isn't the '50s
anymore, no matter how you dress.
So you're ready to go,
you little monkey ?
No !
- No ? !
- Go where ?
Well, back to Brenda's of course.
Brenda said you agreed to that.
Well, yes, but I thought Brenda was
staying in the hospital a little longer.
Brenda's not the one who's sick,
And anyway, she can't
really visit the baby after 10:00 p.m.
So she's coming home tonight.
And the baby's staying in the
hospital an extra couple of weeks.
I suppose I'd better
go pack her things then.
That would be helpful, Ruth.
So he says the house
alone is worth $2 million.
So 25%, I should be entitled
to half a miion dollars.
- What "should be" ? You are.
- Are we gonna have $1 million ?
Mm-Hmm, someday, if you eat your eggs.
You know, I could put half of that
down as a deposit on the new place,
Spend 100 or so on upgrades.
The rest would tide us over
until we got things going.
Yeah. You really think this could work ?
You know what, Rico ?
I liked when I helped you out
with that funeral yesterday.
It was sort of like being a nurse,
But without all the blood
and bedpans and pills...
And I got to wear better clothes.
Julio, please, eggs.
Augusto thinks they're gross.
Well... they are kind of gross,
But eat 'em anyway.
All you gotta do now is get
the Fishers to buy you out.
Or sell...
Preferably to someone who just
wants the house and the land
And wants to shut the business down.
What ?
Nate left his part to Brenda.
I don't think she wants to
be in the funeral business.
I think David's going kind of nuts.
He needs to get out.
Plus, who needs the
competition anyway, you know ?
- Hello ?
- Hi.
I just thought I'd check in with you.
How are you doing ?
Any news about Willa ?
No, and I'm fine.
Doesn't sound very convincing.
Well, I'm sorry, George, but
I have enough to worry about
Without having to convince
you how I'm feeling.
- Another bad day ?
- Yes, it's a terrible day.
Brenda's mother came and took Maya.
Now I'm alone.
I'm finally completely alone.
Oh, honey.
You're not alone. You have me.
George, I have to go. David's here.
I can't be at home right now.
Where will you go ?
Here.
Go put your things upstairs then.
I'll make you some cereal.
Would you like it in your yellow bowl ?
Mom, I don't think I've eaten out
of that yellow bowl
Since I was a little boy.
Yeah, put it in the yellow bowl.
Yeah, uh,
I'm looking for Claire Fisher.
This is Dennis at New Image
And I'm just calling to find out
where I should
- Hello.
- Hi, Claire Fisher ?
Yeah ?
I need an address to send
your application package to.
Are you from the temp agency ?
No, I'm from New Image.
'Re a stock photo production
house in New York city.
What kind of application ?
Photographer's assistant.
It's like a training position.
About a quarter of our staff
photographers started out as assistants.
Really ?
Uh, really.
All I could think of is maybe
the gallery owner from my show
Is the one who suggested me. Or maybe
it was Billy. Yeah, he would do that,
Partly just to make me feel
guilty for dumping him. Fuck that.
And the pay is shit, I'm sure.
But it is a job, New York city !
I actually could move up to
become a staff photographer,
Although I'm not gonna get my hopes
up like I did about that grant.
It's wonderful to hear.
You couldn't pay me to
live in New York city.
Would you like a bowl of cereal ?
Um, no thanks.
I'm not sure who designed
the stained-Glass window.
I heard it was a somewhat
influential artist.
Uh, what about the water
problems in the basement ?
Oh, big repair job less than a year ago.
They completely redid the plumbing as
well as all the underground drainage.
- What did I tell you ?
- Wow !
Yes, apparently, there was
some sort of a... a problem.
Eh, when everything gets backed up,
Then blood comes out of the toilet.
Yeah, that happens.
Can we get a copy of the
work report and the guarantee ?
- Yes.
- Great.
I will have the seller
fax that over to you.
We could put an espresso
bar in this nook.
You know, I always wanted to do that,
But David thought it
would be disrespectful.
Great.
Very nice.
I can't say she's out
of the woods for sure.
You'll have to watch
and see how she develops
To know if there's any
permanent brain damage.
But, from a physical standpoint,
She is doing remarkably well.
Thank God.
She's been taking your milk from
the bottle all the time now, right ?
- Right.
- Then I think we can
Permanently remove that feeding tube.
When can I take her home ?
Well, I'd like to keep
her another 24 hours
After the tube comes out
just to be on the safe side.
So there's absolutely no sign
of spina bifida or down's ?
Definitely neither of those.
And you checked
for every possible problem
That the triple marker
could have found ?
And I can't find anything.
Nothing that would be
apparent at this point anyway.
Great. So she'll seem normal for a while
Before whatever's fucked
up about her shows up.
Well, that's positive
news, isn't it, sweetheart ?
Shut up, Marge, you fuckin' idiot.
The fact she was premature
Has something to do with that
blood test and you know it.
There's something wrong with our baby.
You should never have had her.
- Oh God.
- For Christ's sake, Brenda,
There's something to feel good about.
Don't shit all over it !
Thank you, doctor.
I got him
Don't ever do that !
- What ? Do what ?
- Pop up like that.
- Like this ?
- Don't !
Ruth ?
The back door is open.
Yes, I suppose someone could just
come in and murder me in cold blood,
- Which would be a blessing.
- Ruthie...
It just takes time.
Liar.
That's what everybody
always says and it's a lie.
Each day I feel worse,
More empty, more dead.
I barely even remember
my life before Nate.
I was practically a
child when I had him.
How can I live without him ? I can't.
Yes, you can... for Maya.
They've taken Maya.
I will probably never see
her or her sister again...
If her sister even survives.
Ruth...
I promise you, you
will get through this.
I don't wanna get through it !
This is the worst thing that
can ever happen to anyone.
This is hell, George, hell,
And I just want it to end.
Then let me take care of you.
Let me make sure you don't
go through this alone.
You did it for me.
Now it's my turn.
To do what ?
Feel helpless while you
watch me lose my mind ?
Just... let me hold you.
Absolutely not !
This is my family's
business and I won't sell it.
So... buy me out.
Fine !
But I hope that you're aware that
this place Is probably worth $2 million.
I had it appraised.
So what do you want to
do with your part, Brenda ?
I don't really care.
Sorry, David, I don't.
You know what ? I don't
really care either.
Why am I fighting for something
I've always been ambivalent about ?
Habit.
So... we put it on the market ?
Sure. Why not ?
Cool.
I mean, if we can make
that kind of money,
Why hang on to it ?
I have no reason.
We've been clutching so desperately
to the past, and for what ?
Because that's when there was hope.
Um, I'm going over to Ted's tonight.
Take a sweater ! Oh... damn !
- What is she doing ?
- I have no idea.
Mom ?
Maya's monkey !
She loves this monkey !
I have to wash it.
I think it's great.
I mean, think of what we can do
with your portion and my savings.
We could finally buy a house.
We could buy a house now.
But we could buy a house and
you could go back to school
And become a lawyer like
you've always dreamed.
I don't think I ever really
even wanted to be a lawyer.
I think I just wanted to
have sex with Harry Hamlin.
I'm serious. You can be
whatever you wanna be, David.
- So can you.
- Exactly.
We could really buy a house,
couldn't we, with a yard ?
We could get the boys
a dog and a tire swing.
Those boys don't want a tire swing,
they want a tv the size of a wall.
So do you think you're
rea to come back home soon ?
- Because I do.
- Maybe.
Good.
Man, those are big teeth.
Whoa, look at the wolf
brain made into asphalt !
- Wow !
- But it looks like poop !
Cool.
No, it's not cool.
And you saying it is just
makes it even more not cool.
I think it's cool.
Thank you, Anthony.
I've never never seen you act this way !
- So ?
- Yeah, so it has to be analyzed
And diagnosed and turned into an
example of some kind of pathology.
I mean, this is the Chenowith family.
Oh god, Billy ! Have a drink !
That's what you are
born into. I'm sorry.
Aren't they funny ?
Oh, dear, she's having guests.
Mom, she knows we're coming.
- I called her.
- I can't go in. I'll wait in the car.
Mrs. Fisher,
I think Maya would be very
happy to see her monkey.
And to see you.
- Oh, hi.
- Hey !
Come on in. Everyone's in the kitchen.
- Mrs. Fisher.
- Hi.
Hi. Ted.
This is Billy, Brenda's brother.
- Oh, Billy.
- Ted.
I've heard a lot about
you. Nice to meet you.
Yeah, nice to meet you too !
What-What is that ?
Do you, can you tell me ?
Can you tell me ?
Does the monkey know ?
You're so pensive, what
are you thinking about ?
Oh, just how much it sucks
that we have to get old.
Oh Claire, please,
don't get maudlin on me.
So Brenda tells me you're
planning on moving to new york ?
Uh, maybe.
I've applied for this,
like, entry-level position
At this, like, stock photo house...
.. New Image.
- Impressive.
- Not really.
It's just a lame gofer job
like I used to do for you.
No, it isn't.
You could easily go on to become a
soulless advertising photographer.
And with your gifts, hmm,
I'm sure you probably will.
And I'm the one who recommended you.
Shut the fuck up.
Claire, it doesn't matter
who fucked Russell.
I still believe in you.
Jesus, Olivier,
That's so nice of you.
Thank you so much.
Calm down. I mean, you
just popped into my mind
Because I'd just seen
you at that junior show.
Maya,
Don't you want to show
grandma your okapi ?
- Okapi !
- Yes !
I don't believe I've
ever heard of an okapi.
Oh, the okapi is the only known
living relative of the giraffe.
Its young really don't seem
to imprint on the mothers,
So they nurse from many
available lactating females.
We just went to the zoo this week.
So, uh...
How long have you and Claire been...
- Together ?
- Uh...
Well, we met, I guess it was about..
Four months ago.
Well, we..
We really didn't hit it
off that great at first.
- Really ?
- Yeah.
I was there when she
got the call about Nate
And I spent most of that night
In the hospital with her.
That's how my sister met her brother.
The night his father died.
Really ?
What are you saying, it
like runs in the family ?
I am so...
Jealous of you.
Excuse me a second.
She looks much stronger.
Oh, she is. She's much stronger.
No, she's not.
She's barely moving.
She's a very calm baby.
I think she's blind.
She gets stronger every day.
Oh, she's fierce when she nurses.
I'm covered in bruises.
Nate had a big appetite.
Is she gassy ?
No, not overly so,
But she's always hungry.
That's because she knows
she doesn't have much time.
She wants to get it while she can.
So you're really going
to sell your legacy ?
- Your birthright ?
- Yeah, and good riddance.
Well, I can't say I'm surprised.
You never had it in you.
Neither did you. The only
way you could handle it
Was to have a secret room over
a really bad indian restaurant.
And you don't think
you have a secret room ?
What do you think being
gay is, you fucking freak ?
Fuck you.
What did you just say to me ?
Leave me alone, dad.
Who do you think you are ?
You think you can just
walk away from this ?
Are you really that stupid ?
- It only gets closer, david.
- Shut up.
You don't exist.
the window washer's been right outside
This whole time watching
me change my stockings.
yes, I will call you later.
Okay, bye.
Actually, he's pretty cute.
Dark hair and good build.
- What are you watching ?
- Hello, mr. Clean.
- I don't know. It's always on.
- I've been a very dirty girl.
Isn't it weird this isn't gonna
be our house anymore ?
I guess I'll move in with Ted,
Although I really hate his apartment.
Mom, what are you gonna do ?
I suppose I'll move in with George.
- Yeah ?
- He's offered.
Well, is that what you want ?
I'll never have what I want, never.
- Hello ?
- Is this Claire ?
Yeah.
This is scott in accounting
at new image.
I need you to send me your
social and address in New York.
I don't have an address in New Nork.
I live in California.
That's gonna be an awfully big commute.
Does that mean I have the job ?
I have you down as starting
work on december 7th.
You do ? Oh my god, mom !
Hello ?
I can give you my social now.
Can I give you my in New York
address a little bit later...
- Like when I actually have one ?
- Sure.
I called off Escrow.
You did what ?
This is my family's business,
Rico, and I won't sell it.
I'm sorry.
Well then, you have to buy me out.
I don't have that kind of money.
So, what ? I'm just fucked ?
Maybe you can find someone
to buy your share out.
Nobody's gonna wanna pay
half a million dollars
For 25% of this business,
you fuckin' moron !
If they have that kind of money,
They're gonna want to
Open up their own place.
Something smaller. Something
they can finally call their own
And run the way they want
without a bunch of idiots
Always getting in their fucking way !
Oh, just throw it out.
Really ? I always liked this on you.
It itches.
My entire life I've been
wearing clothes that I hate.
I've been meaning to ask
you, how is Maggie doing ?
I have no idea.
Maggie left over a month ago.
Left ? Where did she go ?
I don't know.
You don't even know where
your own daughter is ?
Ruth, please, don't sensationalize it.
George, don't talk to me like
you're my father or my teacher.
Do you have any idea how much
I hate it when you do that ?
I saw Maggie...
Just before Brenda gave birth.
And she was completely irrational.
She was very very angry.
- With you ?
- No
I think she was angry
with the state of her life.
She just chose to take it out on me.
What state of her life ?
I don't know. She didn't tell me.
- You didn't ask ?
- No, I didn't.
She told me she would call
me when she got settled.
Look, this is not the
first time it's happened.
I don't think I can move
in with you, George.
Why not ?
Because
Don't get me wrong,
You're a good, decent,
Man with a big heart.
But there are walls around that heart
Walls behind walls behind walls.
And I can spend a certain
amount of time around that,
But I cannot live with it, not anymore.
Oh, don't look so sour.
It doesn't mean I won't go out with you.
We can have a lot more fun this way.
Believe me...
I could use a little fun.
Father, we thank thee for
these and all thy blessings.
Amen !
Not so fast.
We thank thee for the
gift of this food...
And please thank the animals who
gave their lives so we could eat,
For the love we feel for each other,
Even when it's hard,
Especially when it's hard.
And finally for these two boys...
Who came into our lives
and made us a family,
And who have given us a home
Every bit as much as we have them.
- Amen.
She can't breathe.
She can't get any oxygen to her brain !
- Why can't you love her ?
- Because she's damaged...
And nobody will ever be able to fix her.
Ever.
I talked to my accountant today.
Between the two of us,
we can buy Rico out.
Keith, I can't let you do that.
- That money is yours.
- That money is ours...
For our new house.
I don't know if you've realized,
but that house you grew up in
Is a pretty great fuckin' house.
You don't find this depressing ?
I don't think it has to be.
I think we can make it into
something pretty spectacular.
- You're serious ?
- Yeah.
I am.
Maggie, Dr. Peterman will see you now.
Okay, thank you.
Just give me a second. Sorry.
This is Maggie.
Thank heavens you still have
the same cell phone number.
Ruth ?
I have to ask you something.
Sure.
You were with Nate the night he...
Yes.
Was he happy ?
He was...
Feeling, I think, that his
life was very complicated.
I'm not talking about his life,
I'm talking about that night.
Was...
Was he happy ?
He was.
Good.
Were you ?
Yes.
Yes, I was happy.
Good.
Thank you for that.
It helps.
Ruth...
I'm sorry.
I have to go.
We're not asking you
to give us anything.
We're just asking you to
let us buy you out over time.
We'll pay you as soon
as we can. I promise.
Okay.
Look, my dad left me a ton of money.
Plus, Nate had life
insurance, believe it or not.
So take your time.
Thank you.
Come on, we're family.
Yeah, we are.
Yes, we are.
- Hello.
- Hello, Ruth.
- How's the baby doing ?
- She's good.
I have new photos !
Thank you.
My goodness !
Look at those eyes !
What do you mean ?
Do you see something wrong ?
Oh no, it's just that it seems
like she sees more than we do,
Like she's a very old soul.
You poor dear.
You're still worried
about her, aren't you ?
She seems good.
Every visit to the doctor goes fine.
I just can't shake the feeling
That something' going to go wrong,
- Something is wrong.
- You're all alone.
If my experience is anything to go by,
Motherhood is the loneliest
thing in the world.
Nathaniel wasn't even
here when Nate was born.
He was still in Vietnam.
Even when he came
home and David was born
And having terrible asthma,
Nathaniel was never really here for me.
Whether it was the war or just
him, I don't think I'll ever know.
- You know Nate and I were
- I know, I know.
I know he loved you
the very best he could,
And I know you needed more.
So did I.
And I hope and pray
that you put everything
Everything behind us
and let me help you,
Because I know you're gonna need it.
Thank you.
I will need it.
I do need it.
- Do we have to move ?
- No.
We're gonna keep living here.
Maybe we'll move, eventually,
If things go well.
But I like this house.
What if you got to have your own room ?
- Okay.
To the...
Future.
Yes, baby.
Mom.
I don't know why I keep looking at this.
It certainly doesn't
make me feel any better.
God, I would give anything if I
could make things different for you.
I would too.
You know what ?
I don't think I'm gonna go to New York.
Olivier says it's a crappy
place to work anyway.
And I have no idea how to go
about finding a place to live.
You would do that ?
You would... stay here for me ?
Yes.
Absolutely not !
Go. Live.
I'll unfreeze your trust fund.
Take it and find whatever
life has in store for you.
Well...
Are you still gonna move
in with George ?
No
No, I'm moving in with Sarah.
She's back from Costa Rica ?
No, Bettina's house-Sitting,
but I'm moving in anyway.
If Sarah doesn't like
it, it's too fucking bad.
Mom, really, I can wait.
Claire, I stayed home to
take care of a sick woman,
And I've always regretted it.
I don't regret you or any of my children
Or... Nathaniel even,
But I do regret
Never giving myself any choice.
I won't let you make the same mistake !
Mom.
Oh, my little girl.
Maya ?
Maya, are you okay ?
She's beautiful.
She's so beautiful.
Hi. We've never met. I'm Nathaniel.
I love her so much.
And I always will.
You have to promise me
you won't listen to this
Until you start to drive
away tomorrow morning.
I can't play it tonight at
my big farewell dinner...
That you won't even come to ?
everybody's gonna want a piece of you.
I'm sorry, but...
I don't want to share you.
That's sweet.
And strangely possessive.
I want you to promise me something too.
I want you to promise
That if the corporate warmongers
decide we have to invade Iran
- And they reinstate the draft...
- That's not gonna happen.
- ... That you will move to Canada.
- It's not gonna happen.
Probably not. But, if they do...
Promise me...
That you won't go get
your head blown off
So Halliburton and
Bechtel can get richer.
I promise.
You're too smart. You're too good.
Don't waste that.
I promise.
- A what ?
- A meth lab.
Marcie, get serious !
I don't even know what that is.
It's illegal and she's pulling your leg.
We'd make a lot of money.
So could opening our own
professional assassin service,
- But that's not gonna happen either.
- Why not ? I think I'd like that.
- We could steal people's kidneys.
- Oh, God,
No ! It's too messy.
I heard on NPR
About those people that go in
and clean up violent crime scenes.
- They make a shitload of money !
- No !
I'm not going to clean up
someone else's violent crime.
We just have to accept it.
There's nothing else. We
have to become hookers.
I'm thinking of starting
a day-care service.
- Seriously ?
- Yes, for dogs.
Well, I wasn't aware
such a thing existed
Until Nate worked in
one briefly last year.
But apparently a lot of people
will pay you a lot of money
To babysit their dogs.
Let's face it, dogs are a
lot easier than children.
They just are.
No offense, honny.
There's George.
Hi, George. Come join us.
Georgie porgie. He hates me.
Claire, hi, this is gavin at new image
And I hate to be the one
to tell you this, but...
New image has been
bought by stock options,
And they're consolidating
their operations, and...
Well, they're in Chicago, so I hope
you haven't headed out here yet.
Sorry.
Aw, who cares ?
Go anyway.
What, are you crazy ?
I'm gonna move to new
york city without a job ?
Mom gave you the money, you're
gonna land somewhere. You'll be fine.
You're talented, you're smart,
- You're ready.
- What if I'm not ?
Claire, you want to know a secret ?
I spent my whole life being scared.
Scared of not being
ready, of not being right,
Of not being who I should be.
And where did it get me ?
What should I tell everyone tonight ?
Nothing !
You can't stay here !
You've done a great job.
And this is video game central.
I've made it to Moscow on
"Tony Hawk underground. "
- That'll come in handy.
- You can't imagine the
respect it bought me.
Boy, what have you done in here ?
Well, we replaced the
jalousie windows place
- With these double-Hung windows.
- That looks great.
It's like I never lived here.
Maya
- There's so much space, though.
- Just beige, though.
Beige beige beige.
- I love this.
- This is the
-  Three fours.
- Does it hurt to have a baby ?
Yes, it does.
It's beautiful I admit it,
but it's a little intimidating.
it's gay.
This is a 100% gay kitchen.
This table looks sort of out of place.
David says they keep
meaning to get rid of it.
I suppose they'll get around to it.
Oh my God, you remember that
one dinner that he came to
And he was high on ecstasy,
which he had taken by accident ?
- What's ecstasy ?
- It's medicine.
I must have missed that one.
Nate kept groping my
breasts through the meal.
I was mortified.
I walked in on the two of you in
much more mortifying circumstances.
Okay, that we will not get into
with younger ears at the table.
- Tell me.
- What, tell me !
I just remember I don't know,
I was in seventh grade,
I think Nate was probably a
junior in high school...
And he had started that new wave band
With Sam Hoviak and Tom
Wheeler, do you remember ?
I do.
He had the worst hair. I
mean really big, bad '80s hair
With all this spray and lacquer in it.
And I was sitting next to him at dinner,
And I saw something move,
And it was a spider.
It had spun a web in his hair.
- I swear.
- Sick !
And I didn't say anything because
I knew how cool he was trying to be.
And...
I wanted him to be that
cool. I wanted him to be...
The coolest brother
anybody had ever had.
To Nate.
To Nate
To my first-born.
- To uncle Nate.
- Yeah, to uncle Nate.
Can you say "to daddy" ?
To daddy.
To Nate.
May he rest in peace.
Hey.
Get up.
Come on, everybody's waiting.
I have no idea how to do this.
You just say "goodbye. "
And just say "I love you. "
I'll miss you.
Oh god, I'm gonna miss you so much.
Be happy.
I am.
Mom.
My sweet baby girl.
Don't let them work you
too hard at your new job.
I won't.
Mom, I really hope
you can come and visit.
I'll try.
Claire.
I pray you will be filled with
hope as long as you possibly can.
Thank you for everything.
And thank you for giving me life.
You gave me life.
Oh, God, I don't want to go.
Yes, you do !
What, are you trying to sneak out on us ?
- Bye, aunt claire.
- Bye.
Bye, Anthony.
- You gonna come visit me in New York ?
- Yes.
Could you...
Get me something from the
fire department museum ?
- It's in Brooklyn.
- Durrell.
Durrell's going to be a fireman.
Did you know my dad used to be a cop ?
I did.
He looked really good in his uniform.
Come here.
I want to take a
picture of everyone.
You can't take a picture
of this. It's already gone.
So as the blood is
draining out of the body
It flows down into that drain there.
It's replaced with this embalming fluid.
So I'm expecting
I'm expecting
Some form of...
Response, emotional response.
Ted responded in a way that
I felt some emotional closure was necessary
Was necessary for me.
This is something that I have
spent a lot of time working
Bren ?