Come on, I'm open. Over here.
Pass the ball.
Come on.
My grandma can kick harder than that.
Shoo! Go, now.
Roderick, can I offer you
a slice of my buttermilk pie?
- Is that the same pie you made last year?
- Yes, it is.
Then... no, thank you.
Roderick, can't you be nice?
She's your aunt. You eat her sour pie.
Well, maybe I'll have one more small piece.
I'll have a piece of pie.
Dammit.
Aunt Jeanie, did you get stung?
Why, yes.
I got stung by a bee. It's not that bad.
She's allergic. I'm calling 911.
Hello. I'm calling from Bellvale Park.
My wife's aunt got stung by a bee.
She's having an allergic reaction.
- Aunt Jeanie?
- Do something.
Talk to them. Jeanie?
By the east entrance.
Where you walk down that little hill.
What's wrong with her? Is she gonna be OK?
She's gonna be OK, sweetheart.
Help's on the way.
That feels so good.
My God. Wow!
- That was nice, baby.
- Nice? That was amazing.
It's great that, you know, you wanted to.
Of course I wanted to.
I mean, it's been a long time since you...
I mean, it's great that you wanted to.
I have a surprise for you.
Whoa.
OK, but you're gonna have to give me
five minutes. Ten minutes, tops.
It's a different kind of surprise.
I signed us up for a dance class tonight.
A dance class? Really?
Salsa, tango, merengue.
Merengue.
Wow. My mom used to do that.
- She won trophies.
- Maybe I'll win one.
- I'm gonna go make some coffee.
- No, no.
I'll do it.
Julio! Augusto! Time to get up!
By dipping the sponge applicator
into cold water
and applying it to Barbie's
lips, cheeks and eyelids,
you get a flourish of glamorous colour.
I'm telling Taylor you took it out of the box.
When I was a kid, I used to have GI Joes.
They were always getting court-martialled,
which in my version meant that they had
to stand naked in front of the other dolls.
Is that something you wanna act out?
I think we've had enough excitement
for a while.
- The three-ways?
- Yeah.
- What about them?
- Maybe they're not the best thing for us.
Really? That wasn't you the other night
begging us to arrest and interrogate you?
I'm not saying they're not fun.
- So what are you saying?
- I'm just starting to feel weird about it.
- OK, fine.
- Fine?
- Yeah, whatever.
- That is so not fair.
You ask me to tell you how I feel
and when I do you just shut down.
I don't feel like talking about it right now.
You're tense
because we're going to see your father.
We're going to my great-aunt's funeral.
Where your father will be
and whose house we'll be staying at.
So? I don't have a problem with him.
Really?
I've been working on that stuff
in my individual therapy.
- Really?
- That's all I talk about.
How come you've never told me
about any of this?
Some things are
between me and the therapist.
- I tell you everything.
- Because you want my approval.
No, it's because I love you.
- The other gentleman, he's your brother?
- Yes. David.
- That's who helped me.
- He left this morning for a friend's funeral.
He sold me a casket.
- Yes, the Cameo Rose.
- It's not good enough.
Mr Fester, the Cameo Rose
is an excellent casket.
No, I want something nicer for Martha.
It doesn't matter how much it costs.
I know when we lose someone
we wanna show how much we loved her,
and we're at a loss as to how to do that
and we spend a lot of money
on something that isn't really necessary.
I don't care.
Don't you understand?
This is the last thing
I'll ever be able to do for my wife.
I was a bad husband.
Affairs and all that shit.
I got cancer, thought I was gonna die,
but I got better.
I got a second chance.
And I realised how much I loved her.
And it's been really good the last few years.
I just want to love her some more.
I owe her...
God, I loved her, I really did.
Of course you did, and she knew that.
She... was everything to me.
I am so sorry.
Nate, do you remember when
I used to make that casserole with the...
I used to do this for your father.
His shoulders would get so full of knots.
It's such a stressful job.
It's OK, baby. It's OK.
- You want the front page?
- No. I can't deal with depressing news.
I don't remember this book being so dark.
These kids in the orphanage
are being tortured.
That's the best part,
where they have to take a bath in iced water.
Isn't that kind of inappropriate for kids?
We're human beings. We all have a sick
craving for that kind of dark fantasy. Even kids.
I've got enough dark reality.
I don't need the fantasy.
Jesus.
Nurse Caterwaul's making Nathaniel and Isabel
cane each other.
Read that part out loud.
You're sick.
If you mean suffering from bipolar disorder
with psychotic episodes, then yes, I am.
This is good, Claire. It's lovely.
The blurriness,
the way the light seems too much.
As if there's a secret fire in her
spilling out for a moment
and you were there to capture it.
Excellent work.
Thanks.
It only turned out this way
because I accidentally dragged the shutter.
I was totally gonna reshoot it.
But he's right, it works.
It's really good.
I wonder how much of art is accidental.
Maybe Magritte,
when he was painting his Listening Room,
was like,
"Damn, I made the apple too big again."
Hello, I'm being clever over here.
- Shit.
- What?
The blade's dull. It's fucking up everything.
- Use another one.
- I got ten mats to cut. I don't have time.
- Why don't you just change the blade?
- I don't want to change the blade.
It's shit! I hate it! I hate everything! I hate it!
- It's shit! It's all fucking shit!
- Good.
A tantrum.
This is an opportunity to learn, people.
Russell, you hate your work
because you secretly hate yourself,
which means
you're still only thinking about yourself.
- Whatever.
- Yeah, whatever.
But I understand the impulse.
I once filled the trunk of my car
with all my latest work
and then lit the car on fire
and let it roll down the streets of Montmartre.
That's interesting, because everything you do
is just so fucking fascinating.
Such vitriol and such rage.
And why aren't you putting this into your work?
Olivier, if you know so much about art and life,
how come you ended up
being such a pathetic poser
who needs people half his age to prop him up
and make him feel good about himself?
He could have at least made the effort
to slam the door.
Young people
have absolutely no commitment today.
Go back to work.
- Hey.
- You OK?
- Yeah.
- Sorry about that. Just a little meltdown.
- I can stay. Go another time.
- No. You're going.
You need a break. You deserve a break.
- You wanna get rid of me.
- No, of course not.
You wanna get to your sister's before dark.
I feel like a terrible mother for thinking this,
and I know I'm gonna miss her,
but I'm kind of looking forward
to a couple of days without Maya.
That's because you're a handful, aren't you?
- Did you make a list for me?
- A list? For what?
I don't know. Usually you make lists.
What time I'm supposed to feed Maya,
what I can and can't feed her.
- You already know all that stuff.
- Yeah. OK.
Don't let your mother bathe her.
She scrubs her like a potato.
I'll bathe her.
OK.
I'm gonna miss you.
- We'll walk you to the car.
- I don't want Maya to see me go.
I just don't.
- Well, goodbye, then.
- I love you.
Be good to Daddy, right?
I love you.
Bye.
- Arthur, are you busy?
- I'm putting away my socks.
But I've become confused
as to which is paired with which.
They all look exactly the same.
That's the dilemma.
Arthur, I really need to talk.
OK.
Quite frankly, I'd like to know how you feel
about the course our relationship is taking.
We've been on quite a serendipitous journey,
haven't we?
And where do you think it's headed?
Surely someplace divine.
Does that mean... you know... intimacy?
I love intimacy. Intimacy is my best friend.
Arthur, I'm so confused.
Do you find me at all attractive?
If you feel I'm too old...
Heavens, no.
You're the perfect age for me, Ruth Fisher.
- I am?
- Absolutely.
So how do you feel about us having,
you know, sex?
It's just that we've been seeing each other
for a while, and not even a kiss.
- Well, not since...
- Yes.
I understand. Well...
I believe that sex can be...
when two become one.
It needn't always be painful,
but it is indeed a very slippery slope.
Arthur, have you ever had sex?
I think I have, in a sense.
Are there any other topics
you'd like to discuss?
No... No.
- Hello?
- It's this way.
- Yeah, I know the way.
- So what's the problem?
We're a couple, and it would be nice if
we could walk together like every other couple,
especially considering I'm about to walk
into a place filled with your every living relative.
So walk faster, then.
- Oh, please.
- Now what?
That's just tacky. No one wants to see that.
This ground is wet.
They should have put down more greens here.
David, it's fine.
Not everyone is such a perfectionist.
I'm not a perfectionist, just professional.
No one's gonna even see these here.
Let's hope these guys remember
to put your great-aunt in her casket face up.
Look, David, here come my folks.
- Try not to nag at me.
- I wasn't...
- Uncle Keith!
- Hey.
Look at you! You gotta stop growing so fast.
- David.
- You look so pretty.
- Thanks. It's my funeral dress.
- Nice.
- So you made it down?
- Yeah, of course.
It's good to see you, baby.
- You too, David.
- Thank you.
Wanna come sit with us?
Yeah, I'd like that.
Excuse me, are you the funeral director?
I'm the organist.
I was wondering if I should begin.
Actually, now would be a perfect time.
Something soft, perhaps Ave Maria.
Prayer card?
Hey. Just in time for lunch.
I know. I could smell curry
all the way from La Cienega.
- I cut up some papaya.
- Thanks.
You seem happy.
- Sorry.
- No, I like it. I like to see you happy.
- I'm glad you're here.
- I told you I was coming home for lunch.
No, here in general, staying with me.
- You just want me to pay half the rent.
- Can I get that in cash?
Fat chance.
- How was work?
- Two cancellations this morning.
- Sorry.
- No, it was great.
I got Raul to give me a massage.
Really? I would have given you a massage.
Yeah, but you didn't train for three years
in Thailand.
- This guy is amazing. You should see him.
- Schedule me.
This looks good.
Look what I got.
Wow. I didn't know there was a video.
Yeah. It's new, I think.
"Join Nathaniel and Isabel
on their fantastic adventures."
I'm not sure I would call
being repeatedly traumatised an adventure.
- We gotta watch it tonight.
- All right.
Thought I might find you here.
You certainly do keep to a schedule.
Hello, Arthur.
- Have you done the whites yet?
- I'm doing them right now.
I have some kerchiefs and undershirts to do.
Some people call them wife-beaters,
which I think is funny.
There's nothing funny about beating your wife.
No, of course not.
I didn't mean to suggest otherwise.
- Perhaps...
- Perhaps what?
Perhaps you'd prefer it
if our laundry didn't mix any more.
Honestly, Arthur,
I don't care what our laundry does.
- Hey.
What are you still doing here?
I'm waiting for you. I figured
you had to come back and get your stuff.
I was walking round campus cursing to myself,
bumming cigarettes off people.
- You don't smoke.
- I know. And I'm feeling kind of nauseous.
What's going on?
What was all that with Olivier about?
I don't know. I think I'm just going crazy.
Why?
Claire, I need to tell you something.
The words every woman longs to hear.
I'm sorry. I'm listening.
I fooled around with Olivier.
What?
- When?
- The day you went to Azusa.
You said nothing happened.
- You lied to me?
- Sorry.
What do you mean, fooled around?
What exactly did you do?
- Claire, I don't think you wanna know.
- Yeah, I do wanna know.
Claire, we had sex.
Russell, I trusted you.
You told me I didn't have to be careful.
You said I could feel safe with you.
I know, and I feel awful.
- So you really are gay?
- No, of course not.
I think I might be bi, but I'm not sure.
I'm just really... I'm fucking confused.
I'm sorry you're fucking confused.
But you sure didn't seem confused
every time we fucked
or every time you said you loved me,
which I was stupid enough to believe.
- I do love you.
- You show it by sucking your professor's dick.
- I already feel like an asshole.
- You are an asshole!
Thanks.
So what goes on between us
is not enough for you?
I don't know.
Have you ever had sex with a man before?
- No. Never.
- But you've obviously thought about it.
I was high, I'm fucking confused...
- I had to tell you.
- Well, thanks.
- You forgive me?
- No.
Fuck you.
- Claire...
- I don't ever want to see you again.
- Don't even call me.
Claire...
- Hey.
- Cute little girl.
- Thank you.
- So's your boy. How old is he?
- 16 months.
- Haven't seen you here before.
- I'm usually stuck at work. My wife takes her.
- How about you?
- Divorced.
No, it's actually really good.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I get Nick two days a week.
Get to take him to the park.
- That's great.
- Hey, Sarah.
Hey, Sarah, hang on.
I can't imagine seeing you
only two days a week.
You wanna talk to your mommy?
- Hello?
- Hey.
I'm at the park with Maya
and I wish you were with us.
Wow, that sounds nice. Hi, sweetie.
She's a little preoccupied watching a squirrel.
- I'm looking at the ocean.
- Yeah? Nice?
It's gorgeous.
- Lise?
- Nate? Nate?
I miss you.
Nate? Nate?
Lise, I'm losing you.
You know what your mom's doing right now?
She's looking out at the ocean.
You know what's more beautiful
than the ocean?
You. Oh, yeah.
My grandfather, my great-grandmother.
I didn't know they were buried here.
My grandfather was in the navy.
He brought the whole family from Chicago
after World War II.
We own all these plots.
- Are you going to be buried here?
- I don't know.
I feel so disconnected from my family.
It'd be nice if you and I
could be buried next to each other.
- Grandma wants to know if you're ready to go.
- Yeah, we'll follow you back to the house.
Taylor, how are you doing here?
Are you happy?
Grandma and Grandpa treat you good?
Yeah. Grandma thinks Grandpa spoils me,
but I like it.
He made me a bunk bed because I asked
him to. Even though I'm just one person.
I get to sleep on the top and the bottom
whenever I want.
- Grandpa isn't mean to you?
- How come you always ask me that?
- Don't you like Grandpa?
- Of course I do. He's my dad.
He was so happy you were coming.
He bought steaks. Said it was your favourite.
I think I should talk to my dad.
Yeah, talk to him. I think that's great.
And one, two, three and five, six, seven.
Cross by me, five, six, seven.
Rico, you're so good.
- Very suave. You look so handsome.
- Thank you.
Dancing makes me feel sexy. Do I look sexy?
You look amazing.
Now we're gonna do an outside turn.
Open break. Back to basic.
I like that. Spin me again.
- No, we have to wait until he says.
- OK, whatever. I'll wait.
All right, everybody,
give yourselves a little applause.
Very good. Short break.
When you come back I'll teach you
how to do the cuddle position.
- Very good.
- Why do I like that?
- I need some water. I'm thirsty. Are you?
- Yeah, a little.
I spilled it.
- This is fun, huh?
- God, this is great. I love dancing.
You're so good at it.
We should go dancing every night.
- The kids might miss us after a while.
- Oh, yeah. The kids.
- You think they're OK? Shall we call them?
- They're fine.
They can come dancing too.
We'll all go dancing.
Shit, these shoes are so tight.
I shouldn't have bought them.
- But they look sexy, right?
- Very sexy.
OK, everybody. Back to your positions.
Come on, line up. Good. Back to basic.
This storm is exceedingly fierce, Nathaniel.
Hang on.
This really sucks.
I know.
It looks like drawings in the mall
by a third-grade class.
- I was really looking forward to this.
- Maybe it'll get better.
Isabel, you've saved me so many times.
Please, Isabel. Please don't die.
- He saves Isabel's life with a fucking tear?
- How did it happen in the book?
Persimmons and pineapples, Isabell
Mouth-to-mouth resuscitation,
which makes sense.
Not some fucking magic tear.
Thanks to you.
- Curses.
- What? What is it?
Nurse Caterwaul.
Children...
I can't even watch this any more.
Billy, chill. It's just a video.
But they ruined it.
They're so fucking sanitised.
There's not any real danger.
And you can't have people say "persimmons
and pineapples" with an American accent.
What a piece of shit!
Hey. It's no big deal.
Yes, it is. It was Dad, you know.
- Dad what?
- Dad who gave us the book.
- Remember?
- Kind of.
He gave it to us for Christmas.
And now Dad's dead.
And our whole childhood sucked.
And Nathaniel and Isabel was the only
good thing we had, and they ruined it.
They didn't ruin it.
We still have it. We'll always have it.
We're so damaged, Bren.
We can go about our lives
and pretend everything's gonna be OK,
but it never will be, ever.
That's not true.
- We're getting better, both of us.
- You are.
- I'm not.
- Come on, you know you are.
I really don't feel like I am.
Those are just feelings.
This is just right now.
And the movie and Dad dying and me
moving in has brought up a lot of stuff for you.
You'll work through it. It'll get better.
- You promise?
- Yeah, I promise.
You gonna help me?
Of course I'll help you. Stupid.
I'm so glad you're here.
I love you so much, Bren.
I love you too.
- Billy!
- What? What?
- Don't ever do that to me.
- It was just a kiss.
No, it wasn't.
I was just being affectionate. I love you.
- I gotta go.
- What? Brenda, wait. What?
No. OK, let's watch another video. Come on.
We'll watch a good one this time. Brenda!
- Sorry.
- You OK? Are you tired?
Maybe.
- You wanna rest?
- No.
Yes... and no.
Are you OK?
My heart's beating so fast.
- I'm so dizzy.
- Whoa.
- Baby, what's wrong?
- I need some air.
- I'm gonna take you to the hospital.
- No. In my purse. My pill thing.
- Jesus.
- The Zanex.
- Which one's the Zanex?
- The blue one.
Which blue one?
Just hold my hand, OK? Just hold on to me.
OK.
My mother says you won't leave.
I had to see you. It's driving me crazy
thinking you're mad at me.
I'm supposed to make you feel better?
I don't want this to end. I need this.
I need you.
I'm sorry, I just can't be with somebody
who's this confused.
I know I'm confused, but the one thing
I'm completely sure of is that I love you.
And I believe you.
But I have been through this before.
I'm not some nurse
who's here to take care of the misfits.
I'm sorry, but whatever it is you're going
through, you'll have to figure it out alone.
We should be together.
We're both crazy, we're both fucked-up artists.
I mean, we have to be together.
I don't think so.
- I'm gonna change your mind, I swear.
- Please just leave me alone.
I would cut out my heart and give it to you
in a box if it would change anything.
Well, it would, cos you'd be dead, OK?
Goodbye.
Claire?
- Did you get Taylor off to bed?
- Yeah. I can't believe how grown-up she is.
She politely informed us
that she's too old to play with Barbies.
And insisted she read us a bedtime story.
- She's smart. Doing well in school.
- Good.
She misses her momma,
but we deal with that the best we can.
She seems happy. I'm glad this is working out.
Of course it's working out.
- Lucille, can I help you in the kitchen?
- Sure, David. Thanks.
Dad, I need to talk to you about something.
Look, I...
I know things haven't always been so smooth
between you and me.
I've been working on some things in therapy.
I've come to realise that I was traumatised
by the way you punished me and Carla.
That was abusive. That was abuse.
- Abuse?
- I know you did the best you could.
You were probably repeating what happened
to you, but it did a number on me and Carla.
I'm to blame
for your sister's drug problems?
No, I wanna acknowledge the truth
about what happened so I can forgive you.
- You wanna forgive me?
- Yeah.
So we can have a real relationship
while we still have time.
What are you talking about? I disciplined
my children when they deserved it.
I gave you a home. I gave you food to eat.
I taught you how to be a man.
You wanna forgive me?
Get on your knees and thank me and maybe
I'll forgive you for being a goddamn faggot.
- I'm sorry. I thought...
- I said I wanna hear you thank me.
Who do you think you pushing, boy?
- Your son was only trying to reach out to you.
- Who the fuck are you again?
- I'm the man your son is in love with.
- It makes me sick to my stomach.
How the fuck can you act so goddamn superior
when everyone knows you beat your kids,
- Cheated on your wife?
- I did not. How dare you?
- Keith, you need to tell him.
- This isn't the place for you to say that.
- It's not my place?
- No, this is my family. Stay out of it.
Then I can't be here.
David...
Should have knocked his teeth out
for what he said to me.
You're pathetic.
It's a bit different
than the music Mommy plays, isn't it?
I couldn't stand hearing that one more time.
I'd tear my head off.
It's open. Come on up.
The pizza man.
Ready for your first taste of pepperoni?
Brenda, hey.
I'm sorry. I didn't know where else to go
and didn't have your number.
- No, that's fine. Come on in.
- Sure I'm not interrupting anything?
No. Lisa's gone. I'm just introducing Maya
to some music that doesn't suck.
- What's wrong?
- Billy.
Let me put Maya down in her playpen.
Ever since your father died,
I've just flitted from man to man.
I am so embarrassed.
I mean, look, you got married
when you were 19. That's how old I am.
You never even got to have your sexual 20s,
so why shouldn't you do it now?
You don't have to worry about us any more.
No.
Did you know I got pregnant
the first time I ever had sex?
My God.
- With Dad?
- Of course.
I thought you were gonna tell me I had
some love child half-brother somewhere,
which I don't think I could handle right now.
No, it was Nate.
Nathaniel and I had to get married right away.
Both our families were mortified.
It changed my life for ever.
Do you ever wonder how your life
would be different if that hadn't happened?
I used to. Not any more.
- Were you and Dad in love with each other?
- Yes.
Very much so at first.
Despite how we grew apart,
your father was the great love of my life.
At least you had that.
I'm beginning to think I never will.
You will. Everyone does. But chances are
it won't be anything like you expect.
I miss Dad, you know.
I feel like... I hate how I just took him
for granted my whole life
and now he's gone and it's too late for me
to ever really know him,
you know, like as an adult.
I miss him too.
There will never be another man
who will love me when I'm young and pretty
and always have that picture of me
somewhere in his heart.
Mom, you're still pretty. God, you're beautiful.
Why do you think all these men
are always hitting on you?
You're so sweet. But look at the men!
I'm sitting here crying over Arthur.
- What should I do about him?
- Run.
I feel sorry for him, though. He's so naive.
Yeah. I feel sorry for Russell too.
I mean, I hate him,
but I feel sorry for him.
Mom, why is it I attract
every screwed-up guy in the state?
Because they can see
what a kind soul you have.
That you're caring and sensitive.
It's the truth, Claire. You're an angel.
But the real question is, why do you like them?
It's like I'll fall for any guy
who shows any interest in me.
I guess we all wanna be loved.
It's hard to say no to that,
no matter who it's coming from.
Right from the beginning there was this voice
saying, "Don't move in with Billy."
What do I do? I move in with Billy.
So self-destructive.
Maybe you wanted to believe
the world is a better place than it really is.
- So I'm an idiot?
- No. Just a very positive person.
That doesn't sound like me.
It's scary to hope things will turn out good
because you risk being disappointed.
- Wow. You've really thought about this.
- No, I'm talking out of my ass.
I have no clue whatsoever.
Look, all I know is you're a good person
who deserves to be happy.
So are you, you know.
Well, I should go.
- Sure you're gonna be OK?
- Yeah.
You've got my number?
Thank you.
What are friends for?
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- This isn't right.
- I'm gonna go.
I can't believe I just did that. You're married.
- Yes, I'm married.
- I'm sorry. I'm worse than Billy.
No, I was right there too.
I'm so fucking predictable.
I'm gonna leave now.
- You have a place to go?
- Yeah, I'll be fine.
Hey, sailor.
- Patrick, I can't believe you're here.
- I got your message.
You sounded miserable.
Yeah.
I'll drive you home. You can tell me all about it.
I still can't believe you're here.
I can't sleep at night anyway.
Hey, Barb, it's Nate. Is Lisa there?
I don't know. She could be in traffic.
I'll try her on her cell.
Listen, if you talk to her first,
make sure she calls me.
Right. Bye.
Hey, Lise. You taking the scenic route up?
Anyway, Maya's sleeping. I just wanted
to hear your voice, know you're OK.
I love you.
Call me when you get this.
Hey, sweetie. Let's get you ready for bed.
- Come on. Up you go.
- No, leave me here.
I'm too tired to move.
Hello?
Hey, Lise. I was hoping to reach you.
It's late and I'm starting to worry.
I love you. Just... call me.
Call me. I love you.