Sous-titres par
la Fisher Team
Transcript:
Raceman
Synchronisation :
EZ, Occeane
Traduction :
Sylvain, Bibipupuce, Spooky, Paqui
Relecture et corrections finales :
Guzo
http://www.sixfeetunder-france.com
http://www.forom.com
Saison 5 Episode 6
"The Rainbow of her reasons"
Boy, the air's thinner up
here than I would've thought.
Come on, fiona, you can do it !
I can't wait to show you
the view from the top !
You know, you were right.
It's good that I got out.
I think was getting a
little depressed inside.
Just me and the fumes from my kiln
And that morose N.P.R.
Here.
Take this. Come on !
All right.
Just through here you can
see all the way to the ocean.
- Be careful up ahead.
- What ?
We're moments from the top,
mere moments.
I didn't think I was gonna-
Make it.
Fiona ?
- This top doesn't fit.
It's the right top, it's the wrong
container. Put the broccoli in a ziploc.
They're didn't eat the
broccoli from yesterday.
- Where's the carrots ?
- Get off of me !
What is ?
What are you doing ?
Jesus.
All right, it's time to
go. Put your jacket on.
I'm not putting on
that busted old jacket.
- Yes, you are. We just got it !
- No, I'm not !
- I'm getting my other one.
- You're not the boss here, OK ?
- You want that one, go get it !
- I don't know where it is !
- Where did you put it ?
- I didn't put it anywhere !
- It's your jacket !
- I'll find the other jacket.
Just go brush your teeth, guys.
It's like he wants me to lose my temper.
No kid wants that. Just give him time.
You've been saying that for two weeks.
You have to remember
where he comes from,
What the social worker
said about his mother.
My sister's a drug addict.
Taylor never acted like this !
- Taylor's a girl.
- So ?
So she isn't hardwired to be
aggressive and territorial.
That's the reason she
doesn't have the same problem
With your father that you do.
So now everything that happened
between me and my father is my fault ?
No, I'm-
Is your brother ready ?
He wants to know where you put his hat.
I'll be in the car.
Why do you need mr. Sibley's name ?
No, Mr. Sibley is right here.
What are the last four
digits of your social ?
4281.
Correct.
I'll hold.
- Are you looking for something ?
- Yeah, the pots and pans.
Oh, I must have forgotten them.
We can just buy new ones.
I can go down to crate
& barrel right now.
We have practically a
brand-New set back at the house.
Well, I don't want to raid their supply.
But you loved that calphalon.
You raved about it when we got it.
That was because it was my first
experience with anodized aluminum.
We don't need those, we'll buy new ones.
It's an incredible waste of money.
I'm here.
Good.
And you do the gas as well ? Splendid.
No, thank you.
Did you talk to dean hikolos
about going back to work ?
No, I... I don't want to.
I'm not ready.
It'll be the summer session if at all.
I just thought you were
doing so much better.
Oh, I am.
And I wanna keep doing better,
Without all the stress and
strain of teaching school.
Will you look at that ?
Remember when we bought this ?
That's when you asked me to marry you.
Okay, I'll go get our pots and pans.
I'll be back before you know it.
I'll be waiting.
Okay, you did really well on
your typing test. Got a 95.
Thanks.
Don't worry, no one
ever has gotten 100.
One person did, but i
think she was psychic.
- Okay, we have one downtown- -
Oh, I should probably tell you,
I have applied for this
grant for emerging artists,
And if I get it which could be this month,
Or even this week, I'd have to
stop working, like, immediately.
Yeah well, "temp" is
short for temporary.
Okay, here we are.
"Quality control auditing
clerk, legal department,
Braeden chemical. Employee
verifies accuracy of figures,
Business transactions
recorded by other workers,
As well as support the support
staff in general tasks."
- Sound good ?
- Okay.
Okay, let me call over there and
see if they've found anyone yet.
It's a very conservative company.
You do have corporate attire, right ?
Like a business suit ?
Or a nice blouse, a skirt, some hose.
I feel so lucky.
I am just so lucky to have been
with her in her final moments.
What a gift.
She was so alive.
And she was happy happy happy,
And excited to see the view.
You've never seen such a perfect
morning in topanga canyon.
Were either of you out this morning ?
No.
I can't believe Fiona's gone.
- You knew her too, huh ?
- Yeah, I did.
It's like the second
person you've known.
I know.
This just must be the
time when everyone's dying.
Nate, it was her time.
I was compelled to bring her.
I was driving through the
canyon to go on my hike
And my car just pulled
over into her driveway.
It's like something said,
"bring Fiona with you."
The spirit had to have her.
The spirit...
Works in mysterious ways.
Coroner's office.
She must be ready to go.
- You okay ?
- Yeah.
- We're gonna make it beautiful, right ?
- Yep.
Yay !
I love these flowers.
Ooh, they smell good. Smell them.
If y're upset, tell him.
If he loves you he should
be able to hear that.
I don't want to freak
him out unnecessarily.
I thought billy was back
on his medication.
Ah, that's what he says.
"I'm back on my meds"
like that's all that matters.
"Is he on or is he off ?"
He's completely oblivious to the
fact that we're all just exhausted.
They should call it
"bipolar asshole disorder."
Just tell him. Okay ? You need a break.
Yeah, that scares me too.
I feel like I have to keep him close
So that if he falls off
the edge someone will know.
People are starting
to notice I'm pregnant.
Brenda, you look beautiful.
- Okay, like a glowing mommy.
- Really.
Look, you've got one at
home and one in there,
You know, put your energy
where it deserves to be.
- Billy can take care of himself.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I know.
Okay.
You look hot.
I ought to look fucking hot. I've
been starving myself like a refugee.
Oh, you're funny.
I could've done that joke better.
I gotta to go to the airport
soon and pick up the babysitter.
Au pair.
Okay, that word is so "bougie." Please.
Okay, nanny, whatever.
This is l.A. Everybody
has live-In help.
I don't know.
Are you mad
I mean, that I can't help you
as much anymore ?
- Tell me.
- Don't.
Everything you ever
wanted is coming true.
It's just a stupid sitcom.
I'm sure it will get canceled.
I just... I don't want it to be weird
for you,
You know, having a stranger in the
house, especially from saskatchewan.
- Where the hell is saskatchewan ?
- Near calgary, I think.
To tell you the truth-
She can have horns and weigh
300 lbs. For all I care.
As long as she brings in the water bottles,
can be here when the cable guy comes
And starts putting away the
groceries that are melting
While I'm getting the rest out of
the car. I just need another adult.
Sarah ?
Oh, Ruthy, you never gonna
believe what happened.
Fiona's dead.
- Fiona ?
- Climbing.
I know you hated her
for what she did to Nate.
But we've lost her, Ruthy.
She's gone.
- I know, it's horrendous.
- Jesus, I can't imagine.
- There was nothing she could do ?
- No, nothing.
Fell hundreds of feet right
down to the bottom of the ravine,
And was dead when they pulled
her out. I'm just sick about it.
Fiona was a very close
friend of mine. Very close.
You sure you don't need
me to come over there ?
I think sarah's in shock.
It's not a pretty scene down here...
Only appropriate for family...
Of origin.
People, I need people. Who can we call ?
What did she say ?
She's just jabbering.
She's incoherent.
- Keep me posted.
- Okay. Bye.
Get me my phone book.
It's in my satchel.
I need to circle the wagons.
Do I need to come down there ?
Okay okay, I'll stop by the office
when I come to pick the boys up.
Bye.
Durrell pulled a fire alarm.
Now I have to make an
appointment with the principal.
I can't tell keith.
He's just looking for more proof
these kids are too messed up for us.
- The foster's just temporary, right ?
- No, not really.
They try to get them in the right
place, have it lead to actual adoption.
- That's the ideal.
- You want to keep them ?
I do.
Anthony's so cute I'd
keep him in a heartbeat.
Durrell, on the other hand, is a mess.
But what can you expect ? These
kids come from a broken home.
Their dad basically abandoned them.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Hey, did I tell you
i found my own place ?
A two bedroom. I'm waiting to hear.
Then my boys can stay over.
I can't wait to wake up with
them again. That's what I miss.
Pajamas, and messy hair
and their eyes all sleepy.
Well, I hope you get the place,
If that's what you want.
What I want...
Is to be back home.
But I have to take in the reality
That it's not going to happen.
I'm sorry about the mess.
I was rushing around this morning.
I didn't get a chance to pick up.
You certainly don't have to clean
for me. That's what I'm here for.
I'm so excited. I love california.
- I practically barfed on the plane.
- Well, don't do that.
- Can she come in my room ?
- Yeah, hold on, julio.
Uh, so I wrote up a list.
Some of it is common sense, like do
the dishes when they start piling up.
And if you could be here
tomorrow between 10:00 and 2:00,
The cable guy's coming
'cause our satellite's out.
Oh, do you have those giant
water bottles in canada ?
- Yeah.
- They're way too heavy for me.
So if you ever see that it's
empty, go ahead and bring one in.
Oh, okay.
Would it be okay if i got
a little settled in first ?
Oh my god. Of course.
I'm sorry. I'm...
- Just really happy you're here.
- Help is on the way.
Oh, here's the e-Mail that's
from fiona's artist week group.
Mm, I'll call them from my house.
Should we regroup in the morning ?
Sure. I'm going to stay here tonight.
George and I are in transition mode.
You sounded like you were
together wh you were on the phone.
You threw the bum out because he
couldn't get his shit together ?
No, I made a plan with my
new friends at knitting.
First, get set him up in his own place,
Sort of pad the landing,
as it were, and then-
Parachute out of there ?
When the time is right.
Cut to you 30 years from
now changing his diapers
And downing a gallon
of merlot every day.
Oh, claire, your aunt sarah's
dear friend fiona was killed today.
- Someone killed her ?
- No.
She fell of a cliff in topanga canyon.
Oh my god. I'm so sorry.
You met her at the
full moon celebration-
Fiona Kleinschmidt, the ceramicist.
Yeah, she wrote me a
recommendation for art school.
And she knew dad... and Nate ?
Uh, yes, that's the one.
So who gets to speak at the service
About fiona's penchant for
ushering young boys into manhood ?
Bettina, that was once.
Hey, that's the one thing
I really admired her for.
The old table's back.
Isn't it wonderful ? The other table
just didn't make any sense in here.
George has it. He moved out,
but I don't want to discuss it.
Your aunt sarah needs our help now.
How are you, claire ?
Well, I had to start temping.
But only until I hear from this emerging
artists' grant that I applied for.
But what really sucks is I had to waste
my money on these ridiculous clothes.
Oh my god.
"Yet these are all still chess moves.
Even being mad at you
today is still a chess move.
What I hate the most is
the game being played."
Okay, let me get her response.
Okay, Maya is down.
Okay, this is what she wrote back.
"Sadly, I never learned to play chess,
So be assured I'm not making a move."
Now why would she put "sadly" if
she didn't feel at least some...
Unconscious regret for
the way things ended ?
There is no way two people
could have gone through
What we went through together
and just let it- Unless-
Wait, let me read you the
transcripts from our i.M.S
No !
Well, nate, have you asked
her what she's thinking ?
Clearly she's moved on.
To be honest, the only
reason I'm dealing with you
Is because you're here and you're
not out here stalking my sister.
Nate ! Stop.
- Sorry.
- No, I'm sorry.
I'm on my medication.
It's just gonna take awhile.
The end of a relationship
is hard for anyone.
- I remember when you two
- Billy, please don't !
I'm sorry.
I'll just
Did you guys say you had
that scorsese thing tivo'd ?
I'll just eat some ice cream.
Then I'll watch it and then head out.
And I won't call her.
I killed her.
I killed my best friend.
- Honey, you didn't kill her.
- Of course you didn't.
You always tell me everything
happens for a reason.
Oh, fuck off !
Fuck that one to the ground !
"Everything happens for
a reason." What a crock !
You say there's a reason
grandma lost her legs,
And there's a reason there's a war.
And tsunamis ?
And there's a reason
george-Fucking-Bush got reelected !
Shit goes wrong because there's
evil in the world, like me !
- I'm evil.
- Sarah, no !
- Let her go.
- It was my idea to go get her
To go on the walk.
She didn't want to.
I... I dragged her.
She turned me down twice. I begged her.
- Twice ?
- Who am I, the antichrist ?
Some one should...
Just lock me up and keep me in a cage.
Someone should dig a
hole and throw me in it,
Not let me out !
Oh my god !
It's a playstation 2 !
- Cool.
- With turismo 4 !
- Can we- Can we hook it up ?
- Of course !
But we have to leave
for school in 10 minutes !
- All right !
- Okay !
What ? It's just a playstation.
All kids have them.
I just think buying this
without any rhyme or reason
Is like saying they deserve a
prize, when clearly they don't.
It's not a prize. It's just
something fun to have a good time.
Yeah, good times.
That's your answer to
everything, miss pollyanna.
- It's to give them an activity.
- It's going to rot their brains.
Who knows ?
I don't.
I don't either. I'm just
trying to make everyone happy.
Maybe that's your problem. You're always
trying to make everybody so damned happy.
- What you should be doing...
- Oh god, just shut the fuck up.
Are we having fun yet ?
Here's beverly's birthday card to sign.
- Oh, I haven't met beverly.
- Yeah.
She won't even read it. Last year i
signed it "hitler," she never said a word.
- Hey, johnny, have you met claire yet ?
- Yeah, baby.
- Oh, hi.
- "Wazzup" ?
Oh, just trying to sign this card.
He wasn't really asking. He has
tourette's, you have to say it back to him.
Oh. What's up ?
Beverly's coming. Give me back the card.
Hurry up !
You can sign it later.
So, I don't think I'll
get home for a few days.
Do you have enough to eat or
should I call koo koo roo for you ?
Okay. I'll check in soon.
Was I frothing like an idiot last night ?
Something in red wine
doesn't agree with me.
I don't even remember what I said.
- You were blaming yourself.
- I don't know why I do that.
It's so narcissistic, you know.
I am the asshole at the
center of the universe,
Forgetting how vast the universe is,
And how nothing...
Is in our control.
An idea both terrifying and beautiful
As spirit itself.
Hooty-Hoo, the gang's all here.
Aw, pookie, I'm so sorry.
You know fiona's dear friends.
- Lakshmi.
- Hi.
And this is susie bright,
feminist sex writer.
- Hi.
- You don't have to introduce me that way.
Oh, this is my sister ruth.
- Hi.
- I'll help you with those.
- Hey.
- Here.
- Hi.
Nate, come meet susie bright.
- Hello.
- Hi.
She's a sex writer.
Wow ! It's nice to meet you.
Bettina will be here soon.
She's at costco buying
hummus by the metric ton.
Tell the whole story.
Lakshmi heard fiona
Didn't even want to go on the
hike. Someone pushed her into it ?
Some woman named
susie bright. Heard of her ?
Yeah, feminist sex writer.
I've read a bunch of
her stuff. I love her.
Yeah, my aunt sarah's a friend of hers.
So there's a bunch of women
over here just whooping it up.
One of those our-Dead-Friend-
Would-Have-Wanted-Us- To-Be-Happy-
So-Let's-Make- A- Funeral-An-Excuse
for-A-Big-Sloppy-Party deals.
Would they mind if I joined them ?
You really want to meet ms. Bright, huh ?
Yeah, and get away from mr.
Chenowith who's here again.
All right. I'll see you soon then. Bye.
- Whoa.
- Yep.
First woman you ever slept with.
For real ?
For real.
I bet you never thought
you'd see her naked again.
Yeah.
Hey, how has she held up ?
What's the difference
on her 20 years later ?
In case you haven't noticed
she's all bruised and busted up,
You fucking idiot !
Hey, claire, did you come across
those requisition printouts ?
May I hug you ?
Okay.
Oh, claire.
Listen, I know this place
can be really intimidating.
18 years ago it was
my after-School job,
And I just fell in love with the place.
The monday after i
graduated from college
I came back and i
said, "put me to work."
It really is very special.
What's the matter, claire ? It
is kirsten, is she being a butt ?
Oh no, it's not that. It's just...
It's just these pantyhose.
Oh, do you have a run ? 'Cause
i have a little clear polish
- You can put on
- No no, it's not that !
It's they're like squeezing against
my torso and I can't even breathe !
I mean, none of this work
would even seem that hard
If I didn't feel like I was sitting here
In some kind of torture chamber all day.
Maybe you should try a different
brand. Mine energize me.
No, it's not the brand.
They're all the same.
- It's
- I mean...
I don't understand how having your legs
Sheathed in this smooth
plastic barbie leg,
Like, encased in a sausage casing
Would help you do your job better.
Doesn't seem sexist that it's
a regulation only for women ?
Men have to wear ties.
Right, but they don't suffate you.
And it's not on their penis.
I'm gonna go wash out some mugs.
* she's a brick, ba ba ba na *
* house, ba ba ba na *
* she's a mighty, mighty *
I'm gonna put the music underneath,
but I have to get the beat.
I'm okay. So zoom in, zoom in.
Are you zooming ? *
lettin' all hang out *
- * oh, she's a brick, a
ba ba na, house- * - Hey !
- Hi.
- Are you guys making a movie ?
We were playing online, and i
found the application to "survivor."
It said you had to make an audition
tape, so julio got the camera.
That's fun.
I have got the whole foreign thing
going for me,
Being from canada and all.
Oh, but we can do it later.
Julio, go get what we made.
So sit down, sit down.
- Put your feet up.
- Oh. Really ?
Yeah, really.
Mommy's worked so hard. That
is so nice of you, julio.
Thank you. Thank you, donna.
You didn't have to do this.
Oh, I love helping people.
And I know you do everything by
yourself. My mom was a single mom.
It's not only twice as hard without
a man, it's exponentially harder.
Was he good to you.
Did he take care of you ?
Yes, he was good to me.
And then he was really bad to me.
Durrell broke it.
I did not ! It wouldn't let me get
to level two so I had to fix it.
- You didn't have to open it.
- Crybaby crybaby.
- What the hell did you do, durrell ?
- It broke !
Okay, I broke it !
Why did you have to buy us a present
that you knew was gonna break ?
You opened the machine up. I'd have
gotten it fixed had you only waited.
- Why does everything always have to get ruined ?
- Everything was already ruined
From the time we had to move
into this stupid gay house !
- Durrell, you're going to your room !
- Get off of me !
Leave him alone. I hate you !
- Get off me !
- Leave him alone !
Stop it, you're
gonna break his arm !
- Keith !
- Stop ! You're hurting him !
I said, get off of me !
What the hell is going on ?
Durrell's getting a time-Out !
- You're locking them in a room ?
These kids will walk all
over you if you let them.
- I'll beat you, man !
- More violence, that's what you want to show them ?
Discipline and violence
are not the same thing.
- I'll kill you, you faggot !
- Let us out of here, you faggot !
This is a nightmare.
Keith, look at yourself !
U're completely insane right now.
Let go of the
door or I'll tell D.C.F.S. !
You think anybody over
there give a shit about you ?
You did that to yourselves !
* adrift on the water *
* could it be actually *
* wearing these clothes *
* I've never been *
* this fucking uncomfortable *
* never again *
* to wear pantyhose... *
* 'cause you ride up my thighs *
* you're tight on my ass *
* you climb up my crotch *
* you ruin my day *
* and fill my soul *
* you fill my soul with hate *
* it can't be right *
* when they feel so tight... *
* 'cause you and you and you *
- * all of you... *
- Claire ?
* ride up my thighs. *
Claire ?
Is my music too loud ? Do
you need me to turn it down ?
Oh, yeah, maybe a little. Thanks.
Coming !
- Hi, daddy.
- Sweetheart.
Oh, boy.
- Here. Happy housewarming.
- Ooh, beautiful.
Tea's ready !
Where does ruth keep her hand lotion ?
I don't know.
It's been so dry out this week,
And the only stuff in
the bathroom's yours.
Maybe she took it with her.
- Took it where ?
- Earl grey or green ?
- When did you move in ?
- Two days ago.
Stop being so nosy. Earl grey or green ?
Daddy, I'm not, I just-
Green.
So I guess...
You guys are just taking
your time unpacking ?
Look, I rely on ruth to
take care of you, daddy.
I just want to make
sure you have everything.
We're fine.
The only reason I'm alone is that ruth's
sister was involved in a fatal accident.
Oh, you're kidding.
Evidently, she's being blamed for it.
And ruth, caretaker that
she is, is by her side.
Apparently she's quite distraught.
I think they've outlived
their usefulness.
- Men are obsolete.
- It's true.
I feel more of a connection to my
women friends than any of my husbands.
I've wanted to have an
all-Women weekend on my land.
Nice idea.
Let's make it an all-Woman year !
All women forever ! A land of no men !
Men can visit, but only for a weekend.
Just to satisfy our needs.
But they have to bring money.
I've got the land, ladies. There's
20 acres up there I don't use at all.
We'll buy yurts off the internet.
Save me a yurt.
Brenda, we could midwife
your baby for you.
You can deliver her in a horse trough.
And we camp while you're in labor. Mmm.
I know how to grow vegetables !
We'll only eat what I can grow or kill.
We can start this weekend. But
we must enforce the no-Men part !
- No men !
I'm just here to pick up my kid.
That's it ! We'll use
the men for child care,
Like they've done to us
for a gazillion years.
I'm moving in to an all-Girl
commune. Don't worry,
I'll sneak you in when they're asleep.
- Okay. Up up up.
- Yeah, do you mind if I stay ?
- This is kind of cool.
- Sure. No problem.
Bye-Bye !
- Bye !
- Bye.
Bye.
- Bye, beautiful.
- Have fun, everybody.
Okay, who's got weed ?
Not me.
Mine's all gone.
I think I know where I've got some.
I'm done.
- With your flossing or ?
- With the kids.
Keith, it's not like
they're slippers you can
Return to neiman marcus
because they don't fit.
That's the whole point of foster-
So you can see whether or not it works.
That's what the social worker said.
And this is definitely not working.
- We're just getting started.
- No.
It's been two weeks. That's
more than enough time to know.
We should stop before they bond to us.
But I've already bonded to them.
What you've bonded to is the
idea of becoming your mother-
Just running around
here blind to everything.
"Oh, everything's gonna be okay."
You turn into your father,
you solve everything with a beating.
- I haven't touched those kids !
- You were close.
Exactly. That's why when the
social worker comes tomorrow
I'll be explaining to her
that this is a bad match.
You should pack their
things in the morning.
How can you just abandon them
When their little lives have already
been filled with so much trauma ?
Good, so now you abandon me ?
That solves everything.
- Hello ?
- Hey, it's maggie.
Hey.
I was just putting maya to sleep.
Have you seen your mother ?
Um, why do you ask ?
Well, I was just over at my
dad's, and she wasn't there.
And then I tried to reach her
at the house and nobody answered.
Huh. Well, i, um...
Nate, we don't know
each other very well,
But do something for me, would you ?
And I'll make the same promise to you.
Never lie to me.
Okay ?
Okay.
She's at the house.
Um, it's just a bunch of women.
They're having a little party.
But she's fine.
If there's a problem with your
dad, she didn't tell me about it.
Okay.
And, uh...
You know, brenda's over there too.
It's just me and maya here.
Um, are you okay ?
I'm fine.
I'll see you soon I hope. Bye.
Oh, hello, honey.
Take off your business
clothes and come join us.
Sarah made dinner, and
bettina's in rare form.
And dominique brought susie bright.
Do you know who she is ?
No.
Oh, the women thought some marijuana
might ease the pain of the loss.
I guess you found it.
This seems very brown.
Is it the same strength as the
green stuff with the pungent aroma ?
Do you guys have papers ?
Uh, they were actually
hoping for a bong.
You know you have to
put water in that, right ?
Bettina knows.
Oh, honey.
What ?
I don't hate you.
I don't hate you either, mom.
You're just so much like me.
And I see you doing these things
and I feel like I'm seeing myself.
Well, I'm not that much like you.
If you give up your
dreams and it's my fault,
I'll never forgive myself.
No, you were right.
I mean, I have to be
able to support myself.
And soon as this grant
comes through I will.
I mean, this job is just for now.
Promise me...
Promise me you'll be who you wanna be.
Oh, I love you, sweetheart.
I love you too, mom.
You look so corporate.
You look so not corporate.
Won't you come down and join us ?
I can't. As soon as i
get this hot-Dog suit off
I am gonna take a bath and be naked.
If I put anything else on
with a waistband I'm gonna cry.
I'll keep my fingers crossed anyway.
Lederhosen are trousers.
But german for song is lieder.
Lieder. Yes, correct.
Hey.
Is there something you wanted ?
Maybe it's true that it
wasn't claire that I lod so much-
But I loved how it felt to see
the world with another person...
To be the two of us.
I felt like she was my first real love.
I know she's just a kid,
But we were kids together.
My first love just died.
Seriously ?
Yeah. I was 15 when I met her.
She was 32.
- Whoa.
- Yeah, oh, yeah.
Everyone afterwards got
all excited, you know-
"What did she do to you ?"
Everybody always thought
she did something to me.
You know, up until fiona
I had just been fooling
around with girls my own age-
Dark-Room-Trying-To-Get-
My-Hand-Down-Some-Girl's-Pants bullshit.
Fiona let me see all of her.
And I just loved her.
And that whole year
I was seeing other girls, but I'm just..
You know, I wrote her letters.
Some of them rhymed.
Now I know she probably laughed
when she read those letters.
I doubt she laughed.
Well, you know, love isn't something
you feel, it's something you do.
If the person you're with
doesn't want it, you know,
Do yourself a favor and
save it for someone who does.
Are you sure it's okay
for us to be down here, fisher ?
Of course I'm sure.
We've all been conditioned
not to touch the dead.
- But it's okay.
- Oh, fiona.
You look good, babe.
I love you.
I forgive you, fiona,
for deflowering my boy.
Oh, she's the one.
He was only 15.
I know, nate told me.
It's okay.
He was okay.
Oh, thank you.
* calling all angels *
* cling all angels *
* walk me through this one *
* don't leave me alone *
* calling all angels *
* we're trying, we're hoping *
* we're hurting, we're loving *
* we're crying, we're calling *
* we're not sure how *
* calling all angels *
* walk me through this one *
* don't leave me alone *
* calling all angels *
* we're trying, we're hurting *
* but we're not sure why *
- * calling all angels *
- * walk me through this one *
* don't leave me alone *
* calling all angels *
* calling all angels. *
Oh, thank god, the
california arts commission.
- Yes !
- You look nice.
You must be joking.
It's sexy, like a business lady.
What's the matter, honey ?
I just got rejected for my grant.
Those dicks. Let me see that.
Oh, well, there will be another one.
Shit !
Maybe you're not an artist.
Why would you say that ?
Did it hurt your
feelings when I said it ?
Well, yeah.
Maybe I'm right.
Maybe if you were an artist, you'd
have laughed when I said that.
Like, if you told me I was purple
I would laugh because
i know I'm not purple.
But when I said you weren't
an artist, you felt bad
Maybe because there's
a grain of truth in it.
You're the one who took me by my
shoulders and looked me in my eyes
And told me that I was an artist.
Maybe you were.
Maybe are. Maybe you
aren't. I don't know.
No one else can tell anyone what to do,
Least of all me.
That's the good news.
Donna, are you-
Hello. How do you do ?
- Who are you ?
- That's Mr. Clarington.
Who is he ?
Oh, he's homeless. I was
coming out of the trader joe's
And he was hungry so I was just
going to make him some pancakes.
I know it's not a great meal, but-
- Where are the boys ?
- They're at school.
Donna...
You cannot bring strange
people home. This isn't canada !
I wasn't trying to cause any trouble.
But thank you both kindly
for your hospitality.
- Never ever come back here !
- Oh my god, that's so mean.
- I'm so sorry, mr. Clarington.
- You're fired, donna.
I'm calling the agency and I'm telling
them you're out of your fucking mind !
I needed someone to help me,
Not shoot videos of themselves dancing
And invite the homeless
in for pancake breakfast.
Go pack your stuff. I
need you to leave now.
I have nowhere to go.
I don't care. Find somewhere to go !
Fine.
If I get something from "survivor,"
can you forward it to me ?
Yes.
Okay.
- Punk.
- Wait one second before you open that !
- Guys.
- The restraining order went out on friday.
- You're weaker.
- You're weakest !
I'm trained in handling
psychotic breaks.
Boys, we have company !
Well, it sounds like a shitstorm,
But I don't have a
clue how I can help you.
- Ow ! I hate you.
- Okay, later. Bye.
Sorry. Everything's falling apart.
Must be the moon.
Yeah, exactly, we have
the same situation here.
The boys are not doing well.
Not at all.
I... Go ahead, I will let it ring.
- Tell me how it's been.
- We have a real problem here.
Or not ! We're not sure exactly.
What we need is your input,
Your feedback. Perhaps the
best way to handle this-
I am so sorry. I do have to take this.
- Girl !
- No. I'm almost out of here.
Hold on one second. Okay...
That'll be it then ?
Listen, I don't think things
are working out for the kids.
I mean, I'm not sure
we're the right match.
You have no idea the hell i
have pulled children out of.
I mean, houses filled to the
brim with garbage, cat feces.
You are doing fine in my book.
I have never seen
these boys doing better.
- They're flourishing.
- "Flourishing" ?
Good. Yes, that's what
I thought. Thank you.
- We're thrilled to have them here.
- Okay. Great. Yeah-
Listen, could you just stay
five minutes ?
- No ! Wait. She needs to go.
- I've gotta go.
Yeah, I'm on my way.
Well, I don't know with traffic...
I can't believe you just did that.
You know, david, just pretending
that something is working
- Doesn't mean it's actually working.
Don't worry, guys.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Have you heard
from personnel yet ?
I started out as a temptoo.
If you have half a brain they'll
offer you something permanent.
Did you get my present ?
Oh, the e-Card with the
dancing puppies ? Yes.
It was very cute. Thank you.
Yeah, baby.
No, I meant my old bathroom pass.
If personnel calls, which
i heard could happen,
They'll give you your own, but in the
meantime you can use my old my one.
I'm telling operations.
Really, you can have it, claire.
Thank you.
You're gonna love it here,
claire. You really are.
Hello ?
Yeah.
Yeah yeah, I can
definitely pick up the kids.
Oh, okay. Okay. Good good.
See you then. Bye-Bye.
I'm gonna take fiona to the crematorium.
How nice of you. I'm sure
she'll appreciate that.
Have you seen sarah ?
Oh, she already left. She was
canoodling in the back row,
- Found an old boyfriend I think.
- She left ?
- Are you going then ?
- Going where ?
Up to topanga. Shall we meet there ?
Aren't we all going
out to the home and...
Commune...
Weekend ?
We were joking.
Hey, guys ! Go put your
books in your rooms
And get ready for your bath.
You wanna move back in ?
- Excuse me ?
- Yeah.
I've been thinking a lot
about it and I guess you were right.
Um, it's not good for the
boys. They need you here.
Yeah.
- Thank you so much, vanessa.
-  Yeah.
So, I'm starting dinner.
Why don't you go do their baths
and we can eat in about 20 minutes ?
Let me, uh, take this
to the kitchen first.
Hello.
I brought the pots and pans.
That... That wasn't necessary.
On second thought, your
other idea was the better one.
I went down to crate & barrel
and bought myself another set.
You did ?
I know what's going on, Ruth.
You do ?
Yes, I do. None of
your furniture is here.
You only brought one change of clothing.
- No toiletries.
- I brought my soap.
No, please, look-
Let's not waste any more
of each other's time, okay ?
It's not respectful. I get it.
You want to leave me.
But first you want to make sure
that I have everything that I need,
Which is...
Very kind and thoughtful
as you always are.
George, it's not because-
It doesn't matter why. It's okay.
I called the dean.
I start back this semester.
And thanks to you I have my apartment...
And my pots...
And my pans.
So thank you.
I loved you.
You loved me.
That was a good thing.
Now it's changed.
So...
Consider yourself free.
* on every day you
gaze upon the sunset *
* with such love and intensity *
* why... *
* it's, uh, it's almost *
* as if you could only crack the code *
* then you'd finally understand *
* what this all means *
* ah, but if you could,
do you think you would *
* trade it all ? *
* all the pain *
* and suffering *
* ah, but then you'd miss *
* the beauty of the
light upon this earth *
* and, and the sweetness
of the leaving. *