Saison 5 Episode 2
"Dancing For Me"
Damn it.
- I'm gonna pull out!
- No no no! Don't!
- We're supposed to wait.
- It's okay.
- It's been long enough.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
- All right.
Why don't you put a
little man inside me?
- Whoa! Whoa!
- Yeah, too much man, huh?
We've got a little visitor.
Hello, gorgeous.
Are you dancing for us?
- I'm dancing for me.
- Good for you.
Why don't we all get
a little breakfast ?
- Rain check.
- Yeah.
On saturday, more than 300,000...
I need you to sign this.
"Step-Parent petition"?
Yeah, if we go the surrogate route.
Then at the time of birth
The child's legal parents
will be me and the surrogate.
But then she'll sign away her rights
And you'll then adopt as co-Parent.
I only get to be co-Parent?
That doesn't seem fair.
We'll both be co-Parents.
It's just words.
I've already read everything.
Everything?
Yeah. I signed your form,
now you need to sign mine.
Okay.
We're really doing this, aren't we?
David.
No, it's gonna be great, I know.
I spoke to shirley
what's-Her-Name,
The adoption counselor. If we adopt,
She's supposed to fax over
an orientation schedule.
Mornings are better for me.
Nights are better for me.
Okay, we can do nights.
- I'm sure rog will let me go.
- Thank you.
This doesn't mean you
get to pick the name.
What are you talking about? I'm
being nice to you because I love you.
You're being nice to me because
you want to pick the baby's name.
The fact that jackson charles
Fisher is an excellent name,
And pretty much guarantees that our son
Will be playing third base
for the los angeles dodgers
Is completely a separate issue.
Look at you, always working.
That's because there's
always work to do.
What are you doing?
Just cleaning a bit up
here. One of the advantages,
Or disadvantages, of being tall
Is you can see dust where no one can.
That was my drying towel.
I'm sorry. Should I use something else?
It's a little late now.
You know, you've been at sixes
and sevens with me all day.
George, the kitchen is my
territory. I have my ways.
So, what if I take
you out of the kitchen
And we walk down to that little
armenian deli and get a sandwich?
- It's 10:30 in the morning!
- okay.
I'll just make myself a sandwich.
Do we have any of that
spicy mustard I like?
If we do, it's in the
door where it always is.
I don't see any.
If it's too much of an imposition
to help your grandmother,
Then I'll make my own sandwich!
Just tip my chair over so
i can crawl to the breadbox!
Let me do it!
Ruth...
I can do it.
Here's a recent photo.
His suit's being cleaned.
I'll get that to you tomorrow.
You wanted us to handle
the memorial marker as well?
Yeah, the polished granite.
I put a post-It in the catalog.
Just his name- "Samuel wayne
hoviak. Beloved husband.
- Sam hoviak?
-  Yeah.
- Did he go to bonaventure high?
- Yeah, did you know him?
Well, yeah. I knew him real well.
I didn't even recognize him.
I haven't seen him in years.
We met in college. We
were both english majors.
How did you end up coming here?
Oh, I drive past all the time
on the way to sam's parents.
- Still on harvard, the same house?
- Yeah.
Again, I am so sorry.
If there's anything you need please
don't hesitate to call us day or night.
- Thank you.
He was a buddy of yours ?
Yeah, yeah...
Me, him and this other guy
Were, like, best friends
all through high school.
I'm really excited about these.
Yeah, I went in a totally different
direction from the last series.
- I can see that.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I felt like I took the
collage stuff as far as I could.
And with these I was thinking
less about the process
I think simple emotional connection.
Well?
They're quite beautiful.
But I can't sell them.
- What do you mean?
- Well, Claire, they're wedding photographs.
- Yeah, technically, but...
- And they're beautifully shot, but...
I'm an art dealer,
I know what people want.
And it's not pictures from
someone else's wedding.
Maybe if I took out some of the ones
That specifically
identify it as a wedding.
You know, make it a
little more ambiguous.
Do you think I should?
I would never ask you to
compromise your artistic vision.
Well, I can probably interpret my vision
In different ways, you know?
And I was kind of hoping
to get another show soon.
Yeah.
Sorry.
I still have a couple ideas
for the collage series.
You know?
All right, I'm having
a group show next month.
If you can bring me two pieces
From your collage series
I'll see what I can do
to find a place for them.
Just two?
The world is an evil place, Claire.
- Notice something different?
- About what?
No formaldehyde smell.
I'm trying a new line of
chemicals- "Millennium new era. "
Less toxic exposure
So I'll live to see my grandkids.
Looks good, right?
Do you know who this is?
- Should I?
- It's sam hoviak.
Sam...
Oh my god, you're kidding.
Sam hoviak from high school?
- Wow, he got fat.
- Yeah.
I used to have such a crush on him.
- Really?
- He always so nice to me.
And he had such great shoulders.
- He was run over?
- Yeah, he ran over himself.
- How do you do that?
- I have no idea.
The adoption agency.
This is David Fisher.
Yes, shirley. How are you?
No fucking way.
Yeah, that's you.
Jesus, what a lardass.
Well, I guess I ate too much pussy, huh?
Look at you. You used to be so
obsessed with your fucking six-Pack
I thought you were secretly gay.
Dude, I got fat. It's
not the end of the world.
You swore you'd never become a fucking
funeral director and look at you now.
At least I don't need a
golf cart to get around.
Oh, dude, harsh.
By the way, I always knew
you slept with sheila maddox
While she was supposedly my girlfriend.
The operative word there is supposedly.
You were too busy trying to
bajennifer kaufman to notice.
- I did bag jennifer kaufman.
- I knew you did.
And sheila knew it too. I
was merely comforting her.
Do you remember that?
Remember feeling like there was
Nothing in the world you
couldn't get away with
And it would always be that way?
Did you make a vegetable?
No, this is spinach lasagna.
I figured that would be our vegetable.
Well, I only asked because
sometimes you make a dish
And it's not until we're
almost finished eating
That you remember
it's still in the oven.
I guess I must have alzheimer's.
I wasn't being critical, Ruth.
Actually, I find all your
little quirks very endearing.
This is delicious.
- Thank you.
- What's in it?
Do you want me to list
all the ingredients?
Not if you don't want to. I was
just wondering what this spice is?
"Italian seasoning. "
I didn't know you could buy
it all mixed up like this.
"Basil, rosemary, marjoram,
sage, thyme, oregano. "
have to keep this in stock.
I'll make a note of it.
Do you know what they
call an italian hooker?
A pasta-Tute
Th kind of humor doesn't
really appeal to me, George.
Guess it's not that funny.
You're goddamned right it's not funny!
None of this funny! You
tricked me into marrying you!
You knew you were crazy
and didn't tell me!
And now I have to take care
of you for the rest of my life!
What did I do to fucking deserve this?!
You can really taste the rosemary.
I think you're making
a terrible mistake.
- You don't belong in a place like that.
- I have to do my internship.
I've got to clock 300 hours.
But a free clinic?
You're going to have to hire an
armed escort to walk to your car.
You're catastrophysing.
Those places attract the
absolute dregs of society.
The most desperate
and the most dangerous.
The reason I charge $200 an hour
Is to keep those kinds of
people out of my office.
Well, thankfully I'm not you.
You know, I would like to work
with people who actually need help.
Really, Brenda, let me find
you a better internship.
One that's more suited to your talents.
I hate to let the fact
that I've slept with
Half of southern california's
psychiatric academia go to waste.
No thank you. I am fine.
What makes you think you're
going to help them anyway?
You're always talking
about doing cognitive work.
You live in your head.
How are you going to
relate to crack addicts?
Because I've had my own
struggles with addiction.
- Because we're all human.
- No, honey, we're not.
That's what you're going to learn.
- Hi.
- Hey !
- Hi, mommy.
- Hello, Maya.
How's my favorite little girl?
Hello, margaret.
Nate. Oh, look at you
And your happy little family.
Mommy just ordered chinese
- And it's going to be here in 10 minutes.
- Perfect.
My mom's trying to
convince me that I'm making
A huge mistake by
working at a free clinic.
- I think it's kind of great.
- Yes, let's all save the world.
Well, why not save the world?
I think you're both
being naive about this.
Well, sometimes that's
not such a bad thing.
I wanna go read "peter rabbit.
You wanna go read "peter rabbit?
the time blame the deaths
Of million of fish in
north carolina waters...
So, you want move up to my room?
I do but I should go.
It's completely private up there.
- Well...
- And no one minds if you stay over.
Am I interrupting anything?
No.
Of course not.
It's your house.
My wife's actually.
Do you remember sharon?
Of course.
We met at the wedding.
Oh, yeah, Nate and Brenda's wedding.
- It's nice to see you again.
- Hi.
So anything good on?
Oh, I don't know.
Something about fish I think.
- I should go.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
- You sure?
Tomorrow's my day off, so...
So what's the hurry?
I have a bunch of errands
to do in the morning.
- Okay, let me walk you out.
- No, I'm fine.
Stay here with George.
- Wanna have lunch tomorrow?
- Yeah. Great.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, give me a call.
Okay.
I'm sorry, baby, I'm
not gonna come tonight.
It's okay.
It's not the lithium. It's the seroquel.
It...
Sometimes it makes it
difficult to ejaculate.
That's okay.
I thought I was passed all that, though.
I hate this.
Billy, it's okay.
I came already.
Oh, so I don't matter, right?
No, of course not.
You're here purely to service me.
And now that you've
satisfied me, I must kill you.
Seriously, don't freak out about this.
It'll just make the next
time that much better.
I don't know. I just don't
want to name him logan.
Why don't you like logan?
You've got to be kidding me.
It's like a porn star name.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
Why are you looking at me
like you're about to eat me?
I'm just looking at
how beautiful you are.
- Shut up.
- I mean it.
You're starting to creep me out.
I want our baby to be part you, too.
Well, I think we're out of luck there.
Not if we ask Claire to
donate some of her eggs.
- Claire?
- Yeah.
Then the baby could be like a
combination of the two of us.
Or as close as we could get anyway.
Well, I guess I could ask.
I think it's a great idea.
Really?
Definitely.
I am the egg man.
Goo-Goo-Ga-Joob?
Daddy.
What's taking so long?
It's okay. Just calm down.
Excuse me. I'm Bren...
Hi, Brenda Chenowith. I'm
here to see Eileen Goldberg.
Brenda, hi. I'm Eileen.
- Hi.
- Follow me.
Try not to trip over any of our family.
So, this your office.
You'll share it with
mohan our other intern.
He's tuesdays and thursdays and
you're monday, wednesday and friday.
So hopefully you'll never meet,
'cause he's kind of a moron.
We have a staff meeting
at 2:00 in the afternoon.
Until then, maybe you could
read through some of these files.
- Okay.
I'm glad you're here. We need you.
- I'm glad I'm here, too.
- Okay.
I thought you had a lunch.
I do.
I'm just waiting for
her to call me back.
I started the prep
work on the other body.
- I'll finish it up by tomorrow.
- Good.
Might be a long lunch
If you know what I mean.
well, good luck.
Yeah.
I really like this girl.
Nate.
- Oh my god. Tom wheeler. Hey.
- Yeah!
When I heard the funeral was
here I was hoping I'd seeou.
- Last I heard you were still up in seattle.
- Yeah yeah.
Well, no, I'm...
- Back here now. Working here.
- Really?
- You always swore that-
- Yeah yeah, I know.
But the funny this is I
actually like this work.
Wow. That's great.
That's great. I've got a software
consulting firm over in encino.
- Oh, great great.
- Yeah, it is good.
I've got a wife, three kids.
Basically turned into
my father.
Your father was a really
good guy as I remember him.
My dad never bought us beer.
Although, he probably
would have if I'd asked him.
My oldest- Can you
believe this?
He's 18.
He's going to college in the fall.
Man, we are getting up there, aren't we?
Man, it is really good to see you.
But, damn, I wish it was
under better circumstances.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's kind of hard
to believe sam's dead.
Yeah, I never would have thought
he'd be the first one to go.
So how does someone run over himself?
I don't know.
- Listen, I've gotta go pay respects.
- Okay.
- What do you say get a beer later, catch up?
- That would be great.
Okay. Good to see you.
He has good days
and he has bad days.
More bad than good.
Really?
Whenever I talk to him on
the phone he sounds great.
Well, your calls always help.
I thought I heard your voice.
- Hi, daddy.
- Hi, sweetie.
Hi.
- You look so good.
- Well, I feel pretty good.
I guess sending thousands of volts
of electricity through the brain
- Must've done the trick.
- That's so good to hear.
Here, sit down. I made some iced tea.
Thank you.
I'm, still having
problems with my memory.
Yesterday he forgot
our home phone number.
They needed it at the pharmacy
And he was hunting all over the
store for me like a lost little boy.
Gets pretty frustrating.
But, dad, that's normal. That's
not something to worry about.
Oh, I know. I know.
The doctor said it could
be a very long haul.
So, how have you been filling your time?
Oh, resting mostly.
And a lot of reading.
I just finished clinton's book.
- Oh, I've been wanting to read that?
- Really?
Let me get it for you.
Before I forget.
Well, he seems so much better.
With everything you said i
wasn't sure what to expect.
I'm never sure what to expect.
Every day's a new adventure.
Hey, sharon. It's Rico again.
Obviously, we're not
going to have lunch today.
But, uh, why don't you give me
a call back so we can reschedule?
Okay? Bye-Bye.
Thanks for helping me with this.
It's not a problem.
Be nice to have something
feels remotely familiar
- At Billy's apartment.
- I can relate.
Of course, if you'd like to do a favor
- For me in return...
- What?
It's a big favor.
Okay.
Donate some of your
eggs to Keith and me?
- Like when?
- As soon as possible, I guess.
I mean, we have to
find a surrogate first.
And then you would both have
to go on birth control pills
At the same time so your cycles
Would coincide.
Then there would be all
sorts of hormone injections.
And you wouldn't be able
to exercise or anything.
No drugs or drinking, of course.
Eventually, the eggs would be harvested
Through a needle
inserted into the vagina.
Your vagina.
It's like surgery.
Okay, I get it. It's asking too much.
I mean, I haven't
given that much thought
To my eggs.
But I'm not exactly sure I
want to give any of them away.
It really wasn't fair of me to ask.
- You're not mad?
- No, of course not. No.
Ev if it all worked out,
there would be the weirdness
Of having a niece that
you're also the mother of.
Yeah, that's really kind of creepy.
It could make thanksgiving
dinners a little awkward.
Everyone say hello to Brenda
Chenowith our new intern.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Hi.
Okay.
We're about to discuss the
case of one tanisha williams.
32 years old, habitual
abuser of crack cocaine
And occasional prostitute.
The state is seeking custody
of her 12-Year-Old child
After said child complained that her
mother tied her to the coffee table,
Whipped her until she bled
and then sexually molested her
With a rolled up copy of "newsweek. "
All for the viewing
pleasure of her boyfriend.
I'm sure the kid's lying.
There's no way that
woman reads "newsweek. "
Is this the same child
with all the burn marks?
No, that's her sister.
Since the children
have been in foster care-
- You okay?
- Yeah.
No, I mean.
Don't feel bad.
You've got to be in a
strong place to work here.
I'm in a strong place.
Good.
Hey, it's sharon.
I'm not in right now.
Please leave
me a message
Excuse me. Have you seen sharon kinney?
No, sorry. Haven't
seen her around today.
Thank you!
Hello, Rico.
Hey, vanessa.
Listen, I'm sorry. I don't think
i can take the kids out tonight.
I didn't make dinner for them.
You said you'd take them out.
I know, I'm sorry. But a
friend of mine is missing
And I'm starting to worry.
- What friend?
- Sharon.
What, that woman you've been seeing?
- Yeah.
- What do you mean she's missing?
I don't know. She just disappeared.
I hope she's okay. Have you
started calling the hospitals?
Oh, man. I guess I should.
I'm sorry about the kids.
Don't worry about it.
I hope you find her.
And I'm sure she's fine.
- Okay, bye-Bye.
- Bye, Rico.
City and listing?
Yes, los angeles. County hospital.
This tea is interesting.
- What did you call it?
- Yerba mate.
You must find all kinds of
new things in your adventures.
What adventures?
I mostly see my hotel room and
the inside of doctor's offices.
Still, hawaii, san francisco, portland.
It all sounds so exciting.
I like it.
I get to set my own schedule.
Yeah, there are plenty of perks.
Are you dating anyone?
There must be men lined at
the door to see you. Doctors.
yeah, like
they're such prizes.
I guess men are the same everywhere.
Actually, I have been dating a doctor
In phoenix for a while.
- What's his name?
- Philip.
- Tell me.
- No, he's fine.
He's a little obsessed with his work.
But that's normal.
- Is it serious?
- Well, he seems to think so.
But...
I'm in no hurry to get married.
Good for you.
If you want my advice
and-
Lord knows I'm not one to give advice.
But I think you should know
exactly what you're getting into
Before you make that jump.
Marriage is hard.
I know this must be difficult for you.
My father.
Thank you for saying that.
Sometimes that's all I need to hear.
That someone understands.
You know, I don't usually
give advice, either.
But I think, if you look hard enough
You'll see that the man you fell
in love with is still in there.
Yes?
Hi, mom. It's me, Brenda.
You want me to make those calls for you?
Yes.
Oh, I feel awful.
Well, honey, those
people are so depressing.
mom, it's not that.
It's...
I don't
know. It's-
You know, it wasn't
really the job for you.
Yeah yeah, maybe not.
You just don't know how
to dress down like them.
You must have been a walking target.
Yeah, mom, you're right, that's it.
And let us not forget,
you just had a miscarriage.
Well, I really don't see
what that's got to do with it.
Honey, you're still in shock.
I'm so glad that you're more in tune
With my emotional state than me.
Well, I'm a very good psychologist.
- I was being sarcastic.
- I know that as well.
Well, don't forget to
send me a bill for $200.
Oh, I won't.
Somehow we end up in cambodia.
And it is like, "holy fuck"!
A world you never even knew existed.
We lived in a little tree
house up with the birds.
Oh, god. That sounds so amazing,
Just traveling like that.
You have to. It's your
responsibility as an artist
To try everything that
world has to offer.
We just went wherever we
wanted till the money ran out.
And get this. The best part was,
When we got back the first
piece of mail that I opened
Was this huge fucking check.
- Oh, wow.
- Yeah, this grant is a godsend.
Gives us enough money
to live on for a year
While I get back to
work on my installation.
That is so great. God, i
wish I could get a grant.
Is this still the, uh, poultry thing?
Yes, but it's expanded
way beyond that now.
You need to come by our
new space and check it out.
- It's amazing.
- I would love to.
Yeah, we're still unpacking shit.
You know what I found
was that video we shot
When we turned the L.A. River red.
Oh no, not as daunting as it sounds.
It hadn't rained in months.
There was an inch of water.
But still it was, like,
this trickle of blood
Snaking through the city.
It was pretty cool.
I can't believe they talked
you into becoming a professor.
Well, associate professor.
But, uh, yeah, it's
not so bad, you know?
Got to pay the rent.
Well, you're a better man than me.
He is such an amazing teacher. Really.
Well, those that can't, do.
So, Billy said you're
working on a new series.
Yeah, yeah.
I just showed them to my gallery owner.
Who loved them, but he still
wants more of my old series.
He does? You didn't tell me that.
Yeah, I guess he thinks I'm a factory
Who's going to keep
churning out the same stuff.
So what about you, Billy? What
are you working on these days?
Well, molding
impressionable young minds.
Arguing for a decent budget.
Oh, god. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm so glad I'm out of that world.
Me, too. I am never setting
foot on a campus again.
I mean, how do you even have time
To do your real work?
To be honest, I'm not exactly
Overflowing with ideas just now.
We all hit dry spots.
Yeah, that we do.
So how are you handling it?
- Handling what?
- Turning 40.
It's a couple months from now, right?
Yeah, yeah.
I think I'm handling it fine,
I haven't...
really thought
that much about it.
yeah, right.
Listen, um...
Can I ask you a personal question?
Sure.
Do you have a harder time now?
You know, like, getting wood?
Yeah. Yeah, occasionally.
Do you ever look at girls?
Young girls, like, 14-15?
You get that same feeling you
got when you were that age.
And then you're so fucking hard
It feels like it might break.
I have a daughter, tom. So I don't
look at young girls like that.
Liar. Look, I've got a daughter, too.
She's 13, of course i
don't look at her that way.
But she's got this one friend.
She comes over to the house all the time
And, jesus, fuck.
She is just so perfect.
She's a child, tom. You cannot go there.
Look, Nate, I know she
is! I would never do that.
But, I mean, it's not even
the thought of actual sex.
It's just- It's that
That
young-
All that energy, you know?
It's likes she reminds
me of this part of me
That I've forgotten even existed.
- You know?
- No, I don't know.
Really? Nate, don't you ever
lie awake in bed at night
And just think, "jesus, fuck,
I'm going to be 40 fucking years old"?
No, I don't. I lie
in bed awake at night
Thinking, "thank you, god,
for letting me live this long. "
Are you, like, christian or something?
no.
I've just had a lot of serious
shit happen to me in my life.
And I really get it now
that this doesn't last.
And I'm no different from anybody else.
Yes, indeed this will happen to me.
It is happening to me a
little bit each everyday.
And that doesn't freak me out.
If anything, it's liberating.
Okay, so I guess it
comes with the territory?
I mean, your job.
No, I don't think it's the
job, really. It's just-
The job allows me to
practice being okay with it.
Yeah yeah, okay, so there.
You have to practice.
Okay? So you're really not okay with it.
- Of course, you have to practice.
- Yeah, but Nate...
It's just so fucking big.
I mean, it's all going by so fucking fast.
- Would you change anything?
- Like what?
Like who you're with or what you
do or what kind of person you are.
Because if you would, do it now.
Whoa, dude.
- That's really harsh.
- Look, this is it, tom!
This is all we have.
Right here, right now.
You know, I've got to go home.
I wanna be there
before Maya goes to bed.
- It was good seeing you.
- Yeah, man.
It was good seeing you. We
should get together sometime.
Yeah yeah, okay.
Yeah, give me a call.
So what's everyone up to?
Should we hit the concord?
I've been dying to go there.
You think we can get in?
Wolf could get his
publicist to make a call.
You guys are going to
have to do it without me.
- No!
- Yeah, I'm beat.
Yeah, right. You got another
party you're going to?
You don't want us slowing you down?
No, I still got to work on
my lesson plan for next week.
You serious? Come on, man.
Where's the old Billy I used to know?
He's going to the restroom.
Is he doing okay?
Hmm? Yeah. He's great.
- Why, you don't think he is?
I don't know. The Billy Chenowith
i knew wouldn't be going home early.
He'd have us out all night doing
something completely insane.
It's nice to have maggie here, isn't it?
Yes, it certainly is.
She's one of the few things I did right.
That and marry you.
You're a sweet one when you want to be.
It's easy to be sweet
when I'm married to you.
Good night, George.
Good night.
He had a tattoo.
Sam had a tattoo on his ass
That said, "U.S.D.A. Prime beef. "
- Well, it was 1982.
- Sorry my cruch is officially over.
If you can handle it from here,
i have a body waiting downstairs.
Wait a minute, I thought
Rico was handling it.
He had an emergency with sharon.
What kind of an emergency?
Uh, hi, I'm tom wheeler.
I first met sam in the 10th grade
When he talked me and Nate,
Who stands right behind you there,
Into cutting biology class.
Then we jumped out the
second story window.
Nate when first and sprained his ankle.
I landed without injury.
Until, of course, sam jumped on me
And gave me a mild
concussion.
At that moment
Or fates were sealed as best friends.
Best days of my life were
spent with these guys.
But as always happens as time goes by...
once we had people using an apartment
For purposes of prostitution.
But I kicked them right
out on their zadnek.
You don't think she's doing
anything like this, do you?
Oh, no. No no no.
She's just been missing
And I'm really worried that
something's happened to her.
Sharon, you in there?
I don't smell anything.
Hello.
Sharon?
Oh my god! What the fuck are you doing?
You're here!
You came into my
apartment. Are you crazy?
- He insisted I let him in.
- I was worried!
We were supposed to have lunch yesterday
And I've called you half a dozen times.
And you didn't even answer your door.
Look, I'm sorry.
I thought you could, you know...
Take a hint.
Okay.
- Miss Chenowith.
- Brenda.
- Jackie.
- Hi.
- Hi, have a seat please.
- Thank you.
I typically award this internship
to my most promising student.
But apparently somebody
pulled some strings somewhere
And it's to go to you now,
so I guess that's that.
We have over 17,000 students here
From every possible ethnic
and socio-Economic background.
Quite a few of them end
up here needing our help.
- I understand.
- We deal with everything
From eating disorders to depression
To stress-Related
disorders. You name it.
It's not a walk in the park.
Are you ready for that?
Yeah, I think I'll manage.
- Anything else?
- It says you speak a second language.
Yes. French.
Ah, great.
We get a lot of people from
france here.
Hi.
I'm sorry I didn't call
first. I was just driving by.
Come in.
Hey, uh, do you think
I can take the kids
out to dinner tonight?
Rico, you can't keep
changing days on me.
I'm sorry.
Forget it.
What happened to
sharon? Did you find her?
She died.
Oh my god, Rico.
Yeah, she died.
- What happened?
- She had a heart thing.
I found her in her apartment.
Baby, that's so awful.
I'm so sorry.
I'm ill kind of reeling from it.
You know?
It's so sudden.
Well, take the boys out for pizza.
You need them with you.
It'll make you feel better.
Do you think that you can come too?
Of course.
Of course. Just give me a few minutes.
Finish your lesson plans already?
No.
I don't really have the energy for it.
I'm working on a new idea.
Yeah, I want to go back
to the collage stuff.
But on a much bigger scale.
Not just people as
fragments glued together,
But, like, the whole world.
Well, that sounds good.
Yeah, sort of capture the idea that...
everything we know is
just barely being held together.
- That's big.
- I know.
It's big. It's really big.
I'm just  trying to
I'm still trying to figure it all out.
Well, I'll let you keep working then.
So have you had an opportunity
to talk to Claire yet?
Well, yes. Yesterday.
And you didn't tell me?
I wanted to give her another
day to think about it.
- And?
- She won't do it.
- Serious?
- She's strongly against it.
- That's weird.
- Is it, though?
Sometimes I think what's weird is
us trying to create our own child.
We're two men, Keith. It's not possible.
There's no way that we're
going to have a child
That's both part me and part you.
- I know that, David.
- Then let's stop pretending.
Whether we have a child through
a surrogate or we adopt a child,
All that's important
is the child itself.
Okay.
- Really?
- Of course.
look...
I wasn't trying to be
selfish about any of this.
And I really can't
imagine anything greater
Than being able to look at our child
And see you in him. Or see you in her.
Hopefully you still will.
It was such a short visit, maggie.
I wish you could stay longer.
That's the good and
the bad part of my job-
I'm never anywhere very long.
Vanilla or chocolate?
I'd like the neapolitan.
We don't have that.
Of course we do.
- I had some yesterday.
- Yes and now we're out of it.
How can we be out of it?
That's what I like! Neapolitan!
Daddy, why don't you take a little
vanilla and a little chocolate?
- It's almost the same thing.
- No, it is not the same!
Neapolitan is chocolate,
vanilla and strawberry!
If there's no strawberry it most
definitely is not neapolitan!
You see what I go through?
I'm sorry. It's just...
My life is so goddamned pathetic.
All I have to look forward to
is a fucking bowl of ice cream.
and I can't even get that!
I'm sorry.
I'm trying not to be demanding.
It's just...
Oh, my life is shit!
I simply don't know
how to deal with this.
It's like having another child.
It's okay, daddy.
You're gonna have moments like
this. It's gonna get better.
Will it really?
Maggie, please don't leave.
I'm not sure I can do this by myself.
If you leave tomorrow,
maggie, I just-
I don't know what I'll do.
Maybe I can stay a little longer.
Sous-titres par
la Fisher Team
Transcript:
Raceman
Synchronisation :
EZ, Occeane
Relecture et corrections finales :
Guzo
http://www.sixfeetunder-france.com
http://www.forom.com