You Never Know
Hello?
- Hi, may I speak with Joe Marti, please?
- Speaking.
Joe, glad I caught ya!
Is this a sales call?
I just wanted to let you know that a representative from Ameritech Vinyl Windows will be in your area…
- I’m not interested.
- There’s absolutely no obligation to buy anything…
Look.
I said no.
- For a limited time, we’re offering interest- free….
- Hey, goodbye, asshole!
Fuck, he’s got a gun!
Get down!
Hey, remember me?
Daniel, what the hell
Oh my God!
Daniel, please! No, please!
Fuck you!
Oh, my God!
Hello? Hello?
- This is okay?
- Yeah
You sure you’re comfortable?
Aren’t you? Do you want to get on top?
Well, I don’t have to. You want me to?
If you want to. But I’m fine like this.
Maya’s right there.
She’s not looking.
I know, but…
Hi, this is Lisa…
And Nate…
And Maya…C’mon, sweetie.
And we’re the Fisher family. Leave a message.
Hi, Lisa, it’s Carol. Please pick up if you’re there.
I don’t know where else you could be. Both your cars are in my driveway.
Listen, I need muffins.
Corn muffins. I had an intense craving for miniature corn muffins.
Please! This is my one hour a day to eat carbs.
Shut up!
Stop ignoring me!
Don’t make her the muffins! Don’t make her the muffins!
Hello!!!
The flowers that bloom in the spring, tra- la, we promise a merry sunshine
As we merrily dance and we sing, tra- la
We welcome the hope that they bring, tra- la
Of a summer of roses and wine,
Of a summer of roses and wine!
That’s great.
And that’s what we mean when we say that a thing
Is welcome as flowers that bloom in the spring.
- David...
David. It’s a little early.
Sorry. I just want to make sure I get it right.
Some of the guys in this chorus are so good.
One of them even recorded with Chanticleer.
You sound great
I even dreamed about singing last night.
You weren’t just dreaming.
- Oh, God, punch me next time!
- I did
What happened to your uniform?
I tore it getting a Frisbee out of a tree.
- Why were you..
- That’s what security guards do, David.
We help people.
I’m leaving.
Do you think you’d like Beef Blast Pizza Rolls?
Um, I doubt it.
Me neither. But with a double coupon, it’s practically free.
Maybe the boys will like them.
I might not be home tonight.
Take a sweater.
You’ve reached the Fisher Family. Please leave a message.
Ruth, are you there? It’s Sarah.
I’m just checking in on you. I know what a drag it is when you’re out of work.
Thought you might want to come up to Topanga for the day.
I could make some of Aunt May’s German potato salad.
I know you like that. Call me. Bye!
You liked her potato salad. I hated it.
It just never occurs to you that a madman will walk into your husband’s office
and suddenly…
he’s gone.
No, of course not.
And then there’s telling the children.
We have 2 girls, 12 and 16.
What should I say to them?
To make them feel better?
What?
Well, uh…you, you could.
Hello.
Glad you could make it. Nate, this is Dorothy Milne.
Nate Fisher.
That’s my partner.
I am very sorry about your husband.
I know these are just words,
but we’ll work together with you to give him a fitting tribute.
Thank you!
Everything’s already been taken care of.
We’re done.
Good.
Now, let me walk you to your car.
I didn’t even go to my prom.
If somebody asked me, I probably would’ve freaked out.
I took Nancy Pollard. She smelled like fried chicken.
- Why?
- I don’t know. She just did.
I got a bottle of champagne with my friend, Parker,
and we climbed the fence to school, and we just sat in the quad,
and got drunk, and said good fucking bye to high school.
Nice!
- Then we both totally started crying.
- Why
I don’t know.
I don’t know. I guess we were like saying goodbye to our childhood, or whatever.
It just seemed sad.
Yeah?
I mean, I hated fucking high school,
but still, it was my life.
And it was all I knew, and it was just over.
God, could I be more pathetic?
You’re not pathetic.
You’re just sensitive.
I know. I’m too sensitive.
No, you’re perfect.
What time do you have to get up?
Oh, fuck, I have to get up in like 3 hours,
and I haven’t even done the assignment yet.
- You keep distracting me.
- I keep distracting you?
Yeah, my hands are like magnetically drawn to your dick!
What is the assignment?
I have to read and critique some theoretical conceptual bullshit.
They make you take all the boring classes with theory before they let you do anything cool with clay.
I know exactly how you feel.
- No, you don’t.
- That’s why I dropped out of music school.
All I wanted to do was write great music,
but they had me studying all this shit that had nothing to do with anything.
They try to program your mind so you’re exactly like everybody else.
Don’t let them do that to you.
You’re too talented.
Do you think so?
What?
You think I like you just ‘cause you have the softest skin I’ve ever felt?
I don’t know.
You’re amazing, Claire.
- Hello, beautiful ladies.
- Good morning.
Thank you for letting me sleep in.
Does your brother like eggplant?
Um, I don’t know. I guess.
I figured we could grill some salmon tonight. I just don’t know what else.
Oh, is that tonight?
- Yes.
- Can we cancel?
- It was your idea!
- I know..
and it sounded good at the time, but...
...I see David at work every day, and it’s not like I’m looking to spend some quality time with Keith.
You wanted David to see Maya!
Okay, you’re right. We’ll do it
Hey, your uncle David’s coming over. Won’t that be fun? Huh?
Yeah, yeah! I’ll try once more.
Please?
I’ll try once more.
Great!
Lisa, you’re being careful, right?
I’m being very delicate.
Hey, Maya.
- Honey, I think you’re going too deep.
- Nate, you worry too much.
Just because you deal with people dying every day…
Look, I’ve noticed that sometimes after you clean her ears,
- she doesn’t respond as quickly.
- So you think I’ve injured her?
Of course not. I’m just saying that…
maybe there’s some ringing in her ears after you’ve cleaned them.
Nate! I know whether my child can hear or not! She can hear!
She’s been tested, and she can hear!
- Right, your child.
- I didn’t mean—
Look, I know I’m just the father but I’m every bit as committed to her as you are.
- Nate—
- I’m just trying to help.
I gotta get to work.
You’ve reached the Fisher family. Please leave a message.
Ruth, it’s Sarah.
I’m disappointed you didn’t call back
Look, I’ll be honest. I was trying to trick you into coming out here.
I need you. I hurt my back and I’m all alone—
What did you do?
I fell off a ladder.
Have you seen a doctor?
He told me to stay in bed, and he gave me a prescription for Vicadin.
What do you need me to do?
Pick it up for me?
Give me the address of the pharmacy.
Oh, Ruth, I knew I could count on you!
Are you doing this with me?
Yes.
I can do it myself, David.
Well, I’m sure that’s true, but Nate and I have found it’s helpful to have two people in there.
Why? So one of you can sleep late?
And, of course, we’ll place an obituary notice in the paper.
No, we’d like to keep this private, and as simple as possible.
You see this kind of thing on TV, and you think,
oh my God, those poor people…
but now it’s happening to us,
and we have to see it every time we turn it on…
Thank you.
We knew that Daniel was a troubled boy, but we really thought he was getting better.
Your son…isn’t the one who did the shooting?
- Yes.
- I’m sorry. We can’t possibly…
…imagine what you must be going through.
But you can rest assured, we will do everything we can help you through this dark time.
Thank you.
Fisher and Sons has never turned down a funeral, and neither will Fisher and Diaz.
Oh, that’s great, so when Dorothy Milne is crying over her husband’s casket,
I’ll be sure to tell her that you’re in the next room arranging flowers around the fucking man who killed him.
The services will be held on different days. There will be no conflict.
Oh, come on, man, I know you like to make a buck, but isn’t this going a little far?
That’s got nothing to do with it
The funeral isn’t for the deceased, it’s for the living.
Oh, really? Yeah, I read the same book as you.
Do you think Mr. and Mrs. Showalter are in any less pain than Dorothy Milne?
Maybe I don’t give a shit
Maybe if they did a better job in raising their kid he wouldn’t have killed all those people.
- Rico, you can’t blame them.
- Yes, I can blame them. And I do.
Well, whether you like it or not, this is your job. You’re gonna have to put your feelings aside.
Now, I need you to go to the morgue and pick up his body.
Fuck you, you pick it up! I’ve got nothing to do with this.
Hello, I’m Ruth, Sarah’s sister.
Well, too bad you didn’t get here five minutes ago. You could’ve cleaned up her puke.
Oh, I’m Bettina. Come on in.
Sarah, your sister’s here!
My goodness, you look awful!
Bettina, can we have a moment alone?
Why?
Because she’s my sister and we need to talk.
- What’s in the bag?
- It’s just the—
Just some, some some things I asked her to bring for me…the...lip balm, hair clips, strawberries.
- Well, no…
- Fork it over.
Ruth, help me, I’m being held hostage.
Shut your yappy mouth, or I’ll goddamn tape it shut!
- Goodness, what’s going on?
- Ruth, please!
Do I have to carry you back to the bed, or you gonna walk by yourself?
Bitch.
Give me the bag.
It’s her Vicodin. She has a prescription.
Of course she does! She has Vicodin prescriptions at half the pharmacies in LA!
Your sister’s into her second day of withdrawal.
She begged me to make sure she got through it NO MATTER WHAT!
Fuck that, I was high!
I'm sorry, Keith, I’m having problems at the morgue.
Why didn’t you call me before?
Because I didn’t know this was going to take so long. I’m sorry.
Fine, whatever. I’ll see you tonight
Can’t make it. Sorry for wasting your time.
You don’t need to leave. You and I can talk.
- We can do that?
- Sure, why not?
Tell me about that phone call. How did it make you feel?
Pissed off.
But I’m working on my anger management technique. I’m taking a lot of deep breaths.
That’s good.
Have you been feeling a lot of anger towards David lately?
I’ve been giving myself so many damn time- outs I haven’t been feeling too much of anything. Just numb.
Maybe this is a good time to let some of that anger out.
I’m fine.
Pretend David’s sitting right there next to you.
What do you want to say to him?
Anything that comes to mind.
Relax. Stop trying so hard. You’re making me nervous.
What other things would you like to tell him that you don’t like about him?
I hate your stupid little buckwheat pillow.
And I hate your nose spray!
And I hate the way you eat! You take little bitty bites,
and then you put your fork down after every little bite like you’re some fucking prince!
I hate the way you always want to fall asleep with your head on my shoulder!
Your head is heavy!
I hate the way you always make me feel like I’m my father by letting me walk all over you!
What?
Y’know, I always thought by being gay, I’d avoid fucking my mother, but I guess that’s not the case.
Have you thought about seeing a therapist on your own?
Wow, this is great.
It’s my polenta. You like it?
- It’s delicious.
- Thank you
- Hello.
- Hi, it’s Carol.
- Hello?
- Lisa
I’m at Mark Harmon and Pam Dawber’s place in the mountains. Listen, their cook knows nothing!
I need you to walk them through your basil vinaigrette.
Right now?
Yes, the salad’s waiting!
What?
- I’ve got to deal with this.
- Okay, go ahead. I’ll start the grill.
- I’ve still got a load of laundry to do.
- I’ll do it. Go.
- I’m sorry about this morning.
- Oh, God, me too!
Are you still there?
I just worry about Maya. I get so scared something’s gonna go wrong.
Nothing’s gonna go wrong.
- Salad dressing!
I know. Maya has the best mom in the world.
Hello!
I NEED dressing!
I mean, Gabe was definitely exciting,
in kind of a sick way,
but…I think Phil’s like the only guy who’s ever really understood me.
That’s cool. Not even my imaginary friends understand me.
Or maybe they do. They just don’t like me.
I think you need better imaginary friends.
No. I think they’re the best I can do.
So what do you really like about this guy?
I don’t know. He’s sweet.
- He’s hot.
- Nice
- He’s got his own band.
- It’s Keanu Reeves, isn’t it?
- Yes! Exactly!
- I knew it!
But come on, Claire, those are superficial things.
And you seem like anything but superficial, so, what do you really like about him?
well, I like the way he treats me, you know?
He makes me feel good. Like I’m kind of okay.
Like I’m smart and talented and pretty.
Hello!
Totally embarrassing.
No, no, no. Women tell me this kind of thing all the time. I’m the guy who listens.
Yeah, you do listen.
That’s really nice about you. I really like talking to you.
I like listening to you.
Well, I hope it could go both ways.
If you’re dating anyone, you can totally talk to me.
Thanks, but, no, I’m not dating. No dating.
I think I’m kind of allergic, actually. I start itching and swell up and bleed profusely.
But no, it sounds really nice, having somebody in your life that makes you hate yourself less.
I could use that.
Oh, come on, I mean, you’re great.
- I wasn’t fishing.
- I’m serious, Russell. I think you’re great.
Well, tell me that when it’s two in the morning, and I’m laying in bed
and I’m eating my fourth bowl of cereal,
and I’m just beating myself up for some stupid thing I said in eighth grade.
What kind of cereal?
- Captain Crunch.
- Oh my God! I think we’re twins!
I don’t know. This whole “Oops! I’m pregnant! ” thing still sounds kind of suspicious to me.
I’m just surprised he married her.
But if Nate’s happy, that’s all I care about.
So are you still mad about this morning? I’m really sorry I missed therapy.
No, I was happy you weren’t there. Frank was, too.
Frank loves me!
Yeah, but he thinks you’ve got a lot of work to do on yourself.
That’s so not true!
I mean, maybe it’s true, but he’d never say that.
So did you talk about me the whole time?
After we both decided that you were a hopeless, passive- aggressive guilt sponge,
we decided to move on to more important things.
God, I’m never gonna miss therapy again!
You bet you won’t, bitch!
Well, hello.
Hey, Dave, how are you? Good to see you.
Keith, good to see you.
Lisa used to burn the fuck out of everything until I discovered the miracle of low even heat.
The secret is mesquite wood chips. Gotta use mesquite.
No, man, that’s just a gimmick. It’s the marinade that makes all the difference.
I just like wearing the apron.
where’d you put her blue blankie?
It took forever to put her down, and you know she can’t sleep without it.
- I didn’t put it anywhere.
- I couldn’t find it.
Well, did you give her Mr. Fat Fanny? She likes him.
He’s in her sweet little hands.
Alright.
I think we’re ready.
Good. Let me go wash up. Where’s your little boy’s room?
The…bathroom is in the back, behind the kitchen.
But don’t flush the toilet. We don’t want to wake Maya.
So, how’s the choir going?
Well, it’s not a choir, it’s a chorus, but it’s going well.
Great! I can’t wait to hear you!
Oh, no eggplant for me.
Uh—I’ll–I’ll take his.
- Mozzarella?
- Yes
- Great.
- I'll go.
- What’d I miss?
- You woke the baby.
- It wasn’t asleep.
- Yes, it was.
It wasn’t. It looked at me when I walked in.
Damn, I told him not to flush.
Well, maybe he had to flush. David said he had that irritable bowel thing.
- Why’d you tell him that?
- It just came up.
Well, please, don’t discuss my private stuff with anyone.
- I’m sorry.
- We’re never gonna get her back to sleep.
And, by the way, I only peed.
You shouldn’t have flushed.
It WASN’T asleep!
Maya, row the boat ashore
Hallelujah
My brother and sisters are all aboard…
That song has never sounded so creepy before.
I know.
You’ve gotta be kidding me. What’s he doing here?
Hey, it wasn’t my idea.
Oooh, look at you in your fancy fucking suit.
I knew I never should have hired you.
No, what you shouldn’t have done is fired me.
You were a fuck- up!
Jesus, could you have made the hole a little bigger?
Why can’t you guys shoot yourself in the heart once in a while?
Maybe I was trying to make a statement.
Besides, it’s not really my problem.
Oh, yeah. Nothing’s your problem.
Blow me, dead man!
- He had a wife and kids, asshole.
- Lucky him! I didn’t have shit!
So whose fault is that? You couldn’t even show up to work on time!
Maybe if you hadn’t been such a goddamn prick!
You know, it’s because of people like you that I had to do this!
What are you saying? This is my fault?
I’m just saying…a guy can only take so much before he snaps.
Hey, hey, you know, we all have to deal with a lot of shit, all right?
But when I snap, I throw something,
or I punch a wall. I don’t pick up a shotgun and start killing people.
Yeah. So far.
God, it feels so good to sit here and do absolutely nothing.
We relax all the time. We have to.
So, how do you like your new job, Keith?
Uh, well…it pretty much sucks.
It’s temporary. We’re both going through a lot of changes right now.
All good, though.
So, how’s the therapy going?
Um, good. We’re not fighting so much.
I mean, we never really fought that much, but… we’re getting along much better.
Nate and I never fight.
Never?
No.
You two have never had a fight?
Not really.
I don’t know how you do it.
We’ve known each other for so long, I guess we just understand each other.
Even so, I would think having a baby adds so much stress.
No, actually, having a baby helps put everything in perspective.
You’ll see when you have kids.
If we have kids.
Knock knock! Oh, look, a party!
Hello, I’m Carol, Lisa’s boss.
- Keith.
- I’m David…Fisher.
This is my house.
Well, you’re back early.
There’s nothing to do in the mountains! Nothing!
I mean, like fresh air’s such a big deal?
- At least no one parks in my driveway there.
- Oh, should we move?
Lisa, I would love some cinnamon toast and a cup of tea.
Could you wait just a little bit?
You would not believe the day I’ve had! Who is my most bitter enemy…
…the one person I hate most in the world?
We’re having a little get- together…
Melissa Gilbert.
And who opens the door at Mark and Pam’s house?
That’s right, Melissa Gilbert!
It was like staring at evil itself.
Carol, you’re not listening to me.
Honey, I heard you. You’re having a party.
They’ve had you all day, I need you right now.
Bring my toast up to my bath and I’ll tell you how I made Melissa cry!
Go ahead, we’re fine.
Man, can you believe Lisa?
I’ve never met anyone who’s self- perception is so far removed from reality.
Keith—what were you talking about in there? If we have kids?
Just what I said. If we have kids.
I thought we decided a long time ago that we’d have kids. When did this change?
Who are you kidding? We’re in therapy now to see if we can even exist as a couple.
Everything about us is if.
But that shouldn’t change our goals.
I’m just being realistic.
I don’t want to put myself into a situation where I end up turning into my father.
I guess maybe I’m a little more optimistic about our future than you are.
Oh, get real! You and I living day- to- day, and you know it!
Oh, God, I’m freezing! Oh, God, this sucks!
I’m dying!
It’ll pass.
Give me a Klonopine!
You wanted to do this natural! I already gave you the Kava- Kava and the Valerian root.
They’re not doing shit…give me a Klonopine!
She’s impossible!
- Now give me an ambient.
- Sarah, really—
Well, it’ll put her to sleep.
Anything to shut you up!
- Now I’m burning up!
- A moment ago, you were freezing!
Well, now I’m burning up.
- Now what?
- Diarrhea!
This is what playing with drugs will get you! It’s not pretty, is it?
You get Carol all tucked in?
After eight slices of cinnamon toast and a popsicle!
- It was nice seeing David and Keith tonight.
- Yeah.
I feel so sorry for them.
Yeah, how come?
I mean, God, they’ve been together such a short time, and already they need counseling?
Well, they’re just—
If they have so many problems, why even stay together?
It’s not like they have a kid to take care of.
I don’t know. Maybe they love each other.
What?
What detergent did you use?
I don’t know. Whatever was there.
It smells like Tide.
So I guess I used the Tide.
You have to use the Dreft. Maya gets a rash from anything else.
Those aren’t Maya’s clothes. They’re ours.
Yeah, but I hold Maya all day long.
So why do we even have Tide?
I’m sorry I wasn’t following you around taking notes!
Nate, don’t get mad. I just thought you knew to use the Dreft.
Well, obviously I didn’t. Now I do. Are we okay here?
Yeah, we’re okay. I just have to wash it all over.
No, no, you don’t.
Here, put those down. Here. I’ll do it.
Thank you.
Good afternoon.
- Is he…?
- He’s right in there.
Mr. and Mrs. Showalter, I will be here the entire time.
Please let me know if there’s anything at all I can do for you.
Is that another son?
- Well, I hope you frisked him.
- Please try to show a little sensitivity.
I did my job. I cleaned him up all nice.
Sure, I was tempted maybe to leave a hand or a foot unembalmed,
so he could stink like he should, but no.
- I’m a professional.
- Then act like one
These people loved this man.
They didn’t know him as a murderer. They knew him as their son.
As their brother.
These are the people who are responsible for him.
They should have known what was going on inside of him.
Jesus Christ, Federico! I’m really getting sick of all this moral superiority!
Everything is so goddamn black and white for you.
You know what? I just think—
You can’t ever really know a person. If you think you can, you’re living in a fucking dream world.
I made egg salad.
Jolts of electricity are shooting through my body and tearing me apart.
Then Bettina and I will eat.
Maybe I’ll have a little.
So, how long have you been taking the Vicodin?
I don’t know.
On and off for years.
Why?
Because, somewhere along the line, I started to realize
I was no longer the youngest or prettiest girl in the room.
For a while I satisfied myself
with being the most intriguing…
but eventually I just became the one in paisley. It’s too fucking depressing.
It’s too fucking depressing.
I’m sorry, dear, but you know you’re much more than that.
Yeah, you’re a drug addict!
I need to spice this up a little.
Tell me what you want, and I’ll get it.
- No, no, no, I’ll get...
- Sit down
- I need spices!
- Where is it?
- In the kitchen.
- Where is the Vicodin?
I don’t know what you’re talking—
We already found your stash in the laundry room and in the bookcase. Where else?
- In the spice rack?
- You’re being ridiculous.
- Let me go!
- Where’s the Vicodin?
- You’re hurting me!
- Where?
In the coriander jar, you pigfucker!
Your lies aren’t helping, dear.
Here. Ruth and I are gonna go
outside and get some air.
What—what are you doing?
You don’t think I’m just gonna leave you?
You can’t tie me up!
It’s for your own good.
Do you want me to break this arm?
because i will
Yeah, that should hold.
I hope the coyotes eat you!
So do I!
I don’t know how you remain so calm.
I took a Vicodin!
- Not really?
- Yeah
I figured, if there was ever a time…
You want one?
Oh, no, thank you.
Well, maybe half.
HELLPPPP!!!
- I think there’s some meatloaf in here.
- Yeah, okay
- You’re…Phil, right? The crematory guy?
- Yeah, hey, Nate?
- What?
- Nothing.
Mom called. She’s spending another night at Aunt Sarah’s.
Cool. We can just stay here, then.
Sure.
Also, there’s a couple of death certificates you can pick up tomorrow.
- Where?
- one’s at a nursing home,
and the other, I think…is also at a nursing home.
I hate those places! All the old people want to touch my hair.
Hey, Lis.
No, I’ll probably just grab a sandwich here.
I’ll probably be leaving in about an hour or so. I’ve still got a bunch of shit to do.
I love you, too. Give Maya a kiss for me.
Bye.
- So, Nate’s the one who just got married?
- Yeah
Do you like his wife?
I don’t really know her that well. But, I mean, I like her.
You should’ve met his last girlfriend.
She was “Charlotte: Light and Dark”.
Not for real? The barking girl?
For real.
- You want another?
- No, I’m good.
So, we should do something, like next Friday or Saturday.
Do you have a really busy week?
I don’t know.
Because, when you say “next Friday or Saturday, ” that kind of sounds like not until next Friday or Saturday.
Have you been thinking the two of us are, well, you know, exclusive?
Because I never really meant to give that impression.
- What do you mean?
- Well...
that sometimes I see other women.
And by “see, ” you mean “fuck. ”
However you wanna put it.
Yeah, I mean, I figured…
Until you really get to know someone, I just… seems the way to go.
Yeah, of course.
You see other guys, don’t you?
You’re always talking about Russell.
Russell’s gay.
But…I guess, if I was to meet someone…not that I’m looking to fuck around, but…
I guess if I liked someone, whatever…
Cool.
Are you mad?
Do you want me to go?
No.
Do you want to go up to your room?
Yeah, let’s go.
Baby, I’m warning you…I’m in a bad mood! I had a very bad day!
I just found out that one of my favorite doctors was arrested for selling steroids.
And, oh, now there’s a rumor flying around that AmeriMed’s gonna close the hospital.
- That’s great.
- There’s KFC in the microwave.
I’m sorry, I just had to get you out from under my feet for a while.
Julio, could you please turn that damn thing down?
Are you going to the store tomorrow?
I wasn’t planning on it.
What do you need?
Baby wipes. And baby food. But you have to go to Whole Foods for that.
All right.
But if you go to Rite Aid, you can get her a new sippy cup, and I lost her nail clippers.
Make sure you get them in the baby section. The others are too big.
toilet paper, light bulbs, the energy efficient ones, and...
...facial scrub for me, y’know? The peach kind.
All right. You’re gonna have to write everything down.
It’s on the refrigerator.
All right. I’ll try to do it on my way home from work.
You’re going to try, or you’ll do it?
Only because if you can’t, then I’ll do it.
I’ll do it.
- Thank you.
- You’re welcome.
I had to make carrot soup for Carol’s stylist today and drive it out to her in Culver City.
You know that woman has been sent to earth for the sole purpose of torturing you, right?
- God, it’s true!
- I don’t even work for her, and she drives me crazy!
She wants me to make her rice pudding tomorrow. I think I’ll use whole milk.
It gives her diarrhea.
You know, we could call all our friends and have them park in her driveway.
We could take pictures of her swimming naked and post them on the Internet!
Oh my God, I saw her once! She has the biggest bush I have ever seen in my life!
She really does!
If I told you something, would you promise not to laugh?
No.
This is the first time I’ve ever been in a hammock.
They’ve always scared me.
I always saw them in cartoons,
and the people would get in them and spin around so fast that people would go flying!
Well, don’t worry. You’re safe.
It’s so peaceful out here.
- You want some more wine?
- Sure. Why not?
I’M DYING!!!!!
- Take a slug right out of the bottle.
- Really?
Go on!
I feel like an old hobo.
Maybe we should hop a freight train.
We could head up to Frisco!
Pick us up a couple of sailors!
We’re so bad!
Yes, we are!
Sync: YOUYOUP
www.forom.com