Fuck, we’re bleeding!
Great, now I’ve got brain coming out of the wound.
Raise his head and give him a hundred grams of Mannitol.
Let’s put him in burst suppression. What’s his blood pressure?
117 over 72.
Are we maintaining cerebral perfusion?
Core body temperature is 34. 5.
117 over 72.
Are we maintaining cerebral perfusion?
Core body temperature is 34. 5.
We loaded him with Dilantin and Decadron.
Fuck!
Fuck! Julie, I need two frasers and some aneurysm clips.
Aneurysm clips. I’ve gotta stop all this bleeding.
Fuck! Julie…And I’ll need lots of gel foam and cottonoids…
We’ve gotta stop all this bleeding
Are we going to do a ventriculostomy?
Absolutely. Gel foam and cottonoids.
Let the C- T scanners know we’ll be coming in after surgery.
If we make it that far.
That shit smells awful.
It’s fenugreek.
Fenugreek? What the fuck is fenugreek?
Want to try some? It’s delicious.
No thanks.
Here, put a little maple syrup on it.
Mmmm!
Would you hurry up? I don’t wanna be late for my funeral.
Relax, you’ve got plenty of time. Hell, you’ve got nothing but time!
Which doesn’t exist anyway, so
You don’t know what you’re missing!
Goddamnit, David, I told you I wanted to be cremated.
Come on, Nate, you can do this.
You can do this.
Cat.
Tac.
No, reverse it.
Cat.
Cac.
Almost. Cat. Cat.
Let’s try another one.
Duck.
Huck.
Close.
Goat.
Let’s take a break.
She’s definitely got your nose. And your eyes.
Look at that face. Look at this little person we created.
I love it when she does that.
When she sort of jerks right before she falls off to sleep, and then wakes herself up.
You freaked out the first time she ever did it.
I remember that feeling of falling, when I was little,
like I was falling out of bed, and it always woke me up.
Like I was scared of what I was going to fall into.
But...that never happens to me anymore.
God. We lose so much, ya know?
Oh, great!
Oh, great, he’s got the hiccups again!
So shake him and scream in his face!
What? The world is a hostile and terrifying place. He needs to learn that.
If your mother starts talking about what a gassy baby you were and him getting that from you again, I will scream.
I’ll start farting.
Thank God we got high before we came!
Call me crazy, buddy boy, but I don’t think it makes a damned bit of difference who won.
They’re all crooks anyway.
How can you not care?
I mean, what about that bullshit acceptance speech
Language!
he gave a couple of weeks ago
when he said, “I was not elected to serve one party but one nation, ”
yeah, the operative words there being “NOT elected”!
You want the end piece?
I don’t eat red meat.
Nate, I made you a chicken breast!
Nate, if you didn’t want to see George Bush in the White House,
then you shouldn’t have voted for Ralph Nader.
I’m sorry I’m late. The traffic was like severely ridiculous.
Ruth
Merry Christmas
Claire, you don’t look well.
I think I may be coming down with a cold.
Oh, dear! Let me feel your forehead.
It’s okay, Mom. People get colds.
Okay, who wants the end piece?
Nate?
Sure, I’ll take it.
Everyone, save some room for dessert!
Mother, are you trying to sabotage my diet?
Of course, not, Trisha.
I fully support your commitment to hating yourself for not having the ass of a 10 year old boy!
Why do you always have to be so crude?
Because God is punishing you through me.
Fisher Funeral Chapel, Nate Fisher speaking.
I’m so terribly sorry. Yes, we are open today. Ah, any time before eleven?
Just once, I wish we could make it through Christmas dinner without somebody dying.
We’ll be waiting for you. Heart attack.
Thank God for small favors.
Aw, shit, I’ve seen this one before!
That was Dr. Schroedinger. Kitty, didn’t make it…
What’re we watchin’ this for?
‘Cause it’s what’s on. Quit flappin’ yer trap. I like this show.
the universe is splitting two
Two? Try two billion!
What’s gonna happen to us?
There, there.
We always end up a universe in which we exist. Remember Copenhagen?
Ah, yes! The Eigenvalues in bloom!
You just keep telling yourself everything that can happen, does…somewhere.
Aw, shit, I’ve seen this one before!
you want tell me what is going on?
I just need you to answer a few questions for me.
Do you believe that your consciousness affects the behavior of subatomic particles?
Am I alive or am I dead?
Do you believe that particles move backwards and forwards
in time and appear in all possible places at once?
And if I am dead, is this heaven or hell?
Do you believe that the universe is constantly splitting into billions of parallel universes?
WHAT THE FUCK DO I CARE?
You only get one choice, so you may want to think about this.
Just tell me. Am I dead? Yes. Or No.
Yes.
And no.
Some places you’re dead, some places you’re alive. Some places you never even existed.
Possibly, theoretically. Or who knows, this could just be the anesthesia talking.
Go ahead. Open the box.
Fuck it.
No, I never actually flat- lined.
I just woke up, and later they told me the AVM ruptured during surgery.
So, what does that mean, ruptured?
Well, it just, ya know, exploded. My head actually exploded.
I should’ve died or had some kind of lasting brain damage,
but I pulled through and 7 months later, nothing even shows up on an MRI.
Wow, you’re really lucky!
I’m so fuckin’ lucky.
So fuckin’ lucky.
Right?
Oh, that is so beautiful!
His doesn’t have the inlay.
Where did you get this?
My boss, Carol, had to have a lot of jewelry made for this King Arthur cable movie.
She turned us onto the Todd who did it.
I still can’t believe how fast you two got married.
It wasn’t that fast. We’ve actually been together 8 years,
ya know, on and off, between here and Seattle.
Well, you look really happy.
I am really happy!
Good.
So, my sister- in- law’s an astrologist
And a drunk!
And she was telling me about this whole weird thing that her profession is facing right now.
Wait, when did astrology become a profession?
You know, with the whole possibility of interplanetary travel
This pasta salad is so good! I want to spend a weekend alone with it!
Honey, that makes me feel a little weird.
Okay, so, say in your chart, your Mars is in Scorpio.
Well, what about when people who are actually born on Mars?
Their Mars isn’t in anything, but their Earth is in, I don’t know, Virgo or whatever.
Honey? No one’s listening.
Oh, I know. I’m even boring myself.
Oh, Lisa, I made some pasta salad without the tuna in it for you.
No, it’s okay. I’m nursing. I need the protein.
Spencer, put the kitty down!
So the whole breast- feeding thing is going better now?
Yeah. I’m taking fenugreek.
Fenugreek.
Oh, I’ve heard of that. Have I heard of that?
It’s amazing! Nursing was so painful for me at first,
and my milk production seemed like it would never catch up with her demand…
Put the kitty down.
But now there’s always enough. The only draw back is my sweat smells a little like maple syrup.
Thank you!
You know, breasts are actually modified sweat glands,
and I hardly ever sweat, which is maybe why it was so painful for me at first.
I wish I got one of those elliptical ones. They’re supposed to be better for your knees.
But I’m sure I wouldn’t be using that one either, so
Hey, Todd, thanks for having us.
You’re taking off so soon?
Yeah, I gotta work tonight.
You want a hit for the road?
No, I better not.
Alright. Hey, I think I might know somebody who wants to buy your motorcycle.
Somebody already bought it.
Oh. Oh, well.
Yeah.
Alright, thanks again. I’ll see ya next time.
Alright, later.
Bye!
That was fun.
Yeah, I like them.
She’s nice, he’s a little weird.
Food was good.
Nate.
What?
We totally grabbed the wrong bag!
Oh, shit.
Keys.
Okay, be right back.
I feel…judged. I feel criticized.
I feel like nothing I do is ever good enough. I feel ashamed of who I am.
I feel like I’ll never be the person you want me to be.
I don’t want you to be anyone except who you are.
Keith, now is about you listening. You’ll get your chance in a moment.
Yeah, okay.
I feel like I’m living in a minefield, sometimes. Your anger is so random and arbitrary.
Let’s try to avoid making judgments about Keith’s behavior right now
and really stay focused on what you feel.
I’m afraid of pissing you off, so...
I’m constantly editing myself.
I guess I’m just confused, like I don’t even know who I am anymore.
I’m done
Now, Keith, what did you hear?
A lot of whining!
Perhaps you have some feelings of your own you’d like to share?
Yeah. I hate my job. I feel like a fucking loser,
driving around in a Home Alert uniform, answering alarms set off by poodles
and sucking up to rich assholes who make more in a day than I make in a year! ,
I ought to be able to blow off some steam when I come home without you always taking it so personally
because it’s very rarely about you!
David.
I don’t think that’s fair.
You don’t want me to have any feelings!
No, I’d just like to have a little fun now and then, like we used to.
We don’t have fun?
Rarely.
Rarely?
On occasion.
How’s your sex life?
It’s kinda great.
Yeah, that part works.
So, it seems engaging passionately is comfortable in that arena,
but not so in other areas. What other things do the two of you like to do together?
Um, we go to movies sometimes. We go to dinner.
We used to play racquetball.
He was so much better than me, it was a joke. I wasn’t challenging enough for him.
I never said that!
It made me feel inadequate.
What kinds of things do you do on your own?
Besides work? Work out.
Yeah. My job kind of keeps me from doing much else.
Friends?
Most of my friends were cops.
But I don’t see them anymore since I left the force.
David never really had any close friends.
That’s not true.
There’s a group of independent funeral directors I get together with every month.
You hate those guys!
We’re out of time.
This week, should any conflicts arise, try to focus on expressing
what you’re feeling instead of criticizing and blaming.
Yeah.
Okay?
Change.
Good, Russell.
Fuck, it’s almost five. Rico’s gonna have my head.
Mom!
Hello! How is my precious girl doing today?
She has the hiccups again.
:…got the hiccups again.
She gets that from her daddy. He was a very gassy baby,
wasn’t he? Yes, he was!
I’ll get her some gripe water.
Do you remember to burp her often, dear, when she’s nursing?
Of course.
What’s wrong with you?
I don’t know. I think I just had the weirdest déjà vu.
Hello! Every time I pop by, there are more people here.
Hi, I’m Carol Ward, Lisa’s boss.
I’m Ruth Fisher, Nate’s mother. We’ve met several times already.
You’re not living here now too, are you?
I’m kidding! Calm down.
I hate to keep harping on this.
I parked in the driveway again.
Well, there are two cars today!
I’m sorry. I didn’t know.
Please, it’s no biggie. I’m sure you didn’t know.
What’s your excuse?
Well, I was just dropping off
I could get a little sign made up, ya know?
Nate, back it up, put it on the street!
I’m kidding!
Look, if you want me to move it, I’ll go move it right now.
Don’t be silly, whenever, it doesn’t matter.
Sooner rather than later.
Oh, Lisa, I’m having dinner with Penny Marshall tonight, so I won’t need you to cook.
Okay.
But, I’m going to host an impromptu gathering tomorrow evening, just some close friends
I want to try out a new pitch on, shouldn’t be more than…30.
Okay.
Do you have time to go over the menu with me?
Now?
Yes!
Take your time, dear. I’ve got all afternoon.
Oh, nice to meet you, Nate’s mother!
She’s energetic.
She’s a lunatic.
Hey, Rico.
Nate, hey, how’s it going?
Good.
Good, good, I’m glad to hear it.
Listen, I don’t know if you’re aware of this,
or if you even care,
but we have two viewings tonight.
One at 6:30 and one at 8:00.
Yeah, I’m on my way.
Good, because your brother is nowhere to be found.
Yeah, and he’s not answering his cell phone.
And there’s only so much I can do, ya know?
Sure.
I can’t be at two places at the same time, Nate!
I get it, Rico, okay? Lay off the lecturing. I’m not your kid!
Yeah, well, I’m not your employee. I’m your partner.
I am a licensed funeral director now, okay?
You guys took my money, you made me a partner.
It’s time you started treating me like one. Goodbye.
So, Claire, how’s art school?
It’s okay.
What kind of stuff are you doing?
Well, yesterday, we had to draw this naked guy in like 30 seconds.
Well, that sounds fun.
Not really. It’s hard.
And, like, I don’t even want to be an illustrator or a painter or whatever,
but they keep saying that we need to know how to do everything, like Picasso.
It’s intense.
Yeah, but, at least you get to be creative every day.
Good morning!
Hey!
Hey, pumpkin!
Hey, how’s it going?
It could not possibly be going any better.
Would you look at this little girl? Is that the face of God, or what, huh?
Yeah, there’s some stuff coming out of God’s nose.
Who’s precious? Is it you? Yes, it is!
Hey, Mom, can you help me with her today?
Lisa’s gotta help Carol.
Carol’s having this big Hollywood asslick dinner, and Lisa gotta shop.
Of course.
You guys, she took the most amazing poop this morning.
Who, Lisa?
Seriously, it was just so perfectly formed, so healthy and compact.
It was like a regular adult poop! It made me so happy.
Look, I swear, when you live with a baby, you get to see the world as being totally new all over again.
They’re just so pure and uncorrupted.
It’s a fuckin’ privilege.
And how come neither of you has been over to visit her recently?
Because being a father has turned you into a dithering idiot.
Wow. You’re so tough and cool and above it all. I wish I was you.
Does anybody want the end piece?
Who wants the end piece?
Oh, Nate, could you drop Mrs. Folger at the crematory this afternoon?
No, I’ve got the Paulk funeral.
Yeah? Well, I’ve got the Bennett funeral.
Can’t Rico do it?
I believe his exact words were, “No fucking way.
I’m not your fucking go- fer any more.
Claire, can you give us a hand?
Sorry, I have homework.
We’ll pay you fifty bucks.
We’d pay a delivery service more than that.
All right.
As long as I don’t have to touch any dead skin.
No, she’s all boxed up.
And I can’t do it till around four, ‘cause I have to practice drawing a perfect circle.
That takes seven hours?
I have to be able to do it on command in class tomorrow, okay? It’s not as easy as it sounds.
Eeww. Is that the box that needs to go to the crematory?
The-- ? Uh, yeah.
Well, I can take it now.
You’re taking it?
Yeah, they hired me to do runs, since nobody else wants to do it.
Really?
Yeah, for 50 bucks a shot.
But you’re gonna need to help me get that into my car.
So, what kind of music do you guys play?
I don’t know. It’s kinda like early Peter Gabriel meets Tool.
Emotionally vulnerable like Sunny Day Real Estate,
but politically conscious, like Public Enemy.
We’re still working it out.
When you guys play, you should let me know. I’ll come.
Why don’t you hang out, while we practice?
I don’t think I can.
I’ve got this thing I’m supposed to
Okay.
I'm Phil.
I’m Claire.
You want a beer?
Sure.
You really amaze me, Lisa.
Why?
Your energy, it’s boundless. You should be bottled as an alternative energy source.
You would save the world, I’m serious.
Well, that’s kinda funny, because I feel tired all the time.
Really?
Yeah. I think it just comes from being a mom, ya know?
Yeah.
Not that I’m complaining.
I mean, Maya has totally transformed my life.
I can’t even imagine going back to the way things were before.
Wow.
I mean, so what if I have to work extra hard?
I want to. It’s worth, it is so worth it.
Carol?
No, don’t pay any attention to me.
I’m just nervous…nervous about this meeting next week.
I have to pitch to McG, in person! Whoa, is he intimidating!
Can I make you some chamomile tea?
Oh, for Chrissake, I’m not your grandmother, okay? I’m your boss.
Stop looking at me, Lisa!
Carol, I’m always here for you.
Eh!
Also, I swim laps in the morning, and I used to be able to do that naked,
which was a great way to start the day, like I was Artemis.
I would go out there feeling like a warrior, like a huntress,
which is what you have to do when you’re in my business.
But now I can’t do that anymore, because there’s a man living here!
I’m sure Nate wouldn’t mind
I would!
Also, I don’t appreciate the hostility he shows by always parking in the driveway!
I’m sorry. I—I will talk to him about it.
Yeah. I’m gonna go swim laps.
Are you ready for the bok choi?
Yeah.
What are you doing?
Adding pepper.
I already added pepper.
Oh.
Okay, I feel shamed.
What?
When you said, “I already I added pepper, ”
my perception was that you were irritated with me for not knowing that already,
and that you were also angry with me, that I shouldn’t have done it.
Why would I be angry with you?
I don’t know. Maybe you don’t want me to be involved in the cooking process.
Maybe you just want me to prepare the ingredients for you?
Maybe you want total control over what actually happens inside the wok.
So, we have a little extra pepper in the wok. It’s not a big deal!
I know it’s not a big deal.
Okay, I heard what you said.
It was not my intention to shame you.
I know.
Good. I love you. Are the carrots ready?
Yeah.
You know, I grew up in a family where people expressed their anger on a regular basis,
so that’s what intimacy feels like to me.
But you, you grew up in a family where no one ever expressed anything.
Yeah, we also never hit each other.
So whenever I’m slightly irritated, it scares you, right?
Right.
It just means I’m comfortable with you.
It doesn’t mean I don’t love you.
Did you pick up the dry cleaning today?
Yeah, it’s in the closet.
There, isn’t that delicious?
Your daddy, he used to love peanut butter, too, yes, he did!
So did your uncle David. Not your aunt Claire, though.
She absolutely hated it. Always did, still does.
Isn’t it funny? They were all little babies once, too.
But their daddy’s mommy never liked spending time with them
the way I like spending time with you.
She never really liked me, and she never liked my children.
She was convinced I had gotten pregnant on purpose
to trap Nathaniel into marrying me, which wasn’t true at all.
I certainly never intended for that to happen.
Especially when I was so young.
And I was terrified when your daddy was born, absolutely terrified.
Hey, Mom!
Goodness, you startled me!
She give you any trouble?
Heavens, no, she’s an angel.
Are you ready to go home, angel?
Have you eaten? I made you a chicken breast.
Uh, no, thanks. I’ve gotta be getting home.
But put it in the fridge. I’ll eat it tomorrow.
You know, if you and Lisa would like a night off, I’d be happy to watch her.
You could go out to eat, see a movie. I could even keep her here overnight.
Well, thanks, Mom,
but Lisa’s working tonight, and plus Maya hasn’t slept outside the family bed yet, so
Well, maybe it might be better for her to try a night sleeping on her own.
Mom, we know how you feel about it. You’re very clear on that.
We feel differently, okay?
She’s almost nine months old. She’s going to have to leave the family bedsometime.
Well, Maya will let us know when she’s ready to leave, all right? Good night.
Good night, Grandma.
Good night.
Are we having sex?
Uh, okay. Just let me take a shower first.
Morning.
What time is it?
A little before 10, I think.
How do you take it?
Black.
Hey.
So, what do you have to do today?
Uh, class.
What kind of class?
A drawing class. We’re learning how to draw a perfect circle.
That sounds kinda cool.
It’s not. It’s stupid and tedious and pointless.
I went to art school to be expressive, not to perform some pointless task like some lab rat.
You wanna play hooky?
Yes.
Nate, I need you to do me a big favor
and cover the Folger funeral for me this afternoon.
Hey, who’s Frank Muehler?
Frank who?
Muehler. He’s in the date book here every Wednesday at 2.
I have absolutely no idea.
It must be somebody Rico put in there.
Hmm. There’s a phone number. I’m gonna call and find out.
All right, no.
Keith and I are in couples counseling.
Really?
It’s not that big a deal.
Are you guys okay?
Yeah, of course we’re okay.
We’re just seeking the advice of a trained professional to help us
to establish appropriate boundaries and write the rules of our relationship together.
What happened?
Nothing happened.
Keith has a lot of anger issues that he inherited from his father,
and I have a lot of doormat issues that I inherited from Mom.
Can we please never talk about this again?
Sure. You’re okay, though, right?
Got it.
And how are you and Lisa?
Uh…we’re great. It’s still a little bizarre to me.
All the possible ways my life could’ve gone, ya know?
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, it’s just about a year ago I got engaged.
Remember that?
You know, I thought I loved Brenda,
or maybe I thought I could just make it work out of sheer will.
But, you just never know.
You have no fucking idea what life has in store for you.
So, can you cover the Folger funeral for me or not?
What is it, you just need some time off? Are you sure you’re alright?
I’m fine.
I’ve got an audition for the Gay Men’s Chorus of Los Angeles.
What?
That sounds fun.
I’m trying to create something for myself outside of my job and my relationship.
I could really use your support on this.
All right. Don’t worry. The Folger thing’s a walk in the park.
You just go knock ‘em dead. No pun intended.
I’m so nervous.
David. You’ll be great.
>From your mouth to God’s ears.
Right.
Thanks, Nate.
Any time.
Hello?
Hi, Ruth, it’s Lisa.
Oh, hello.
Ruth, did you give Maya peanut butter?
Yes, and she just loved it! Now, Nate--
Ruth, you never give babies peanut butter under the age of one.
They can develop horrible allergies! Didn’t you know that?
No, I didn’t. Is she all right?
Yes, but that’s not the point. You should never give her peanut butter
…or honey…or strawberries…or egg whites. Please.
Of course.
I’m sorry to be so abrupt with you. I just—
No, I’m sorry. I had no idea.
Peanut butter was never a problem when my children were young.
Are you sure she’s all right?
She’s fine.
Do you need any help with her today? I could come over.
Ruth, no. You spend so much time over here. I feel bad.
It’s no problem at all. I like—
Seriously, take some time for yourself.
I hardly saw Maya at all yesterday.
I really just wanted it to be the two of us today.
Okay.
But thanks. I’ll talk to you later.
Thank God! It’s very frightening! I didn’t know who to call!
Ma’am, just calm down and tell me what happened, okay?
Come, I’ll show you.
Where has the time all gone to?
Haven’t done half the things we want to
Oh, well, we’ll catch up some other time…
This day was just a token
Too many words are still unspoken
Oh, well, we’ll catch up some other time.
Just when the fun is starting
Comes the time for parting
But let’s be glad for what we’ve had
And what’s to come.
There’s so much more embracing
Still to be done, but time is racing…
Oh, well. We’ll catch up some other time.
It’s just always weird when you find stuff like that out.
You know, later on in your life.
I mean, I had no idea that I wasn’t planned.
I’m not sure what difference it makes.
I mean, Maya wasn’t planned either.
We couldn’t love her any more than we do.
Yeah.
It’s just…
I don’t know.
What?
I don’t like knowing that my whole existence is any accident.
It’s just too fucking…random.
Yeah, but that’s the way it happened.
Things happen the way they’re meant to, Nate.
See, there’s a kind of fatalism in that that I just don’t buy.
Well, what’s the alternative?
We make choices.
Yeah, but maybe your parents never would have chosen to get married
if you hadn’t happened, and then not only would you not exist,
but Claire and David wouldn’t either.
It’s just not what was meant to happen.
But surely we’re more than just…things that happen.
Maybe we are. Maybe we’re not.
Oh, I love it when she does that!
…when she does that.
When she sort of jerks, ya know?
Right before she falls…
…off to sleep, wakes herself up.
You freaked out the first time…
…she ever did it.
I remember that feeling of falling…
…falling…
…when I was little, like I was falling out of bed,
and it always woke me up, like I was scared of…
…what you were going to fall into?
Yeah. But that never happens to me anymore.
Don’t be so sure of that.
What’s going on with you?
I think I dreamed this.
What?
This moment.
This. This life we have together. You, me, Maya.
Here.
Now.
I hope you enjoy the show. sync by youyoup
www.forom.com