Mr Williman's last statement
may be offensive,
it may contain expletives
or matter of a dark nature.
When Mr Williman expires,
you may hear what is known as a death rattle
or a snort or a cough of some sort.
Some fellas bleed from the nose.
It's not common but it happens.
Or he may just appear to fall off to sleep,
with his eyes either open or closed,
it can go either way.
I'm sorry if this is troublesome to you folks
but if, when this is all over, you tell me,
"Officer Paddick, it happened
just like you said it would,"
then I figure I did my job.
We don't want any surprises.
Any questions?
There's no explanation.
There's no excuse.
I can't lay here and tell you there is one.
But if anybody thinks the state of Texas
is teaching anybody anything
by putting this poison into me,
they're even dumber and crueller than I am.
And you're all gonna cry in the same wet hell
that I'm going to for doing this.
You're gonna eat shit,
you're gonna vomit blood forever.
Because this isn't right.
You're all pigs.
You're all fucking pigs
slipping out of God's ass
and I would cut all your throats if I could.
I hate this motherfucking...
Nate, it's Brenda again.
If you're there, pick up.
You must be at work. OK,
well, if you want me to stop calling,
could you just tell me,
otherwise I'll keep trying. I'm really worried...
...at 89.9. The Greater Palm Springs area
at 89.3.
Oxnard, Ventura, Carpinteria at 89. 1.
Lemon Grove at 89.9...
But we don't want to get the paper every day.
No, it's not about the money.
It's... Look, we don't care
how free you make the paper,
we don't want all that paper in the apartment.
Yes, that sounds a great saving...
We're not interested.
Is there coffee for me, too?
What was that?
I can't stand listening to you
deal with those telemarketers.
You have to be so
damn nice about everything.
- She was just trying to do her job.
- And you're trying to do yours.
This coffee tastes like shit.
- Keith.
- What?
- Can you hear the tone in your voice?
- Don't start again.
- I'm serious.
- There is no tone in my voice.
Yes, there is.
It's same tone you used in San Diego.
- I'm sick of talking about that.
- The same tone...
When are you gonna get it that
you're the one who fucked up in San Diego?
It was my family business.
- I stuck up for you.
- I don't need anybody sticking up for me.
You always turn shit around
and make it about me.
You can't face it that you were out of line.
- Being on your side is out of line?
- If I don't want you on it.
This is the difference between you and me.
I want you on my side, I need you on my side
and it's the one thing that I never have.
- That is not true.
- Everything I do is too weak or too nice.
You don't really like me.
You're not for me.
I look at you and all I think about is
how I can help you be
whatever it is you wanna be
between now and the day you die.
- You look at me and all you see are problems.
- That's not true.
I'm so fucking sick of it.
God! Why should I stand for this?
Why should this constant abuse
be what I call love?
Don't touch me.
Remember, nothing to eat or drink
after midnight tonight.
Have you arranged for a ride?
I was just gonna take a cab, I thought.
You know?
I'd prefer it if a family member takes you home.
Nobody in my family would wanna do that,
I don't think.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
You have a friend who could help you?
No.
Well, we really don't want you to drive yourself.
This has been the longest month
of my whole life.
- I can imagine.
- Yeah? Get this.
I lost my job to go to my father's execution.
Isn't that the most pathetic thing
you've ever heard?
My stupid boss told me
I shouldn't go and I did.
- Where did you work?
- A used-car dealership.
It's OK, I'll get another job. It's just so dumb.
- You did the right thing.
- Now I'm out of a fucking job.
Thank you, right thing.
Work can be difficult
with regards to something like this.
You don't know.
And on top of that, I'm out like $700
because I had to pay to ship his body
back from Texas.
Miss Williman, will you be
wanting a service for your father?
- Or we could just...
- No. I want a service for my dad.
I thought Father Jack talked to you.
- No, he didn't.
- He told me he did.
He did, Rico. He talked to David.
I forgot to tell you.
- He called yesterday from St Bart's.
- That's my church.
I'm sorry, I didn't know.
I don't want the fact
that he killed a bunch of women
to be the only story
anybody ever tells about him.
I mean, he was a kid once.
He had a life. I've seen the pictures.
And he wasn't such a bad dad.
My brother got the shit beat out of him a lot
but he never beat me.
Well, excuse me one moment, Miss Williman.
I'll find the other Mr Fisher
and we'll figure this thing out.
- Thank you.
- OK.
I bet if my dad wasn't a murderer, you'd be
saying all kinds of sweet things to me.
Like how hard this must be for me
and shit like that.
No, I know how hard it is for you.
I'm sorry, I've been having
a hard time myself lately.
Show me what the choices are for the box
while we wait.
OK.
They're little people.
They fall into the pipe here
and they go down through the pipe
and then they break apart
into a bunch of little pieces over here
and then they disappear.
And then slowly,
very slowly, they get put back together
and come out the other side.
So, show me the boxes.
Yeah.
There are a lot of affordable choices
so you don't have to worry,
you don't have to spend a lot.
That's good cos I don't have a lot.
Like almost nothing.
I talked to David.
Everything's been taken care of.
I've made stuffed cabbage rolls.
If anybody wants some for dinner,
they're in the sky-blue Tupperware.
- Thanks.
It's such a beautiful day today.
No.
- Oh, dear.
- What?
- It's one of Lisa's Dr Peppers.
- She doesn't drink Dr Pepper.
Maybe not in front of you.
Put it back in the fridge...
- I can't leave Maya.
- We'll get her after things have cooled down.
Why did I ever get myself into this?
You wanted love and he made you believe
he could give it to you.
That's what Nate does.
You've always known that. He's toxic.
- I should have brought Maya with me.
- Maya's on her own journey, Lisa.
This is about you.
It'd be wonderful
if someone could take her to the park.
Well, I think that's it.
If any of you need me,
I've left the number by the phone.
So, what are you guys doing tomorrow?
Same old shit.
- I'm busy.
- Me, too. Why?
Nothing.
- Where's Mom going?
- George's.
Oh, yeah.
The original title of this famous poem
was He Do The Police In Different Voices.
The Waste Land.
That is a much better title.
Well, we're still a genius, even with one wrong.
I'm dead already.
- Ruth?
- No more questions.
Do you...
move this fast with everybody?
No.
But then I've never met
anybody like you before.
I don't want you to get away.
I'm not going anywhere.
I guess I do feel like the stars
are moving a little faster lately.
Like in those movies
where they speed things up.
And the stars stream across the sky in stripes,
they're moving so fast.
But...
But what?
My daughter-in-law's
been missing for over two weeks,
my granddaughter may be without a mother
for the rest of her life.
I'm just very aware of how important it is
to enjoy what life gives you...
when it gives it to you.
Who knows, George,
you may be my last chance at finding love.
And you may be my last chance to be happy.
You've been happy before.
Not like this.
Russell, stop calling
or I'm gonna change my number.
- You actually hit him?
- Of course not.
I just swotted him away.
See, I don't see why you two
stay together if it's always that bad.
- It's not always that bad.
- But even if it's that bad for a little while...
You know, me and Vanessa,
we've got the kids to think about.
Gay couples have no reason to stay together?
No. I'm saying I don't see how
anybody stays together without kids.
- It was a compliment.
- It doesn't sound like a compliment.
We got something chunky here.
A clot, I don't know.
All gone.
- Hello, comrades.
- Hi, Arthur.
So, this is the gentleman
who murdered all those women.
- Yep.
- Only to be murdered himself
by the state of Texas.
- You're against capital punishment?
- Certainly.
It fails to deter other criminals
and mistakes are often made.
- Innocent people die.
- Innocent people die cos of guys like him.
What did he do anyway?
- He made one woman eat broken glass...
- Don't tell me.
- It's bad enough things like that happen.
- I agree.
- But, Rico...
- If he did something like that to Vanessa,
- I'd happily flip the switch.
- What about the value of human life?
He cashed in the value
of his human life a long time ago.
He's a dorito, crunch them, don't make more.
You get worse.
Nate.
Maya's having a nap,
I'm gonna go for a quick run.
- Who's watching her?
- Claire.
- Who's this?
- It's Mr Williman.
Remember? With the daughter.
So what the fuck are you doing?
He came in here already embalmed.
He looked like a tangerine.
I thought this was a better colour.
I agree.
Oh, God, now what?
Hi.
- Your father's service is tomorrow, right?
- I know.
I wanted to
talk to you about flowers.
Well, we'll take care of that.
It's part of the package.
But, I mean, what kind of flowers do you like
or do you think we should have?
I only asked cos, you know, you're a man.
Well, we have a florist
who does all the arrangements.
It'll be a nice selection and variety.
Nothing pink, don't worry.
OK.
Do you
wanna go get some coffee or something?
I haven't eaten anything yet today.
Thank you, but I'm kinda busy.
Is your wife around?
No, she's not.
I think you should go,
I was just about to go out for a run.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to be sorry.
I don't know where else to go.
I don't have a job,
I just sit around all day and stare at the walls.
It's OK.
Look, I'll see you tomorrow.
It'll look great, don't worry.
- Nothing pink.
- Right, nothing pink.
Thanks.
Get the cordless.
I know. I know what you mean.
Then one day it isn't charged up
and you need it.
This one has more torque.
How much torque
does a guy like me really need?
This one feels good in your hand. Try it.
See what I mean?
I do.
George, I wonder if
we shouldn't just get married.
- Are you serious?
- I am.
- Because I've been thinking the same thing.
- You have?
I don't mind telling you I'm lonely
and I've been lonely for a long time and I...
Ruth, I think...
I think it's a wonderful idea.
- You really do?
- Yes.
I don't want to come to places like this alone.
Neither do I.
- That's what life is, coming to places like this.
- Yes.
- It's awful.
- I know!
So let's get married. What the hey?
I want to, that's what I'm saying.
Me too.
I've been married before,
you should know that.
Of course, you have two grown children.
- More than once.
- How many times?
Six.
- I should have told you before.
- No, I'm glad you didn't.
Get the cordless,
I'll help you make sure it stays charged.
It's a deal.
Excuse me. You didn't happen to see
a dog on the beach?
No, I'm sorry.
Gosh darn it.
- You lost your dog?
- Not me, my wife.
- What does he look like?
- He's a chocolate lab. Wanna see his picture?
No, I didn't see him. I'm sorry.
Good luck.
- What are you doing here?
- I've been calling and calling.
I wanted to know that you're OK.
Well, I'm not.
But there's not a lot we can do about it so...
Thanks anyway.
I'm trying to be your friend.
Sorry, were you there
the night that you kissed me?
Do you know how that makes me feel?
- My wife's gone.
- I know.
I can't imagine
what you must be going through...
You have no concept
of what I've been going through.
I haven't slept in days,
I've been to Gaviota State Beach five times.
I been driving up that fucking PCH
putting up flyers on telephone poles.
Then let me help you.
- Why the fuck would you wanna help me?
- I care about you.
- I can't just turn that off.
- Sure you can, you've done it before.
- Sorry.
- Just give her to me.
- I couldn't get her to sleep.
- Just... Thanks.
Do you think you could give me a ride?
I have to go get an abortion.
Sure.
It's so good you've kept up with your chorus.
It must be a wonderful outlet.
It is. It's...
What?
Well, there are times
when you're in the midst of all these voices,
being carried along, and all you have to do
is get to the end of the song.
For a few minutes, it's that simple.
Just get to the end of the song.
That's kind of a relief.
From the rest of life?
Yes.
I think Lisa's dead.
- I do, too.
- I hate to say it but I do.
I just feel like she's gone.
For a while, I imagined all kinds of things.
Her showing up...
I know.
She was a part of our family.
- Maya's my niece.
- She was such a sweet person,
why should something like that happen to her?
Why is life like that?
Thanks for the tea.
David...
Yeah?
I've been seeing someone.
George, yeah. We've noticed.
It's going pretty well.
- Good. He seems a nice enough guy.
- He is.
I've...
I've been thinking maybe I could think about
even settling down with him.
It would be time, maybe, to try that again.
That depends on what you mean
by settling down.
Well, getting married.
- Don't you think I deserve to be happy?
- Of course.
But you've only known him for a few weeks.
Why do you have to rush into it?
Because.
When I'm with him, life is full of possibilities
and I haven't felt that way in so long,
I've forgotten what it feels like.
- I don't want to forget that again.
- It's your decision,
I just don't wanna see you get hurt, that's all.
- Sushi.
- Like what?
Like spicy tuna or yellowtail,
I don't like it when it gets too baroque.
Like frozen spider roll of the 10,000 secrets?
- Yeah. I don't need that.
- Me neither.
What else do you like?
I don't know.
It has different orchestrations...
Hey, David.
Do you wanna get something?
Lunch or a drink or something?
Yes, please. God, thank you, yes.
Susan, Denise, Pam, Claire.
- See you later.
- I'll be here.
Ms Fisher? Good afternoon.
Dr Simpson.
Before we begin the procedure,
I'm going to do an ultrasound.
You'll feel a little pressure,
it won't be too uncomfortable.
I see you chose Twilight.
I don't know.
- The sedation.
- Oh. Yeah.
That's Twilight.
You're not really gone
but you're not really here.
That sounds good.
You're going to be OK.
- Am I?
- Yes.
We're gonna take good care of you,
don't worry.
OK. OK, you're fine.
- Are you her ride?
- Yeah.
Some instructions.
A bath, no tampons, just Motrin, pads
and get some rest.
You'll feel better by tomorrow.
Thanks.
Mary, Hayley, Bethany, Rosa.
What do you think?
I think it's a wonderful book.
You should be proud.
- "University of Maryland Press."
- My alma mater.
- It really is a different way of seeing things.
- Isn't it?
To me, California has
always been here,
but to you, it's just stopping by.
Yeah.
I'm thinking we should slow down
on the marriage plans.
I don't want anything else to change,
would that be OK with you?
I know I must seem confused.
It's only because I am.
Ruth, I'm here if you want me.
I don't have any other prospects
and I don't want any.
So there's no rush.
Thank you.
- Why isn't there a picture of you?
- I didn't want one.
It's about rocks, not me.
It just feels like it ought to be the end.
I'm so tired of having
the same fight over and over again.
I hear what you're saying.
I'm so bored of this kind of unhappiness.
I think I'm ready for some new unhappiness.
There are all kinds of things I could say but...
Go ahead, say them.
No, I...
What?
Say it.
I want you to know,
more than anything, David,
that I take you and your situation
with Keith really seriously
and if you can be happy with Keith,
I want you to be, you know what I'm saying?
I do.
Thank you.
- Hey, how you feeling?
- A little bit better.
It just feels like really bad cramps.
- You need another pad?
- No.
- Another Motrin?
- No, thanks.
So, what do you think of my new house?
- It's kinda gross, isn't it?
- No, it's cool.
- And it's kinda gross.
- I know. See? I know.
I used to wonder when I'd get there,
to the grown-up place.
Almost got there with Nate.
And then here I am.
- You're still in love with my brother, aren't you?
- No.
No.
Only in the way that I always will be
but not in the way of thinking about him like,
"God, when am I gonna see Nate again?"
you know what I mean?
Yeah, I do.
I am worried about him, though.
I know.
He's so fucked up with Lisa being
wherever she is.
You know what's weird about Lisa?
- What?
- Well, I think she really liked me...
- I'm sure she did.
- She was fucked up, too, don't get me wrong.
Just a different kind of fucked up
from our family.
Like a mostly friendly kind of fucked up.
- You miss her?
- I guess, yeah.
- Sorry if that's...
- No.
It's totally right.
Well, I'm going to make some pasta.
I was just gonna do it with olive oil,
nothing too aggressive.
You want some?
No, I don't think I can ever eat again.
Hey, it's Nate.
- Tell me when you want me to stop.
- I don't want you to stop.
I want you inside me.
No, no, wait.
- I like it like this.
- Yeah.
OK.
- Fuck me.
- You'll wake the baby.
I don't care, you're fucking me so good.
Fuck me. Fuck me till
I can't remember my name.
Just fuck me.
Fuck me.
Who will separate us from the love of Christ?
Will hardship or distress or persecution
or famine or peril of the sword?
No.
In all these things we are more than
conquerors through Him who loves us.
For I am convinced that neither death nor life
nor anything else in all creation
can separate us from the love of God.
Carl Williman was a part
of God's good creation.
Susceptible to sin, yes, but worthy of grace.
May his soul and the souls
of those whose lives he took
find peace in the infinitely
complicated and eternal life of God.
I knew her at St Bart's.
Yeah.
She was pretty fucked up.
Seems like it.
- So I came out of the closet.
- And that was good?
Yeah.
- And I'm in a committed relationship.
- With Keith?
Yeah. That's supposed to be
a good thing, too, right?
That's what I've heard.
So, shouldn't my life be better?
Truth and relationships don't make life better,
they make life possible.
So you think I should stay with Keith?
I think you should do whatever brings you
deeper into the reality of your life.
The reality of my life.
Yes, but not the life you think you can have,
the life you've got.
Hi.
What you doing?
I am just checking things out,
you know, keeping track.
I had a really good time last night.
And I think we should...
I think we should do that again.
I don't think that's such a good idea.
- How come?
- I just don't.
I'm sorry.
Are you serious? You're gonna cry?
I can't help it.
Come on.
Have you seen
what kind of fucking world this is?
You see what people do, what your
fucking father did, now you're gonna cry?
"Fuck me, fuck me, fuck me, fuck me."
You don't get to cry.
Where were you last night?
I was looking for you.
- To watch Maya?
- Yeah.
I was busy. Sorry.
- Can I have these?
- Sure. I don't care.
- That's weird.
- What?
Russell used to say the whole house
smelled like the colour wheel.
- Yeah?
- He liked it here.
Well, somebody should get something out of it.
Nate, maybe you could give Brenda a break.
She's only trying to help.
Things between me and Brenda are
a lot more complicated than you might think.
Yeah, I'm sure I could never imagine.
So what went wrong?
Well, the first one was Susie
and we just got married too young, that's all.
Wasn't anybody's fault.
Number two.
Gloria, yeah, that one was my fault.
I screwed around.
- I know better now.
- You better know better.
Number three.
She was the one I was screwing around with.
Tanya. We were at Rutgers, my first job.
Assistant professor.
She cheated on me all the time.
How do you not see that coming?
Andrea died.
I'm sorry.
Cheryl, that one was only for nine months.
And Doris,
the last one, died.
I'm so sorry.
Well, if you marry six people,
a few of them are gonna die,
that's the odds.
And you're ready to try again?
With you? Of course.
Why? You don't want to?
No, of course I do, George.
I think.
But
you had all these women.
Let me tell you something.
One time,
one time I bought a house,
this was back in Massachusetts
when I was teaching at Amherst,
and the house was built over a stream.
Literally over it.
It had been a mill at one time
and someone had taken the wheels
and grinding stones out
but it was still over the stream.
And after we moved in
I wanted to put a new floor in the kitchen.
So?
So I tore up the old floor,
ripped up the linoleum,
pulled up the plywood.
Then I pulled up one of the original boards.
This 200-year-old pine board.
And there was the stream,
not two feet underneath me.
I'd always known it was there
but there it was.
You know-really.
There it really was.
This live, sparkling water,
flowing right underneath my house.
That's how I feel about you.
What?
Did I say something wrong?
I'm sorry.
You make me miss Nathaniel, though.
It's OK.
I miss a few of mine, too.
He was like, "I'm paying your rent,
I bought you all this shit,
"I expect you to have dinner with me
whenever I want."
And I was like, "No."
Glad we could be here for you.
Yeah, me too.
But you gotta treat my sister better or
she's gonna leave you like I left that Anthony.
She will.
You guys are out of popcorn.
Oh, God.
Overruled it.
Said they'd be too high in carbohydrates...
We have to talk.
What is it? I've had a fucking day from hell.
I don't want us to be together any more.
- You're breaking up with me?
- Yeah. I'm breaking up with you.
- Wait a minute.
- No.
Just give me a few days to find a place
then you can find somebody
more whatever it is you like-mean.
- We should go to therapy and talk about this.
- It's not a discussion.
There's nothing to talk about,
it's never been right between us.
- We can stop wasting each other's time.
- Don't.
Or what? You'll hit me?
- No.
- I'm sick of being scared of you.
I hate it.
I absolutely fucking hate it.
Lise?
Lisa!
Lisa, where are you?
I'm right here.
Where are you?
I don't know.
None of this turned out the way I wanted it to.
You know that, right?
I wanted to love you, I did love you.
And I just felt like we were beginning to...
I know we were, I know it in my heart
and I feel like I had this
once-in-a-lifetime chance and I fucked it up.
Nate, I'm not a chance, I'm a person.