Sous-titres par
la Fisher Team
Transcript:
Raceman
Synchronisation :
EZ, Occeane
Traduction :
Sylvain, Petrushka, Paqui
Relecture et corrections finales :
Guzo
http://www.sixfeetunder-france.com
http://www.forom.com
Saison 5 Episode 9
"Ecotone"
- Sorry.
- I'm going with
- Only family rides along.
- I won't get in the way.
- I can't let him go alone.
- I'll be with him the whole time.
Ma'am, all you can do is follow.
- Nate
- Don't try to keep up.
We'll be running the red lights.
No ! Way I am family !
He's my stepbrother !
You have 45 minutes and $300.
- Go for it.
- You really have to think...
- Just five more minutes. Okay ?
- Okay.
But you have to meet
the needs of the client.
For me, it set off just
a total panic attack.
I am glad this
final challenge is...
an evening gown because I think
That is probably
my true speciality.
- Hey, what's up ?
- David, it's maggie.
- Hi, Maggie.
Nate collapsed at my house.
Nate what ? He what ? Why ?
- I don't know.
- Is he okay ?
I don't know.
He was still passed out.
The paramedics took him. Can
you meet me at the hospital ?
- Which hospital ?
- Saint bridget's.
- David
- I'm on my way.
David, could you call Brenda ?
Yeah.
Tell them AVM.
- Maggie ?
- What happened to Nate ?
Get me the number for Saint
Bridget's
And Dr. Dipaolo.
D-I-P-A-O-L-O.
Everything's going
to be okay, all right ?
- Where the fuck are you ?
- Brenda, it's david.
David, I'm sorry.
- Is nate with you ?
- He's at Saint Bridget's.
- Something happened to him
- What do you mean ? What happened ?
I don't really know any of
the details. I just got a call.
Who called you ?
Why didn't they call me ?
- Can you come ?
- Yeah, I don't understand
Brenda, I'm sorry. I
have to call my mom.
I'll take care of everything
until you get there.
David.
Are you ready yet ?
You're quiet.
am I ? Sorry.
No, it's okay. It's nice
To be quiet with somebody.
Do you like this place ?
Yeah. It's lovely.
But ?
You can tell me.
You're not going
to hurt my feelings.
I just kind of feel like
Nancy Reagan might walk in
And sit at the next table.
Yeah, I think we've stumbled
upon a republican nest.
I believe it's called an enclave.
No no,
Like vampires, a nest.
Here they are, safe in
their fancy restaurant bubble while
that stupid,evil war goes on and on.
- Stupid, Evil, I don't think so.
- Right.
We eliminated a murdering
asshole dictator.
And now we're establishing democracy
which, of course, takes time.
But we have to stabilize the
middle east. The war was inevitable.
- You're not serious.
- Of course I'm serious.
Ma'am.
Ma'am ?
Will you complete this, please ?
Physicaltherapy to five west.
Physical therapy to five west.
I don't know if he had a colonoscopy
Or what his paternal
grandmother died of.
I don't. I don't know
the answers to anything.
How about his
insurance provider ?
I don't know.
Do you have his wallet ?
Maybe it's in his jacket.
Is that his jacket ?
Yeah.
Okay.
You don't think they
wanted a free eltion ?
Did you see those pictures ?
They were dancing in the streets,
- Literally.
- That doesn't mean they wanted to be
invaded and slaughtered.
I saw the pictures from Abu Ghraib, too,
and nobody was fucking dancing there.
That was an isolated group
of disturbed individuals.
Don't give me that.
Those orders came down from the top.
The top ! There's memos to prove it.
Wow !
The world is corrupt. How can that be ?
Freedom isn't free.
Oh, god ! What are you ?
Some redneck blogger pig ?
Come on. Name one
right, one civil liberty,
That doesn't have blood all over it,
that people haven't fought and died for.
We didn't go to war to
protect iraqi civil liberties.
- That's just a lame justification.
- I didn't say it was just.
But that's the way human
beings make progress.
We're violent. It's our nature.
It's a little naive to
expect anything different.
So you just rationalized
away all moral responsibility.
I guess you learned
that in law school.
What ?
oh, no.
- He's stable for the moment.
- Is he conscious ?
- Not yet.
- I called his specialist, Dr. Dipaolo,
- But he's out of town.
- That's all right.
His records are coming over
and we're going
to get him in for a cat scan right away.
- Okay, that's good. that's good
He's been completely
asymptomatic for two yeaars
- For two years, since the embolization ?
- As far as I know.
And immediately prior,
any nausea or pain ?
He said something about his arm.
Has there been any recent
physical or mental stress ?
Yeah, actually, I think he's
been under a lot of stress.
But nothing physical ?
Except...
Before he fell, there was...
Physical activity.
All right. Well, would
you characterize it
As extreme exertion ?
No.
No, but...
There was a climax.
Okay. That's helpful.
When there's new information,
we'll let you know.
Please. Thank you.
Dr. Klein, call pain management.
My mother's not answering her phone.
I tried her at your
father's. She's not there,
Not that she would be, but...
You want me to call George again ?
- Maybe he could come
- No. God, no.
I'm looking for my husband.
- I'm so sorry.
- I know.
David !
- Is he okay ?
- We're not sure.
What happened ?
I called 9-1-1.
He was at my house
when he collapsed.
He came to pick me up for church.
That was like two hours ago.
Dr. Duvall, 1421.
Right.
I want to see him.
They're doing a cat scan.
Okay, so...
- What, we wait ?
- Yeah.
This wasn't planned, you know.
I know.
What ?
My arm's numb.
- Are you all right ?
- Yeah, yeah.
Whole thing went to sleep
Sleep there for a second.
Maggie.
What are we going to do ?
Nothing.
I don't want to hurt anyone.
I don't, either.
I want to do it.
Cardio tech to room 322.
Cardio tech to 322.
There they are.
What's going on ? Is he okay ?
He's in radiology. We
don't know what it is yet.
where's mom ?
- I haven't reached her.
- What ?
- That sucks. She should be here.
- I know.
When can we see him ?
Probably after the cat scan.
Last we heard, he was still unconscious.
Okay.
This is my friend ted.
- This is my brother david.
- Hi.
I'm so sorry.
And my
sister-in-law Brenda.
- Hi.
- And Maggie.
Stepsister,
Former, so of.
Hi.
Why is she here ?
later.
Whenever I see a fire, I think of you.
It reminds me of the color of your hair.
Sometimes I feel like
all I have going for me
Is the color of my hair.
It reminds me of your spirit...
Your sexual spirit.
- What ?
- Nothing.
Let's talk a little.
We're talking.
You know what I'd like ?
What ?
I'd like to see life clearly,
But that's the first thing to fly out
the window when I get romantic.
I wonder if there's a way to
do it where that doesn't happen.
You're overthinking.
You need to just...
Let things flow.
You came back to me for a reason.
I did ? What reason ?
This.
This is dr. Fraker.
She's nate's neurosurgeon.
- Neurosurgeon ? Oh, god.
- What did you find ?
- There was a hemorrhage in his brain.
- How bad ?
Well, obviously, any hemorrhage
is bad, but I've seen worse.
We need to get him into the
O.R. as soon as possible.
Was it another avm ? Or did the
other surgery not work, or what ?
We're not going to know until we get
in there. We may not even know then.
Are there any other
options ? Sometimes there are.
Not this time. We have to stop the
bleeding before there's more damage.
- There's damage ?
- What kind of damage ?
We don't know yet. Maybe none,
But you should prepare yourselves
for possible... changes.
- "Changes. "
- We really need to see him.
I'm sorry. We need to move
on this right now.
I'll talk to you as soon as we finish.
It's going to be at least a few more
hours. Show them to the waiting room.
Mrs. Fisher, could you go with
Derrick and sign the papers ?
I'm Nate's wife.
Oh. Uh... I beg your pardon.
If everyone could follow me.
Fuck.
What are you doing up ? It's
the middle of the night.
You hurt ?
Fine. I give up.
How could you say I don't love
you ? How could you think that ?
What am I supposed to think ?
You treat me like shit.
We already argued about this. I
don't want to go through it again.
You're not supposed to love someone
who cheats on you. It's stupid.
It's weak. I know, because
i work with these women.
They get their hearts broken
every saturday night,
and I won't be like them.
I fuckin' refuse.
It will never happen again.
But then here I am in the same
house with you, and I'm so scared
Because you're closer
to me than my skin.
That's how much you're
a part of me, Rico.
I can't ever stop loving you.
That's why I treat u like shit.
Don't you get it ?
Got it.
Okay, rico. Bye.
I'm running out of battery.
Can I use your phone ?
Here. Take mine.
Thank you.
Where could she be ?
- She's not answering her cell ?
- She doesn't have one.
David,
I can't remember when they took him in.
How long has it been ?
I don't know.
I have to go outside to call keith.
Oh, god, what if something
happened to my mother ?
That's extremely unlikely.
I'm sure she'll call back soon.
I'm kind of flipping.
I don't blame you.
I think I'm going to leave. So would
someone give me a call and let me know-
I think you should stay.
You were with him. You might
know something that none of us do.
Did he just pass out ?
What were you guys doing ?
Nothing.
Talking.
Did he say something ?
Was he not feeling well ?
Could you tell something was wrong ?
No, he was fine till he...
Did he have his phone on ?
'Cause I called like 20 times.
- How long were you guys talking ?
- I don't know.
Well, it must have been
a great conversation.
What were you guys talking about ?
His daughter and his pregnant wife ?
You don't have to stay.
- I know.
- I mean it.
I've got people here for support.
Right.
- Oh, god, you're beautiful.
- Thank you.
Oh, wait. Ow !
I've fantasized about another
night with you in the woods,
Kissing you everywhere,
your soft, white skin.
There's a rock right under me.
- Did you think about me ever ?
- If you could just shift this way.
Tell me you missed me. Oh,
god, you feel wonderful.
- You're too heavy. Please.
- Would you hold me ?
- I can't breathe. Move.
- I want you naked. Say my name.
- Hiram !
- Yes, yes.
- Get off me !
- What ?
I can't do this.
Hey, would you like me to
go down to the cafeteria
And get you some tea or real food ?
No, I'm good with these. Thanks.
How are you feeling ?
- With the pregnancy ?
- Oh. Good, good.
No morning sickness.
She's kicking like a horse.
She ?
Yeah. Yeah, it's a girl.
- Congratulations.
- Thanks.
Have you picked a name ?
Well, the only one that nate
and I could agree on is willa.
Willa ? That's pretty.
- Yeah ?
- Yeah.
- A little sister for Maya.
Anthony and Durrell have
such a bond. It's beautiful.
I really admire your choice.
You didn't go for the
perfect little infant.
Well, we went for it.
We just didn't get it.
And I'm totally glad we didn't
Because these kids need us
And I love them to death.
I didn't know I'd feel like
this, like a lioness with my cubs.
Dr. Hoffman 308.
Dr. Hoffman, call 308.
Then there are days I want to kill them.
Well, that's part of the fun.
- Is he okay ?
- Was it the avm ?
Let me tell you
everything I know up front,
And then I'll try to
answer your questions.
He developed a new avm.
That's what ruptured and...
caused some herniation
and swelling in the brain.
We did manage to stop the bleeding
and to relieve the cranial pressure...
But there were some problems
With his heart rate and his breathing.
- What does that mean ?
- He's in a coma.
There may be some long-term effects
from everything that's happened.
We won't know for certain
until he wakes up,
and we don't know when he will.
Jesus.
- So he could be in a coma for... ?
- Days, weeks.
What kind of long-term effects ?
Loss of vision, memory,
Impairment of speech, movement.
But you can learn how
to speak and walk again.
My grandfather had a stroke, and he did.
That's right. That can happen.
But, like I said, we are not going
to know anything until he's conscious.
We really need to see
him as soon as possible.
Once he's out of
recovery. If all goes well,
We'll transfer him to the neuro
step-down unit in the morning, but...
let's just get him
through the night first, okay ?
- Hold good thoughts.
- Thank you, dr. Fraker.
Thank you for the worst
fucking news I ever heard.
He's alive.
That's something.
- Did you sleep with her ?
- Yes.
You're so fucking predictable.
- It wasn't about the sex.
- Oh, right, you fucked her because
- of silence and meaning and god.
- Yeah.
Not because we're having a hard time
and you need an illusion
to stick your dick in.
We're always having a hard time.
There's all this pain and
anger and struggle here.
I used to think it was
passion, but it's just drama.
You came to me. I had
my own fucking life
Before you turned up on the
doorstep, bleeding and crazy.
- Remember ?
- I remember. We have to face the truth.
We don't fit.
We never have. We weren't meant to be.
"Meant to be" ?
What quaker bullshit.
You think you and Maggie are meant to be
After you slept with her, what, once ?
- What are you, 15 ?
- No, I'm 40 years old.
And I see that there can be
peace between a man and a woman,
- And that's what I want.
- Fine.
Go for it.
I'm certainly not going
to beg you to stay.
But you might want to ask yourself,
"What kind of person am I ?"
What kind of man betrays his
pregnant wife and leaves her ?
It's better this way. You know it is.
Nate.
Nurse, he's awake.
- I'll go get the doctor.
- Nate.
Nate.
Do you know who I am ?
Brenda.
You had a cerebral hemorrhage.
We thought you might be in
a coma for months, but...
...here you are.
What's wrong with my arm and my leg ?
Well, they said you might
have problems just for awhile.
- Maya ?
- She's with my mother.
It was an emergency.
You were with Maggie.
Do you remember that ?
Yeah.
You're going to have
to step out, Mrs. Fisher.
We're going to run some tests.
- How long will that take ?
- A little while.
Here. Let me help you.
I'm going to go
tell everybody you're awake.
Chuck, get back in that bed.
Brenda ?
I think it's very childish that
you're not speaking to me, Hiram.
But suit yourself.
I don't want to say
something I'll regret.
Go ahead. What's one more
regret ? I'm full of them.
All right. I think it was
rude and selfish of you
To leave the tent last night.
You're not mad at me
for leaving the tent.
- You're mad at me for not having sex.
- Well, yes.
You were the one that
came into the salon.
Then you seduced me with
the promise of aperitifs.
Then it was your idea to go camping.
You led me on, then pushed me away.
I feel rejected and humiliated.
I didn't mean to lead you on.
I wanted to want to
have sex in the tent,
But when it came down to it, I couldn't.
Couldn't or wouldn't ?
What do you want me to do ? Just
lie there while you do whatever ?
I am not a receptacle.
There are other things you could
have done, but you didn't even offer.
- Do you mean oral ?
- Yes, or a hand job.
Hiram, a woman has to be in the mood
To do that stuff, or it's just no good.
I'm a sensitive man, but,
you know, I have needs.
Your needs are not my responsibility !
Where are you going ? You can't
survive out here on your own.
You have no wilderness skills.
Oh, go give yourself a hand job !
- Where's dr. Fraker ?
- She went home.
I'm her associate. I'm
following Nate at the moment.
- We can talk, or you could wait to talk
- No, no more waiting.
Okay, what nate had was called
an arterial venous malformation.
We know.
He had one before.
Oh, right. Here it is.
What happened this time
is this avm ruptured,
Causing herniation and bleeding.
We know. We've been here all night.
So you know the operation went
well and he was in a coma briefly ?
- Yes, we know.
- How is he now ?
His vitals are stable,
and everything looks good,
Except for a weakness
on your right side, Nate.
Yeah.
What about physical therapy ?
We'll start as soon as he's up to it.
When do you think he might
be able to leave the hospital ?
A week or two, if he
continues to improve.
- That's not long.
- Yes.
Are you okay ?
I am now.
Really ?
You put up a great
fight. We're all proud of you.
I've got a lot to live for.
We'll be right back.
Dr. Klein,
call pain management.
Dr. Klein, call pain management.
I know you want to see
Maya. I'll go pick her up.
Thanks.
Ruth, you came to me for a reason.
Yeah, this.
Ruthie, bring me my lunch.
I care for you. Let's rub heads.
It's perfectly normal to
live in a bomb shelter.
I'm your first love, Ruth,
The father of your children.
I'm where it all began.
Oh, Nathaniel.
Go on, durrell, it's your play.
Hey hey hey ! Quiet, all right ?
So we don't get busted by having
too many visitors in the room.
- Okay.
- Be careful, Durrell. Chuck's a shark.
There you go.
Anthony, come talk to your uncle Nate.
Is this too much action for you ?
No, no, it's good.
- They wanted to come and see you.
- No, I didn't.
Anthony.
Hey, don't worry about
your arm and your leg.
It feels strange.
I have to really concentrate
to make anything happen.
But it's not permanent.
There's a cop I know. They said he
would never get out of a wheelchair.
You know what ? Now he's running.
- Ha ! I won !
- What do you mean ?
You owe me a dollar.
Durrel, you're not taking
anybody's money.
Where's Anthony ?
He was right here.
Anthony, come back here.
I don't know how to thank you.
I'll think of a way.
No, I mean it.
I mean, how many guys
would spend the night
In a hospital on the first date ?
I mean, that is just fucking goodness.
- I didn't know you were like that.
- Not a big deal.
You'd do the same thing
for me, wouldn't you ?
I would now.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Your brother's fine.
All I could think about
during the parent-Teacher meeting
Was how much I wanted to smoke a joint.
- Maggie.
- I'm sorry. I don't mean to interrupt.
No. Please.
I won't stay. I just want to see him.
Stay.
I'm sure my boys are
creating mayhem somewhere.
I'll be back in a little bit.
- Hi.
Are you all right ?
Swear to me.
I swear.
If only I hadn't asked you for a ride.
I'm not sorry for anything.
You're making love with
somebody and your head explodes.
That's a good sign.
- Stop it.
You're awful.
I'm so relieved.
Last night was just...
100 years long.
So many things I want to say.
I don't know where to begin.
Just rest.
- Oh, hey, Maggie.
- Hi, Rico.
Take care, Nate. I'll be in touch.
What do you want ?
Man, oh, man, oh, man.
What the hell, nate ?
Pretty fuckin' bizarre, huh ?
David told me, but
I couldn't believe it.
- I mean, you were fine.
- I'm still fine.
What a shock.
I had to come by, but
i only got a minute.
There's an intake. This
guy got mauled a cougar.
- No shit.
- Yeah, right here in L.A.
He was walking in the canyon.
The ecotone.
Ecotone. It's the area where
Two ecological worlds overlap.
You know, like wilderness
and civilization.
Ecotone.
I'll be sure to say
that in the intake.
Excuse me. I notice you have a bus.
Courtney. Courtney.
Please, somebody. I
just want to go home.
Hi. I'm Courtney. Is there a problem ?
I'm not hungry.
Fine. Then don't eat.
- I'll take his.
- I want to go home.
Why are you acting so crazy ?
We are staying with uncle Nate
until we are sure that he is better.
Man, it's okay. Just chill.
No !
- Hey, get back here.
- He's going for the front door.
Durrell, stay here and
help me clean this up.
- What is wrong with him ?
- Are you blind ?
He hates hospitals. We always
had to go when mama O.D'd.
- Why didn't he tell us ?
- You didn't ask.
Can I go get him now ?
Yeah.
Look who's here.
- Daddy !
- Hey.
Hey, big girl.
Come on up.
Come here.
Give me a big hug, would you ? Come here.
I am very happy to see you.
Why don't you read your book, honey ?
You brought a book, huh ?
I was waiting for you at
the church last night...
... when you and Maggie were...
Talking.
I told you to go do what you want.
I guess you did.
I'm sorry. I never
waed it to go this way.
Listen.
I've been up all night,
Thinking and...
You're alive.
That's all that really matters.
We've been through
worse together, I guess,
And we'll get through this, too.
I don't think so.
What ?
Not together.
Are you saying what
I think you're saying ?
Yeah.
- What about Maya ?
- We'll talk about that.
That's a future conversation.
So that's it ? You're done ?
We're... We're not even going to try ?
We've been trying.
Both of us, for a long time.
Since the beginning.
We're just different, that's all.
Yeah. You're a narcissist.
I don't even think you're capable
Of committing to anybody
or anything, even yourself.
I'm not going to fight.
I am so tired of fighting.
Do you really want a husband again ?
Maybe. I don't really feel
any better as a single woman.
- Did the crazy husband beat you ?
- Oh, no, no.
He's a gentle person,
Sometimes boring.
I think he may want a
mother more than a wife.
They're all like that.
Have you had other boyfriends ?
Yes, unfortunately.
What did she say ?
All men are crazy. Stick
with the devil you know.
Where the fuck could mom be ?
- Sorry, chuck.
- That's okay.
I'm a buddhist. We don't
care about that shit.
First, I was worried,
but now I'm just pissed.
It's really irresponsible of her.
She wouldn't have been
able to handle it, anyway.
You know, she'd get all upset
And flap around and squawk.
We'd have to take care of her.
Poor mom,  she's so out there.
It's all this stuff with george.
It really did a job on her.
Well, she could still show
up for her own son's coma.
Okay, I'm going to go
home and take a shower.
I was going to say.
But then I'm going to come right back.
What are you going to do ? Watch the
nurses wake me up every 10 minutes ?
Okay. Will you call me later, please ?
Yep.
You, you rest.
- Good-Bye, Chuck.
- Good-Bye.
Dave, you should go, too.
Maybe later. I'll keep
you company a little while.
You look tired.
I am.
We'll watch tv.
- Hey, Chuck, turn it up, will you ?
- Yeah.
Nate !
Yo, Nate !
Fuck, dude, we've been honking
for, like, ever. Let's go.
We're going to be late.
Jesus, david. Watch the grip, man.
Lightweight.
Where's your suit ?
I'm wearing it, dude.
You stoked ?
- I guess.
You guess. You asshole,
We've been waiting for this
our whole fuckin' lives, man.
Oh, my motherfuckin' god.
This is so fuckin' weird.
What ?
I had this whole other idea of you.
I really thought you were this
whole completely other person.
You are so fuckin' toasted, man.
I don't know what it is. I must have
been dreaming or so fuckin' high.
Am I going to have to separate you boys ?
We are so fucking lost.
Give me that.
Whew ! Oh, man.
- I'm going in.
- Up to you.
- Nate, don't be stupid.
- Stupid ?
Stupid ? This is what we
came here to do, you asshole.
Play nice.
- Come on, bro ! You and me !
- There could be sharks !
Why don't you join him ?
- Why don't you join him ?
- Dave !
You gotta try this !
It's so fuckin' warm !
You wanna smoke some crack ?
Nate.